<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2013, 2014 David King <davidk@gnome.org> -->
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.gnome.Logs.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>GNOME Logs</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_TW">GNOME 紀錄</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_CN">GNOME 日志</name>
  <name xml:lang="vi">Nhật ký máy GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Журнали GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">GNOME Günlükler</name>
  <name xml:lang="th">ปูม GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">GNOME Loggar</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr@latin">Gnomovi zapisnici</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Гномови записници</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Dnevniki GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Záznamy prostredia GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Журналы GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Înregistrări GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">GNOME Logs</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Registos GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Przeglądarka dzienników GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="oc">Jornals GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Gnome Logboeken</name>
  <name xml:lang="ne">जिनोम लग</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">GNOME logger</name>
  <name xml:lang="ml">ഗ്നോം ലോഗുകള്‍</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">GNOME žurnāli</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">GNOME žurnalai</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">그놈 로그</name>
  <name xml:lang="kk">GNOME логтары</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Registri di GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">GNOME Log</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">GNOME Naplók</name>
  <name xml:lang="hr">GNOME Zapisi</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">GNOME יומנים</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Rexistros de GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="gd">Logaichean GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="fur">Regjistris di GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Journaux de GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Gnomen lokit</name>
  <name xml:lang="fa">وقایع گنوم</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">GNOMEren Erregistroak</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Registros de GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">GNOME Protokoloj</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_GB">GNOME Logs</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Καταγραφές GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">GNOME Protokoll</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">GNOME Logge</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Záznamy GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca@valencia">Registres del GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Registres del GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Журнали</name>
  <name xml:lang="be">Журналы GNOME</name>
  <summary>View detailed event logs for the system</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">檢視詳細的系統事件紀錄檔</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_HK">檢視詳細的系統事件紀錄檔</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">查看系统详细的事件日志</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="vi">Xem nhật ký sự kiện chi tiết của hệ thống</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Переглянути детальний журнал подій для системи</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Sistem için ayrıntılı olay günlüklerini görüntüle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="th">ดูปูมเหตุการณ์ของระบบอย่างละเอียด</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tg">Намоиш додни сабтҳои рӯйдодҳои ботафсил барои система</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="te">వ్యవస్థ కోసం వివరణాత్మకమైన కార్యక్రమ చిట్టాలను చూడండి</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Visa detaljerade händelseloggar för systemet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr@latin">Pregledajte opširne zapisnike događaja na sistemu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Прегледајте опширне записнике догађаја на систему</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Pokaži podrobne dnevniške zapise dogodkov sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Zobrazuje podrobné záznamy o udalostiach v systéme</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Просмотр подробной информации о событиях в системе</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Vizualizați jurnale de evenimente detaliate ale sistemului</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Veja registros detalhados de eventos do sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Ver registos detalhados de eventos do seu sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Wyświetlanie szczegółowych dzienników zdarzeń w systemie</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pa">ਸਿਸਟਮ ਲਈ ਵੇਰਵੇ ਸਮੇਤ ਈਵੈਂਟ ਲਾਗ ਵੇਖੋ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="oc">Veire en detalh los eveniments del sistèma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Inzage in de logboeken van het systeem</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ne">प्रणालीबाट लग विवरण हेर्नुहोस्</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nb">Vis detaljerte hendelseslogger for systemet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ml">സിസ്റ്റത്തിന്റെ വിശദമായ ഇവന്റ് ലോഗ് പ്രദര്‍ശിപ്പിക്കുക</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">Skatīt detalizētu informāciju par žurnāliem datorā</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Matykite sistemos įvykių detalius žurnalus</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">시스템의 자세한 이벤트 기록을 봅니다</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="kk">Жүйенің толығырақ ақпараты бар оқиғалар логын қарау</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Visualizza il registro degli eventi di sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Tilik log kejadian terinci bagi sistem</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">A rendszer részletes eseménynaplóinak megtekintése</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hr">Pogledajte opširnije događaje svojeg sustava</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">הצגת יומני אירועים מפורטים למערכת</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Ver rexistros de eventos detallados para o seu sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gd">Seall logaichean mionaideach air tachartasan an t-siostaim</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fur">Mostre il regjistri detaiât dai events di sisteme</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Afficher en détail les évènements du système</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Katsele järjestelmän yksityiskohtaisia tapahtumalokeja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fa">نمایش جزئیات وقایع برای سیستم</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Ikusi sistemako erregistroen gertaera xeheak</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Ver registros detallados de eventos del sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Vidi detalajn eventprotokolojn de la sistemo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en_GB">View detailed event logs for the system</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Δείτε λεπτομερείς καταγραφές συμβάντων για το σύστημα σας</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Detaillierte Ereignisprotokolle des Systems ansehen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Vis detaljerede begivenhedslogge for systemet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Zobrazte si podrobné záznamy událostí v systému</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca@valencia">Mostra els registres detallats d'esdeveniments del sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Mostra els registres detallats d'esdeveniments del sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bs">Pogledaj detaljne zapisnike o događajima u sistemu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Визуализация на журналите на събитията в системата</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="be">Прагляд падрабязных запісаў сістэмы</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="as">চিস্টেমৰ বাবে বিৱৰিত ঘটনা লগসমূহ দৰ্শন কৰক</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">يعرض سجلّات مفصّلة عن أحداث النظام</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="an">Veyer rechistros detallaus d'eventos d'o sistema</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Logs shows events from the systemd journal, and sorts them into
       categories, such as hardware and applications.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">《紀錄》會顯示 systemd 日誌的事件，並將它們依分別排序，像是硬體與應用程式。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_HK">Logs 會顯示 systemd 日誌的事件，並將它們根據分別排序，像是硬件與應用程式。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">日志查看器 显示来自 systemd 的日志并按“硬件”、“应用程序”等进行分类。</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">Ứng dụng xem nhật ký này cho ta xem nhật ký do máy tính ghi lại, và sắp xếp chúng thành từng nhóm, như là phần cứng và ứng dụng.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Журнал показує події з журналу systemd і сортує їх за різними категоріями.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Günlükler, systemd günlüğünden olayları gösterir ve bunları donanım ve uygulamalar gibi kategoriler halinde sıralar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">"ปูม" จะแสดงเหตุการณ์จากบันทึกของ systemd และคัดแยกเหตุการณ์เป็นหมวดๆ เช่น ฮาร์ดแวร์และโปรแกรม</p>
    <p xml:lang="tg">Сабтҳои рӯйдодҳо рӯйдодҳоро аз маҷаллаи системавӣ намоиш медиҳанд ва онҳоро ба категорияҳо, монанди сахтафзор ва нармафзор, мураттаб мекунад.</p>
    <p xml:lang="te">వ్యవస్థ జర్నలు, మరియు వాటిని వర్గాలుగా క్రమబద్దీకరించి (హార్డువేరు, అనువర్తనాలులా) వాటి నుండి కార్యక్రమాలను చిట్టాలు చూపిస్తాయి.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Loggar visar händelser från systemd-journalen och sorterar in dem i kategorier som exempelvis hårdvara eller program.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">Zapisnici prikazuju događaje iz sistem-d žurnala, i ređaju ih po kategorijama, recimo hardver i programi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Записници приказују догађаје из систем-д журнала, и ређају их по категоријама, рецимо хардвер и програми.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Program pokaže dogodke, ki jih je shranil systemd in jih združuje v kategorije, kot sta strojna oprema ali programi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Aplikácia záznamy zobrazuje udalosti zo žurnálu služby systemd a triedi ich do kategórií ako sú napríklad hardvér alebo aplikácie.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Приложение «Журналы» показывает события из журнала systemd и упорядочивает их по категориям (аппаратные, программные).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Înregistrări afișează evenimente din jurnalul systemd, și le sortează pe categorii, precum hardware și aplicații.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Logs mostra eventos de sistema Journal através de systemd e os ordena em categorias, como hardware e aplicativos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Registos mostra os eventos do jornal systemd e ordena-os em categorias, tais como equipamento e aplicações.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Przeglądarka dzienników wyświetla zdarzenia z dziennika systemd i porządkuje je według kategorii, takich jak sprzęt i programy.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pa">ਲਾਗਸ ਸਿਸਟਮ ਜਰਨਲ ਤੋਂ ਈਵੈਂਟ ਵਿਖਾਉਂਦਾ ਹੈ ਅਤੇ ਉਹਨਾਂ ਵਰਗਾਂ ਮੁਤਾਬਕ ਜਿਵੇਂ ਕਿ ਹਾਰਡਵੇਅਰ ਤੇ ਐਪਲੀਕੇਸ਼ਨ ਵਿੱਚ ਵੰਡਦਾ ਹੈ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Jornals aficha los eveniments del jornal de systemd, e los tria per categorias, talas coma material e aplicacions.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Logboeken toont gebeurtenissen uit het systemd-logboek en toont deze in verschillende categorieën, zoals hardware en toepassingen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Logger viser hendelser fra systemd-journalen og sorterer dem inn i kategorier slik som maskinvare og programmer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ml">സിസ്റ്റംഡി ജേര്‍ണലില്‍ നിന്നുള്ള ഇവന്റ് ലോഗുകളെ പ്രദര്‍ശിപ്പിക്കുക,ഹാര്‍ഡ്‍വെയര്‍ ആപ്ലിക്കേഷന്‍ എന്നിവപോലെ വിഭാഗങ്ങളായി തരംതിരിക്കുക</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">Žurnāli rāda notikumus no systemd žurnāla un kārto tos kategorijās, piemēram, aparatūra un lietotnes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Žurnalai rodo įvykius iš systemd žurnalo bei rūšiuoja juos į kategorijas, tokias kaip aparatinės įrangos ir programų.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">기록에서는 systemd 저널에서 이벤트를 표시하고, 하드웨어나 프로그램 등 분류에 따라 정렬합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">Логтар systemd журналынан оқиғаларды көрсетеді, және де оларды құрылғылар, қолданбалар сияқты санаттар бойынша сұрыптайды.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Registri mostra eventi dal giornale di systemd e li ordina per categorie come hardware e applicazioni.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Log menampilkan peristiwa dari jurnal systemd, dan memilah mereka ke dalam kategori-kategori, seperti perangkat keras dan aplikasi</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Naplók eseményeket jelenít meg a rendszernaplóból és kategóriákba rendezi azokat, úgymint hardver és alkalmazások.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">Prikazani zapisi događaja iz systemd dnevnika koji su razvrstani u kategorije, poput hradvera i aplikacija.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">יומנים מציגה אירועים מהיומן systemd ומסדרת אותם בקטגוריות כגון חומרה ויישומים.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Rexistros mostra os eventos do diario de systemd e ordénaos en categorías, como por exemplo hardware e aplivativos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gd">Seallaidh Logaichean na tachartasan on leabhar-aithris systemd agus seòrsaichidh e ann an roinnean-seòrsa iad, can bathar-cruaidh is aplacaidean.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fur">Il regjistri al mostre events dal gjornâl di systemd e ju ordene par categoriis, par hardware e aplicazions.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Journaux affiche les évènements du journal de systemd, et les trie par catégories, telles que matériel et applications.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Lokit näyttää systemd:n tapahtumasanomia ja jakaa ne luokkiin, kuten laitteisto ja sovellukset.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fa">وقایع، رویدادها را از وقایع systemd نمایش و آنها را در دسته‌بندی‌های مختلف، مثل سخت‌افزار و برنامه، منظم می‌کند.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Logs-ek systemd egunkariak sortutako gertaerak bistaratzeaz gain, haiek Hardwarea edo Aplikazioak bezalako kategorietan antolatzen ditu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Registros muestra eventos del registro de systemd, y los ordena en categorías tales como hardware o aplicaciones.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Protokoloj montras eventojn de la systemd-protokolo, kaj ordigas ilin laŭ kategorioj, kiel aparataro kaj aplikaĵoj.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">Logs shows events from the systemd journal, and sorts them into categories, such as hardware and applications.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Η εφαρμογή Καταγραφές εμφανίζει συμβάντα από το systemd journal και τα ταξινομεί σε κατηγορίες, όπως υλικό και εφαρμογές.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Protokoll zeigt Ereignisse aus dem »systemd«-Protokoll und sortiert sie nach Kategorien wie z.B. Hardware oder Anwendungen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Logge viser begivenheder fra systemd-journalen, og sorterer dem i kategorier såsom hardware og programmer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Aplikace Záznamy zobrazuje události ze žurnálu systemd a řadí je do kategorií, jako jsou třeba hardware nebo aplikace.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca@valencia">El Registres mostra els esdeveniments del diari systemd i els ordena per categories com el maquinari i les aplicacions.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Registres mostra els esdeveniments del diari systemd i els ordena per categories com el maquinari i les aplicacions.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Dnevnici prikazuju događaje iz sistemskih časopisa, te ih sortira u kategorije kao što su hardver i aplikacije.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Можете да преглеждате журналните съобщения от systemd, да ги филтрирате и подреждате по атрибути и категории.</p>
    <p xml:lang="be">Журнал паказвае здарэнні ў сістэмным журнале і сартуе іх па катэгорыях, такіх як "апаратныя" і "дастасаванні".</p>
    <p xml:lang="as">লগসমূহে systemd জাৰ্নেলৰ পৰা ঘটনাসমূহ দেখুৱায়, আৰু সিহতক বিভাগসমূহ, যেনে হাৰ্ডৱেৰ আৰু এপ্লিকেচনসমূহত সজায়।</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">يُظهر 'سجلّات' الاحداث من يوميّات عفريت النظام (systemd)، ويصنّفها إلى فئات، مثل فئتي العتاد والتطبيقات.</p>
    <p xml:lang="an">Rechistros amuestra eventos d'o rechistro de systemd, y los ordena en categorías tals como hardware u aplicacions.</p>
    <p>Using Logs you can search your logs by typing a search term, and
       view detailed information about each event by clicking on it.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">透過《紀錄》您可以輸入搜尋詞語來搜尋您的紀錄檔，並且點選每個事件就能檢視詳細的資訊。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_HK">使用 Logs 你可以輸入搜尋詞語來搜尋你的紀錄檔，並且點選每個事件就能檢視詳細的資訊。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">使用 日志查看器 时您可以输入条件在日志中搜索，点击某个事件可以查看它的详细信息。</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">Dùng ứng dụng xem nhật ký này, bạn có thể tìm trong nhật ký bằng cách gõ các hạng mục muốn tìm, và hiển thị chi tiết các thông tin về từng sự kiện bằng cách bấm chuột vào nó.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Програма може шукати журнали і переглядати подробиці про кожну подію, якщо натиснути на неї.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Günlükleri kullanarak, bir arama terimi yazarak günlüklerde arama yapabilir ve her olayın üzerine tıklayarak hakkındaki ayrıntılı bilgileri görüntüleyebilirsiniz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">ด้วย "ปูม" คุณสามารถค้นปูมต่างๆ ของคุณได้โดยป้อนคำค้น และสามารถดูข้อมูลรายละเอียดเกี่ยวกับแต่ละเหตุการณ์ได้โดยคลิกที่เหตุการณ์นั้นๆ</p>
    <p xml:lang="tg">Бо истифодаи сабти рӯйдодҳо шумо метавонед сабти рӯйдодҳои худро аз рӯи калимаҳои калидӣ ҷустуҷӯ кунед ва бо зеркунӣ ба онҳо маълумоти ботафсилро намоиш диҳед.</p>
    <p xml:lang="te">చిట్టాలతో వెతుకులాట పదాన్ని టంకింటి మీ చిట్టాలను వెతకవచ్చు, మరియు ప్రతీ కార్యక్రమం పై నొక్కడం ద్వారా వివరణాత్మకమైన సమాచారాన్ని చూడవచ్చు.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Med Loggar kan du söka dina loggar genom att skriva in en sökterm. Se sedan detaljerad information om enstaka händelser genom att klicka på dem.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">Upotrebom Zapisnika možete da pretražujete vaše zapisnike upisivanjem pojma, i da vidite opširne podatke o svakom događaju klikom na njega.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Употребом Записника можете да претражујете ваше записнике уписивањем појма, и да видите опширне податке о сваком догађају кликом на њега.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Program omogoča preiskovanje dnevnikov z vpisom iskalnega niza in pregled podrobnosti vsakega dogodka.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Použitím aplikácie Záznamy môžete vyhľadať zadaný výraz a kliknutím na udalosť zobraziť podrobné informácie o každej udalosti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">С помощью приложения «Журналы» вы можете выполнять поиск по журналам и просматривать подробную информацию о событиях.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Folosind Înregistrări puteți căuta prin înregistrările dumneavoastră folosind un termen de căutare, și aveți acces la informații detaliate referitoare la fiecare eveniment printr-un simplu clic.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Ao usar este aplicativo, você poderá pesquisar seus registros digitando um termo de pesquisa e poderá ver informações detalhadas sobre cada evento ao clicar neles.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Utilizar o Registos permite-lhe procurar os seus registos através de termos de pesquisa e ver informações detalhadas sobre cada evento com um simples clique.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Za pomocą przeglądarki dzienników można przeszukiwać dzienniki wpisując szukany termin oraz wyświetlać szczegółowe informacje o każdym zdarzeniu po jego kliknięciu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pa">ਲਾਗਸ ਦੀ ਵਰਤੋਂ ਕਰਕੇ ਤੁਸੀਂ ਖੋਜ ਸ਼ਬਦ ਲਿਖ ਕੇ ਆਪਣੇ ਲਾਗ ਵਿੱਚ ਲੱਭ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ ਅਤੇ ਹਰੇਕ ਈਵੈਂਟ ਉੱਤੇ ਕਲਿੱਕ ਕਰਕੇ ਉਸ ਬਾਰੇ ਵੇਰਵੇ ਸਮੇਤ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਵੇਖ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Amb Jornals, podètz recercar dins los jornals en picant un tèrme e visualizar d'informacions detalhadas a prepaus de cada eveniment en clicant dessús.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Met Logboeken kunt u gebeurtenissen doorzoeken door een zoekterm in te typen en vervolgens detailinformatie inzien door op een gebeurtenis te klikken.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Med Logger kan du søke i dine logger ved å skrive inn teksten du søker etter og du kan vise detaljert informasjon om hver hendelse ved å klikke på den.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ml">ലോഗുകള്‍ ഉപയോഗിച്ച് തിരച്ചില്‍ വാക്ക് നല്‍കി നിങ്ങള്‍ക്ക് ലോഗുകള്‍ തിരയാം, ഓരോ സന്ദര്‍ഭത്തിന്റെയും വിശദവിവരം അതില്‍ ക്ലിക്ക് ചെയ്തു കാണാം</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">Izmantojot “Žurnālus” jūs varat meklēt savos žurnālos, rakstot meklējamo tekstu un skatot detalizēto informāciju par katru notikumu, uz tā uzspiežot.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Naudodami žurnalus galite ieškoti žurnaluose įvesdami paieškos sąlygą bei matyti detalią informaciją apie kiekvieną įvykį paspaudę ant jo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">검색어를 입력해서 기록을 검색할 수 있습니다. 또 이벤트를 눌러서 정보를 자세히 볼 수도 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">Логтар көмегімен сіз іздеу сөзін енгізу арқылы іздей аласыз, ал, оқиға туралы көбірек білу үшін, оған шерте аласыз.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">È possibile eseguire ricerche nei propri registri digitando termini di ricerca e visualizzare informazioni dettagliate sugli eventi facendo clic su di essi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Memakai Log Anda dapat mencari catatan log Anda dengan mengetikkan istilah yang ingin dicari, dan melihat informasi terrinci tentang setiap kejadian dengan mengkliknya.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Naplók használatával keresési kifejezés begépelésével kereshet a naplókban és megtekintheti minden esemény részletes információit, ha rájuk kattint.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">Korištenjem Zapisa možete pretražiti svoje zapise upisivanjem izraza pretrage i vidjeti opširnije informacije o svakom događaju klikom na njega.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">בעזרת יומנים ניתן לחפש בקובצי רישום המערכת שלך על ידי הקלדת מונח ואז לצפות בפרטים על כל אחד מהאירועים על ידי לחיצה עליו.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Ao usar Rexistros pode buscar nos seus rexistros escribindo na caixa de busca, e ver información detallada sobre cada evento premendo nel.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gd">Le taic Logaichean, ’s urrainn dhut lorg sna logaichean agad le facal-luirg agus mion-fhiosrachadh a shealltainn air gach tachartas ’s tu a’ briogadh air.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fur">Tu puedis cirî tai tiei regjistris scrivint tiermins di ricercje e mostrâ informazions detaiadis sui events fasint clic su di chei.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Avec Journaux, vous pouvez rechercher dans les journaux en saisissant un terme et visualiser des informations détaillées à propos de chaque évènement en cliquant dessus.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Lokisovelluksen avulla voit etsiä tapahtumia lokeista, ja tarkastella yksittäisiä tapahtumia napsauttamalla niitä.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fa">با استفاده از رویدادها می‌توانید وقایع خود را با تایپ کردن آنها جست‌وجو کنید و جزئیات اطلاعات مربوط به هر رویداد را با کلیک کردن بر روی آن ببینید.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Logs erabiltzean erregistroak bila ditzakezu, eta gertaera bakoitzaren informazio xehea ikus dezakezu haren gainean klik eginez gero.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Al usar Registros puede buscar en sus registros escribiendo un término de búsqueda y ver información detallada sobre cada evento al pulsar sobre él.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Uzante Protokolojn vi povas serĉi viajn protokolojn tajpante serĉvorton, kaj vidi detalajn informojn pri ĉiu evento alklakante gin.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">Using Logs you can search your logs by typing a search term, and view detailed information about each event by clicking on it.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Χρησιμοποιώντας τις Καταγραφές μπορείτε να αναζητήσετε στα δικά σας αρχεία καταγραφών πληκτρολογώντας έναν όρο αναζήτησης και να προβάλετε λεπτομερείς πληροφορίες για κάθε συμβάν πατώντας πάνω του.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Mit Protokoll können Sie Ihre Systemprotokolle durch tippen eines Schlagwortes durchsuchen und detaillierte Informationen über die einzelnen Ereignisse ansehen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Med Logge kan du søge i dine logge ved at skrive et søgebegreb, og vise detaljerede oplysninger om hver begivenhed ved at klikke på den.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Díky aplikaci Záznamy můžete ve svých záznamech vyhledávat jednoduše napsáním výrazu a ke každé události si pak kliknutím zobrazit podrobnosti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca@valencia">Amb el Logs podeu buscar els vostres registres teclejant un terme de busca i veure la informació detallada sobre cada esdeveniment fent-hi clic.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Amb el Logs podeu cercar els vostres registres teclejant un terme de cerca i veure la informació detallada sobre cada esdeveniment fent-hi clic.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Korištenjem Dnevnika možete pretraživati Vae dnevnike upisivanjem traženog pojma, i pogledati detaljne informacije o svakom događaju tako što ćete kliknuti na njeg.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Можете да търсите по израз и да разглеждате детайлната информация за събитие като го натиснете.</p>
    <p xml:lang="be">У дастасаванні "Журналы" вы можаце шукаць вашыя запісы і глядзець падрабязнасці пра здарэнні пстрыкнуўшы па іх.</p>
    <p xml:lang="as">লগসমূহ ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি আপুনি আপোনাৰ লগসমূহক এটা সন্ধান বিষয় টাইপ কৰি সন্ধান কৰিব পাৰিব, আৰু প্ৰতিটো ঘটনাৰ বিষয়ে বিৱৰিত তথ্য তাত ক্লিক কৰি পাব।</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">يمكنك باستخدام 'سجلّات' البحث في السجلّات بكتابة عبارة بحث، وعرض معلومات مفصّلة عن كلّ حدث بالنقر عليه.</p>
    <p xml:lang="an">Al usar Rechistros puede buscar en os suyos rechistros escribindo un termin de busca y veyer información detallada sobre cada evento en pretar sobre el.</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot height="575" width="1000" type="default">
      <image>http://amigadave.com/temp/gnome-logs-default.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Logs</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugzilla.gnome.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=gnome-logs</url>
  <url type="donation">http://www.gnome.org/friends/</url>
  <url type="help">https://help.gnome.org/users/gnome-logs/stable/</url>
  <update_contact>davidk@gnome.org</update_contact>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>AppMenu</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <translation type="gettext">gnome-logs</translation>
</component>
