<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2016 Robert Roth -->
<component type="desktop">
  <id>gnome-system-monitor.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <name>GNOME System Monitor</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_TW">GNOME 系統監控程式</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_HK">GNOME 系統監控程式</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_CN">GNOME 系统监视器</name>
  <name xml:lang="vi">Theo dõi hệ thống GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Системний монітор GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="ug">گىنوم سىستېما كۆزەتكۈچ</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">GNOME Sistem Gözlemcisi</name>
  <name xml:lang="th">เครื่องมือเฝ้าสังเกตระบบของ GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="tg">Монитори системаи GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="te">గ్నోమ్ వ్యవస్థ పర్యవేక్షకం</name>
  <name xml:lang="ta">GNOME கணினி கண்காணிப்புக் கருவி</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">GNOME Systemövervakare</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr@latin">Gnomov pratilac sistema</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Гномов пратилац система</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Sistemski nadzornik za GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">GNOME monitor systému</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Системный монитор среды GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Monitor de sistem GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Monitor do sistema GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Monitor de sistema GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Monitor systemu GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਗਨੋਮ ਸਿਸਟਮ ਨਿਗਰਾਨ</name>
  <name xml:lang="or">GNOME ତନ୍ତ୍ର ପ୍ରଦର୍ଶିକା</name>
  <name xml:lang="oc">Monitor sistèma GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Gnome Systeemmonitor</name>
  <name xml:lang="ne">जिनोम प्रणाली निगरानी</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">GNOME systemovervåking</name>
  <name xml:lang="mr">GNOME सिस्टम मॉनिटर</name>
  <name xml:lang="ml">ഗ്നോം സിസ്റ്റം നിരീക്ഷകന്‍</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">GNOME sistēmas pārraugs</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">GNOME sistemos monitorius</name>
  <name xml:lang="ky">GNOME тутум монитору</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">그놈 시스템 정보</name>
  <name xml:lang="kn">GNOME ಗಣಕ ಮೇಲ್ವಿಚಾರಕ</name>
  <name xml:lang="km">កម្មវិធី​ត្រួតពិនិត្យ​ប្រព័ន្ធ​របស់ GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="kk">GNOME жүйелік бақылаушысы</name>
  <name xml:lang="ja">GNOME システムモニター</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Monitor di sistema GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="is">GNOME Kerfisvakt</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">GNOME Monitor Sistem</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">GNOME rendszerfigyelő</name>
  <name xml:lang="hr">GNOME nadgledatelj sustava</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">गनोम तंत्र मॉनीटर</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">צג המערכת מבית GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="gu">GNOME સિસ્ટમ મૉનિટર</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Monitor do sistema de GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="gd">Monatair an t-siostaim GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="ga">Monatóir an Chórais GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="fur">Monitor di sisteme GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Moniteur système de GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Gnomen järjestelmän valvonta</name>
  <name xml:lang="fa">پایشگر سیستم گنوم</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">GNOMEren sistemaren monitorea</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">GNOME süsteemijälgija</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Monitor del sistema de GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">GNOME Sistemmonitoro</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_GB">GNOME System Monitor</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Παρακολούθηση συστήματος GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">GNOME Systemüberwachung</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">GNOME-Systemovervågning</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Sledování systému GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca@valencia">Monitor del sistema del GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Monitor del sistema del GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">GNOME Monitor Sistema</name>
  <name xml:lang="bn_IN">GNOME সিস্টেম মনিটর</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Наблюдение на системата</name>
  <name xml:lang="be">Сістэмны назіральнік GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="as">GNOME চিস্টেম মনিটৰ</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">مراقب نظام جنوم</name>
  <name xml:lang="an">Monitor d'o sistema d'o GNOME</name>
  <summary>View and manage system resources</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">檢視與管理系統資源</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_HK">檢視與管理系統資源</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">查看和管理系统资源</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="vi">Xem và quản lý tài nguyên hệ thống</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Переглядати та керувати системними ресурсами</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Sistem kaynaklarını görüntüleyin ve yönetin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="th">ดูและจัดการทรัพยากรระบบ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tg">Намоиш додан ва идора кардани сарчашмаҳои системавӣ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="te">వ్యవస్థ వనరులను దర్శించు నిర్వహించు</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ta">கணினி வளங்களைக் காணவும் நிர்வகிக்கவும் உதவுகிறது</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Visa och hantera systemresurser</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr@latin">Pregledajte i upravljajte resursima sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Прегледајте и управљајте ресурсима система</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Pregled in upravljanje s sistemskimi viri</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Zobrazuje a spravuje systémové prostriedky</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Просмотр и управление ресурсами системы</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Vizualizează și administrează resursele de sistem</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Veja e gerencie recursos do sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Ver e gerir recursos de sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Wyświetlanie i zarządzanie zasobami systemu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pa">ਸਿਸਟਮ ਸਰੋਤ ਵੇਖੋ ਅਤੇ ਇੰਤਜ਼ਾਮ ਕਰੋ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="oc">Veire e gerir las ressorsas del sistèma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Systeembronnen bekijken en beheren</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ne">प्रणाली स्रोतहरू हेर्नुहोस् र प्रब्नध गर्नुहोस्</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nb">Vis og håndter systemressurser</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="mr">प्रणाली स्रोतचे अवलोकन आणि व्यवस्थापन करा</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ml">സിസ്റ്റം റിസോഴ്സുകള്‍ കാണുകയും കൈകാര്യം ചെയ്യുകയും ചെയ്യുക</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">Skatiet un pārvaldiet sistēmas resursus</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Matyti ir tvarkyti sistemos išteklius</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">시스템 자원을 보고 관리합니다</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="kn">ವ್ಯವಸ್ಥೆಯ ಸಂಪನ್ಮೂಲಗಳನ್ನು ನೋಡಿ ಮತ್ತು ನಿರ್ವಹಿಸಿ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="km">មើល និង​គ្រប់គ្រងធនធាន​ប្រព័ន្ធ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="kk">Жүйелік ресурстарды қарау және басқару</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">システムリソースの表示と管理を行います</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Visualizza e gestisce le risorse di sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="is">Skoða og stjórna kerfistilföngum</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Menampilkan dan mengelola sumber daya sistem</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Rendszer-erőforrások megjelenítése és kezelése</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hr">Nadgledajte i upravljajte resursima sustava</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hi">तंत्र संसाधन देखें और बदलें</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">הצגה וניהול משאבי מערכת</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Ver e xestionar os recursos do sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gd">Seall is stiùirich goireasan an t-siostaim</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fur">Visualiza e gjestìs lis risorsis di sisteme</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Voir et gérer les ressources du système</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Katsele ja hallitse järjestelmän resursseja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fa">نمایش و مدیریت منابع سیستم</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Ikusi eta kudeatu sistemaren baliabideak</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Süsteemi ressursside kuvamine ja haldus</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Ver y gestionar los recursos del sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Vidigi kaj administri sistemrizurcojn</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en_GB">View and manage system resources</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Δείτε και διαχειριστείτε τους πόρους του συστήματος</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Systemressourcen anzeigen und verwalten</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Gennemse og håndter systemressourcer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Zobrazit a spravovat systémové prostředky</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca@valencia">Visualitzeu i gestioneu els recursos del sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Visualitzeu i gestioneu els recursos del sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bs">Pregled i upravljanje resursima sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bn_IN">সিস্টেম রিসোর্সগুলি দেখুন এবং ব্যবস্থাপনা করুন</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Наблюдение и управление на системните ресурси</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="be">Прагляд і кіраванне сістэмнымі рэсурсамі</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="as">চিস্টেমৰ সম্পদসমূহ চাওক আৰু ব্যৱস্থাপনা কৰক</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">اعرض و أدِر موارد النظام</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="an">Veyer y chestionar os recursos d'o sistema</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      System Monitor is a process viewer and system monitor with
      an attractive, easy-to-use interface. 
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">系統監控是程序檢視器與系統監視器，具有吸引人、易於使用的介面。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_HK">系統監控是程序檢視器與系統監視器，具有吸引人、易於使用的介面。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">系统监视器是一个界面易用的进程查看器和系统监视器。</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">Ứng dụng theo dõi hệ thống là phần mềm xem và theo dõi các tiến trình hệ thống với một giao diện hấp dẫn và dễ dùng.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Системний монітор — переглядач процесів з приємним і зручним інтерфейсом.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Sistem Gözlemcisi çekici ve kullanımı kolay arayüze sahip bir süreç görüntüleyici ve sistem izleyicisidir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">เครื่องมือเฝ้าสังเกตระบบเป็นเครื่องมือสำหรับดูโพรเซสและเฝ้าสังเกตระบบ ที่หน้าตาดึงดูดและใช้ง่าย</p>
    <p xml:lang="tg">Назорати система - ин намоишгари равандҳо ва назорати система мебошад, ки бо интерфейси ҷолиб ва осон таркиб меёбад.</p>
    <p xml:lang="te">వ్యవస్థ పర్యవేక్షకి అనేది ఒక ప్రోసెస్ దర్శించునది మరియు వ్యవస్థ పర్యవేక్షకి ఆకర్షణీయమైన, సులువుగా-ఉపయోగించగల ఇంటర్ఫేస్ అందించును.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ta">கணினி கண்காணிப்புக் கருவியானது அழகிய மற்றும் பயன்படுத்த எளிதான இடைமுகத்தைக் கொண்ட செயலாக்கங்கள் காட்டும் கருவியும் கணினிக் கண்காணிப்புக் கருவியுமாகும்.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Systemövervakare är en processvisare och systemövervakare med ett attraktivt, användarvänligt gränssnitt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">Pratilac sistema je pregledač procesa i pratilac sistema sa privlačnim sučeljem lak za korišćenje.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Пратилац система је прегледач процеса и пратилац система са привлачним сучељем лак за коришћење.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Nadzornik sistema je program za ogled in nadzor sistemskih opravil.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Monitor systému je zobrazovač procesov a monitor systému s atraktívnym a ľahko použiteľným rozhraním.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Системный монитор — простой инструмент для просмотра и управления процессами.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Monitor Sistem este un vizualizator de procese și un monitor de sistem cu o interfață atractivă, ușor de folosit.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">O Monitor do sistema é um visualizador de processos e monitor de sistema com interface atraente e fácil de usar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Monitor de sistema é um visualizador de processos e monitor de sistema com um ambiente apelativo e de fácil utilização.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Monitor systemu to przeglądarka procesów i monitor systemu posiadający atrakcyjny, łatwy w użyciu interfejs.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pa">ਸਿਸਟਮ ਨਿਗਰਾਨ ਵਰਤਣ ਲਈ ਸੌਖੇ ਇੰਟਰਫੇਸ ਵਾਲਾ ਪਰੋਸੈਸ ਦਰਸ਼ਕ ਅਤੇ ਸਿਸਟਮ ਨਿਗਰਾਨ ਹੈ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Lo Monitor sistèma es un visionador de processus e monitor sistèma amb una interfàcia conviviala e de bon utilizar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Systeemmonitor is een procesviewer en systeembewaker met een aantrekkelijke, eenvoudig te gebruiken interface.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ne">प्रणाली मनिटर एक प्रक्रिया दर्शक र प्रणाली मनिटर एक आकर्षक, सजिलो प्रयोग इन्टरफेस हो</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Systemmonitor viser prosesser og overvåker systemet i et attraktivt grensesnitt som er lett å bruke.</p>
    <p xml:lang="mr">सिस्टम मॉनिटर प्रोसेस व्युअर आहे आणि देखनीय, वापरण्याजोगी सोप्या संवादसह सिस्टम मॉनिटर आहे.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ml">സിസ്റ്റംമോണിറ്റര്‍ ഒരു പ്രക്രീയാ കാഴ്ചക്കാരനാണ് അതിന് ആകര്‍ഷകവും എളുപ്പം ഉപയോഗിക്കാവുന്നതുമായ സമ്പര്‍ക്കമുഖമുണ്ട്.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">Sistēmas pārraugs ir procesu procesu un sistēmas pārraudzītājs ar viegli lietojamu saskarni.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Sistemos monitorius yra procesų stebyklė bei sistemos monitorius su patrauklia ir paprasta naudoti sąsaja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">시스템 정보 프로그램은 실행 중인 프로세스를 보고 시스템 정보를 보는 프로그램으로 보기 좋고 사용하기 쉽습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="kn">ಗಣಕ ಮೇಲ್ವಿಚಾರಕ ಎನ್ನುವುದು ಒಂದು ಆಕರ್ಶಕವಾದ, ಬಳಕೆಗೆ ಸುಲಭವಾದ ಬಳಕೆದಾರ ಸಂಪರ್ಕಸಾಧನವನ್ನು ಹೊಂದಿರುವ ಒಂದು ಪ್ರಕ್ರಿಯೆ ವೀಕ್ಷಕ ಮತ್ತು ವ್ಯವಸ್ಥೆಯ ಮೇಲ್ವಿಚಾರಕವಾಗಿದೆ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="km">​កម្មវិធី​ត្រួត​ពិនិត្យ​ប្រព័ន្ធ​គឺ​ជា​ដំណើរការ​របស់​កម្មវិធី​មើល និង​ការ​ពិនិត្យ​ប្រព័ន្ធ​ដែល​មាន​ចំណុច​ប្រទាក់​ស្អាត និង​ងាយស្រួល​ប្រើ។</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">Жүйелік бақылаушы - интерфейсі икемді әрі қолдануға ыңғайлы, үрдістерді қарауға және жүйені бақылауға арналған сайман.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">GNOME システムモニターは、魅力的で使いやすいインターフェースを備えたプロセスビューアー兼システムモニターです。</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">«Monitor di sistema» è un visualizzatore di processi e delle risorse di sistema, dotato di un'interfacca semplice da usare.</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">Kerfisvaktin er forrit fyrir ferlis- og kerfisvakt í einföldu og auðskiljanlegu viðmóti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Monitor Sistem adalah aplikasi pemantau serta pengelola kinerja sistem dengan tampilan yang atraktif serta mudah dipakai.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Rendszerfigyelő egy folyamatmegjelenítő és rendszerfigyelő alkalmazás vonzó, egyszerűen használható felülettel.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">Nadgledatelj sustava je preglednik procesa i nadgledatelj sustava s dopadljivim, lakim za korištenje sučeljem.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">तंत्र मॉनिटर प्रक्रिया प्रदर्शक है और तंत्र मॉनिटर एक आकर्षक और सुगम अंतरफलक से.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">צג המערכת הוא מציג תהליכים ועוקב אחר המערכת עם ממשק מרהיב וקל לשימוש</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">O monitor do sistema é un visor de procesos e un monitor do sistema con unha interface bonita e doada de usar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gd">’S e sealladair phròiseasan is monatair an t-siostam le eadar-aghaidh eireachdail is furasta cleachdadh a th’ ann am Monatair an t-siostaim</p>
    <p xml:lang="fur">“Monitor di sisteme” al è un visualizadôr di procès e des risorsis di sisteme, dotât di une interface semplice di doprâ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Le Moniteur système est un visionneur de processus et moniteur système avec une interface conviviale et facile à utiliser.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Järjestelmän valvonta mahdollistaa prosessien ja resurssien hallinnan helppokäyttöisellä käyttöliittymällä.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fa">پایشگر سیستم، یک نمایشگر فراروندها و یک نظارت کننده‌ی سیستم، با یک واسط کاربری جذاب و ساده است.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Prozesuen ikustaile eta sistema monitore bat da erabilera errazeko interfaze itxuroso batekin.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Süsteemijälgija on atraktiivse lihtsa kasutajaliidesega protsesside kuvaja ja monitoorija</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Monitor del sistema es un visor de procesos y un monitor del sistema con una interfaz atractiva y fácil de usar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Sistemmonitoro estas procezvidigilo kaj monitoro, kun alloga kaj facile uzebla fasado.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">System Monitor is a process viewer and system monitor with an attractive, easy-to-use interface.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Η Παρακολούθηση συστήματος, προβάλει τις διεργασίες και παρακολουθεί το σύστημα με ελκυστική και εύχρηστη διεπαφή.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Die Systemüberwachung ist ein Prozessbetrachter mit einer attraktiven und einfach zu verwendenden Benutzeroberfläche.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Systemovervågning er en procesfremviser og systemovervåger med en attraktiv brugergrænseflade, som er nem at bruge.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Sledování systému je prohlížeč procesů a sledování systému v přívětivém uživatelském rozhraní se snadnou obsluhou.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca@valencia">El monitor del sistema és un visualitzador de processos i un monitor del sistema amb una interfície atractiva i fàcil d'utilitzar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El monitor del sistema és un visualitzador de processos i un monitor del sistema amb una interfície atractiva i fàcil d'utilitzar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Sistem monitor je pregled procesa i sistem monitor sa atraktivnim, lako koristecim interfejsom.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bn_IN">সিস্টেম মনিটর হল একটি প্রক্রিয়া ভিউয়ার এবং সিস্টেম একটি অাকর্ষণীয়, সহজে ব্যবহার করা যায় এমন ইন্টারফেস দ্বারা নিয়ন্ত্রিত হয়।</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">„Наблюдение на системата“ е програма за наблюдаване на процесите и системата. Притежава привлекателен и лесен за работа интерфейс.</p>
    <p xml:lang="be">Сістэмны назіральнік - гэта праглядальнік працэсаў і назіральнік за сістэмай з прыемным, прыязным інтэрфейсам.</p>
    <p xml:lang="as">চিস্টেম মনিটৰ এটা আকৰ্ষণীয়, সহজে ব্যৱহাৰ কৰিব পৰা আন্তঃপৃষ্ঠৰ সৈতে এটা প্ৰক্ৰিয়া দৰ্শক আৰু চিস্টেম মনিটৰ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">مراقب النظام هو عارض عمليات و مراقب نظام له واجهة جذابة و سهلة الاستعمال.</p>
    <p xml:lang="an">O monitor d'o sistema ye un visor de procesos y un monitor d'o sistema con una interficie atractiva y facil d'usar.</p>
    <p>
      System Monitor can help you find out what applications are using the processor
      or the memory of your computer, can manage the running applications, force
      stop processes not responding, and change the state or priority of existing 
      processes.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">系統監控可以協助您找出哪個應用程式正在使用電腦上的處理器或記憶體，可以管理執行中的應用程式，強制沒有回應的程序停止，以及改變現有程序的狀態或優先等級。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_HK">系統監控可以協助你找出哪個應用程式正在使用電腦上的處理器或記憶體，可以管理執行中的應用程式，強制沒有回應的程序停止，以及改變現有程序的狀態或優先等級。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">系统监视器可帮您查看哪个程序正在使用计算机内存或处理器、管理正在运行的程序、强制停止无响应的进程和更改已有进程的状态或优先级。</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">Ứng dụng theo dõi hệ thống giúp bạn tìm ra ứng dụng nào đang tiêu dùng bộ vi xử lý hay bộ nhớ của máy tính, có thể quản lý các ứng dụng đang chạy, ép buộc dừng các tiến trình đang treo, và thay đổi trạng thái hay mức ưu tiên của một tiến trình sẵn có.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Системний монітор може допомогти з'ясувати, які програми використовують процесор і пам'ять вашого комп'ютера, може організовувати запущені програми, примусово зупиняти процеси і міняти стани або пріоритети наявних процесів.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Sistem Gözlemcisi hangi uygulamanın ne kadar bellek ve işlemci kullanıdığı konusunda yardımcı olabilir, Çalışmakta olan uygulamaları yönetebilir, yanıt vermeyen süreçleri zorla kapatabilir ve var olan süreçlerin durumunu veya önceliğini değiştirebilir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">เครื่องมือเฝ้าสังเกตระบบสามารถช่วยคุณหาโปรแกรมที่กำลังใช้งานตัวประมวลผลหรือหน่วยความจำของคอมพิวเตอร์ของคุณอยู่ สามารถจัดการโปรแกรมที่กำลังทำงานอยู่ บังคับหยุดโพรเซสที่ไม่ตอบสนอง และเปลี่ยนสถานะหรือลำดับความสำคัญของโพรเซสต่างๆ ที่มีอยู่ได้</p>
    <p xml:lang="tg">Назорати система намоиш медиҳад, ки кадом барномаҳо просессор ё ҳофизаи компютерро истифода мебаранд, барномаҳои иҷрошавандаро идора мекунад, равандҳои бепосухро маҷбуран қатъ мекунад ва вазъият ё аввалияти равандҳои мавҷудбударо тағйир медиҳад.</p>
    <p xml:lang="te">సిస్టమ్ పర్యవేక్షకి ఉపయోగించి మీ కంప్యూటర్ యొక్క మెమొరీ లేదా ప్రోసెస్‌ను ఏ అనువర్తనములు ఉపయోగిస్తున్నాయో కనుగొనవచ్చు, నడుస్తున్న అనువర్తనాలు నిర్వహించవచ్చు, స్పందిచని ప్రోసెస్‌లు బలవంతంగా ఆపివేయవచ్చు, మరియు మనుగడలోవున్న ప్రోసెస్ ప్రాముఖ్యతను స్థితిని మార్చవచ్చు.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ta">உங்கள் கணினியின் செயலியை அல்லது நினைவகத்தை எந்தெந்த பயன்பாடுகள் பயன்படுத்தி வருகின்றன என்பதைக் கண்டறியவும், இயங்கிக் கொண்டிருக்கும் பயன்பாடுகளை நிர்வகிக்கவும், பதிலளிக்காமல் நின்றுவிட்ட செயலாக்கங்களை பலவந்தமாக நிறுத்தவும் நடப்பு செயலாக்கங்களின் நிலை அல்லது முன்னுரிமையை மாற்றவும் கணினி கண்காணிப்புக் கருவி உதவுகிறது.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Systemövervakaren kan hjälpa dig att ta reda på vilka program som använder datorns processor eller minne, kan hantera körande program, tvångsavsluta processer som inte svarar, och ändra tillstånd eller prioritet för existerande processer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">Pratilac sistema vam može pomoći da otkrijete koji programi koriste procesor ili memoriju vašeg računara, može da upravlja pokrenutim programima, da prisili zaustavljanje procesa koji ne odgovaraju, i da izmeni stanje ili važnost postojećih procesa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Пратилац система вам може помоћи да откријете који програми користе процесор или меморију вашег рачунара, може да управља покренутим програмима, да присили заустављање процеса који не одговарају, и да измени стање или важност постојећих процеса.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Nadzornik sistema omogoča nadzor in iskanje programov in njihovo obremenitev procesorske moči in pomnilnika. Mogoče je tudi upravljati zagnane programe in jih po potrebi vsiljeno končati.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Monitor systému vám pomôže zistiť, ktoré aplikácie používajú procesor alebo pamäť vášho počítača. Taktiež vám uľahčí správu spustených aplikácií, vynútené ukončenie neodpovedajúcich procesov a zmenu stavu alebo priority existujúcich procesov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Системный монитор поможет определить, какие приложения используют процессор или память компьютера, может управлять запущенными приложениями, останавливать зависшие процессы и изменять состояние или приоритет выполняющихся процессов.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Monitor Sistem vă poate ajuta la găsirea aplicațiilor ce folosesc procesorul sau memoria calculatorului, poate administra aplicațiile ce rulează, forța oprirea proceselor care nu răspund și schimba starea sau prioritatea proceselor existente.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">O Monitor do sistema pode ajudá-lo a desvendar quais aplicativos estão usando o processador ou a memória do seu computador, pode gerenciar os aplicativos em execução, forçar processos que não estão respondendo a pararem e alterar o estado ou prioridade de processos existentes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Monitor de sistema pode ajuda-lo a descobrir quais as aplicações que estão a utilizar o processador ou a memória do seu computador, gerir as aplicações em execução, pode forçar a paragem de processos que não respondem e alterar o estado ou prioridade de processos existentes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Monitor systemu umożliwia wykrywanie, które programy używają procesora lub pamięci komputera, zarządzanie uruchomionymi programami, wymuszanie zatrzymania nieodpowiadających procesów i zmienianie stanu lub priorytetu istniejących procesów.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pa">ਸਿਸਟਮ ਨਿਗਰਾਨ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਉਹ ਐਪਲੀਕੇਸ਼ਨ ਲੱਭਣ ਲਈ ਮੱਦਦ ਕਰਦਾ ਹੈ, ਜੋ ਕਿ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਕੰਪਿਊਟਰ ਦੇ ਪਰੋਸੈਸ ਜਾਂ ਮੈਮੋਰੀ ਨੂੰ ਵਰਤਦੀਆਂ ਹਨ, ਚੱਲ ਰਹੇ ਐਪਲੀਕੇਸ਼ਨ ਦਾ ਸੰਚਾਲਨ ਕਰ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ, ਜੇ ਪਰੋਸੈਸ ਠੀਕ ਤਰ੍ਹਾਂ ਨਹੀਂ ਚੱਲਦਾ ਤਾਂ ਧੱਕੇ ਨਾਲ ਬੰਦ ਕਰ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ ਅਤੇ ਮੌਜੂਦਾ ਪਰੋਸੈਸ ਦੀ ਸਥਿਤੀ ਤੇ ਤਰਜੀਹ ਬਦਲ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Lo Monitor sistèma vos pòt ajudar a trobar quinas aplicacions utilizan lo processor o la memòria de vòstre ordenador, gerir las aplicacions que foncionan, forçar los processus que respondon pas a s'arrestar e cambiar l'estat o la prioritat de processus existents.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Met Systeemmonitor kunt u onderzoeken welke programma’s het geheugen of de processor van uw computer gebruiken, draaiende programma's beheren, vastgelopen processen afsluiten en de prioriteit van bestaande processen aanpassen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ne">प्रणाली मनिटरले तपाईंलाई कुन प्रोसेसर वा कम्प्युटरको मेमोरी प्रयोग गरिरहेको छ भन्ने पत्ता लगाउन मद्दत पुर्याउन सक्छ, चलिरहेको अनुप्रयोगहरू व्यवस्थित गर्न सक्छ, प्रतिक्रिया नदिएका प्रक्रियाहरू बल पूर्वक रोक्न सक्छ, र अवस्थित प्रक्रियाहरू को स्थिति वा प्राथमिकता परिवर्तन गर्न सक्छन्।</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Systemovervåking kan hjelpe deg med å finne ut hvilke programmer som bruker prosessor eller minne på din datamaskin, og kan håndtere kjørende programmer, stoppe prosesser som ikke svarer og endre tilstand eller prioritet for eksisterende prosesser.</p>
    <p xml:lang="mr">सिस्टम मॉनिटर तुम्हाला संणकावरील कोणते ॲप्लिकेशन्स प्रोसेसर किंवा मेमरिचा वापर करत आहे, ते शोधण्यास, कार्यरत ॲप्लिकेशन्स व्यवस्थापीत करणे, प्रतिसाद न देणाऱ्या प्रोसेसेना थांबवणे, आणि अस्तित्वातील प्रोसेसचे स्तर किंवा प्राधान्यता बदलवण्यास मदत करते.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ml">എതെല്ലാം ആപ്ലിക്കേഷനുകളാണ് സിപിയുവും മെമ്മറിയും ഉപയോഗിക്കുന്നതെന്ന് കണ്ടെത്താന്‍ സഹായിക്കുന്ന ആപ്ലിക്കേഷനാണ് സിസ്റ്റം മോണിറ്റര്‍. ഇത് പ്രവര്‍ത്തിക്കുന്ന ആപ്ലിക്കേഷനുകളെ കൈകാര്യംചെയ്യാന്‍ സഹായിക്കുന്നു, പ്രതികരിക്കാത്ത പ്രോസസുകളെ ബലമായി നിറുത്തുന്നു, നിലവിലുള്ള പ്രോസസുകളുടെ പരിഗണന മാറ്റുന്നു.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">Sistēmas pārraugs var jums palīdzēt atrast lietotnes, kas izmanto datora procesoru vai atmiņu; pārvaldīt palaistās lietotnes; piespiest apturēt procesus, kas vairs nereaģē; mainīt esošu procesu stāvokli vai prioritāti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Sistemos monitorius leidžia jums pamatyti, kurios programos naudoja jūsų kompiuterio procesorių ar atmintį, gali tvarkyti veikiančias programas, priverstinai stabdyti neatsakančius procesus ir keisti esamų procesų būseną bei prioritetą.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">시스템 정보 프로그램을 사용해 어떤 프로그램이 컴퓨터의 프로세스와 메모리를 사용하는지 알 수 있습니다. 또 실행 중인 프로그램을 관리하고, 응답이 없는 프로세스를 중단하고, 실행 중인 프로세스의 상태나 실행 우선 순위를 바꿀 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="kn">ವ್ಯವಸ್ಥೆಯ ಮೇಲ್ವಿಚಾರಕವು, ಯಾವ ಅನ್ವಯಗಳು ಸಂಸ್ಕಾರಕವನ್ನು ಅಥವ ನಿಮ್ಮ ಗಣಕದ ಮೆಮೊರಿಯನ್ನು ಬಳಸುತ್ತಿವೆ ಎಂಬುದನ್ನು ಪತ್ತೆ ಮಾಡಲು, ಚಲಾಯಿಸಲಾಗುತ್ತಿರುವ ಅನ್ವಯಗಳನ್ನು ನೋಡಿಕೊಳ್ಳಲು, ಪ್ರತಿಕ್ರಿಯಿಸದೆ ಇರುವ ಪ್ರಕ್ರಿಯೆಗಳನ್ನು ಒತ್ತಾಯದಿಂದ ನಿಲ್ಲಿಸಲು, ಮತ್ತು ಈಗಿರುವ ಪ್ರಕ್ರಿಯೆಗಳ ಸ್ಥಿತಿ ಅಥವ ಆದ್ಯತೆಯನ್ನು ಬದಲಾಯಿಸಲು ನೆರವಾಗುತ್ತದೆ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="km">កម្មវិធី​ត្រួតពិនិត្យ​ប្រព័ន្ធ​អាច​ជួយ​អ្នក​រកមើល​នូវ​កម្មវិធី​អ្វី​ខ្លះ​ដែល​ប្រព័ន្ធ​ដំណើរការ ឬ​អង្គ​ចងចាំ​​​កុំព្យូទ័រ​របស់​អ្នក​កំពុង​ប្រើ អាច​គ្រប់គ្រង​កម្មវិធី​កំពុង​ដំណើរការ បង្ខំ​បញ្ឈប់​ដំណើរការ​មិន​ឆ្លើយតប និង​ប្ដូរ​ស្ថានភាព ឬ​អាទិភាព​ដំណើរការ​ដែល​មាន​ស្រាប់។</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">Жүйелік бақылаушы компьютеріңіздің процессор мен жадын қандай қолданбалар қолданып тұрғанын анықтау, орындалып тұрған қолданбаларды басқару, жауап бермейтін үрдістерді мәжбүрлі аяқтау және бар үрдістердің қалып-күйін немесе приоритетін өзгертуге көмектесе алады.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">システムモニターを使えば、お使いのコンピューターのプロセッサーやメモリを使用しているアプリケーションを特定する、実行中のアプリケーションを管理する、応答しないプロセスを強制終了する、既存のプロセスの状態や優先度を変更する、などができます。</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">«Monitor di sistema» è in grado di mostrare quali applicazioni stanno utilizzato il processore o la memoria del computer; può gestire le applicazioni in esecuzione, terminare i processi bloccai e modificare la priorità dei process.</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">Kerfisvaktin getur hjálpað þér við að fylgjast með hvaða forrit eru að nota örgjörva eða minni tölvunnar, sýsla með forrit í keyrslu, þvinga ferli til að hætta ef þau svara ekki, og breyta stöðu og forgangi ferla í keyrslu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Monitor Sistem dapat membantu Anda mengetahui aplikasi yang sedang diolah oleh prosesor atau jumlah memori pada komputer Anda, sekaligus memanajemen aplikasi yang berjalan, menghentikan proses yang membeku, serta mengubah prioritas proses yang sedang berlangsung.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Rendszerfigyelővel meghatározhatja, mely alkalmazások használják a számítógép processzorát vagy memóriáját, felügyelheti a futó alkalmazásokat, kikényszerítheti a nem válaszoló folyamatokat, és módosíthatja a meglévő folyamatok állapotát vagy prioritását.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">Nadgledatelj sustava može vam pomoći u pronalaženju određene aplikacije koja vam koristi procesor ili memoriju računala, može upravljati pokrenutim aplikacijama, prisilno zaustaviti procese koji ne reagiraju i promijeniti stanje ili prioritet postojećih procesa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi"> System Monitor can help you find out what applications are using the processor or the memory of your computer, can manage the running applications, force stop processes not responding, and change the state or priority of existing processes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">צג המערכת יכול לעזור לך לגלות מה הם היישומים המנצלים את המעבד או הזיכרון של המחשב שלך, יכול לנהל ולהריץ יישומים, להכריח עצירת תהליכים שאינם מגיבים ושינוי מצב או עדיפות תהליכים קיימים.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">O monitor do sistema pode axudarlle a saber que aplicativos están usando o procesador ou a memoria do seu computador, pode xestionar os aplicativos en execución, forzar o peche de procesos que non respondan e cambiar o estado ou prioridade dos procesos existentes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gd">’S urrainn do Mhonatair an t-siostaim taic a thoirt dhut gus faighinn a-mach dè na h-aplacaidean a bhios a’ chleachdadh pròiseasar no cuimhne a’ choimpiutair agad, ’s urrainn dha na h-aplacaidean ’gan ruith a stiùireadh, toirt air pròiseasan nach freagair gun stad iad is staid no prìomhachas aig na pròiseasan a tha ann atharrachadh.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fur">“Monitor di sisteme” al è in grât di mostrâ cualis aplicazions a stan doprant il processôr o la memorie dal computer; al pues ministrâ lis aplicazions in esecuzion, terminâ i procès blocâts e modificâ la prioritât dai procès.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Le Moniteur système peut vous aider à trouver quelles applications utilisent le processeur ou la mémoire de votre ordinateur, gérer les applications qui fonctionnent, forcer les processus qui ne répondent pas à s’arrêter et changer l’état ou la priorité de processus existants.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Järjestelmän valvonnan avulla on helppo nähdä, mitkä sovellukset käyttävät koneen suoritintehoa ja muistia, hallita käynnissä olevia sovelluksia, lopettaa pakottaen jumiutuneet sovellukset ja vaihtaa prosessien prioriteettia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fa">پایشگر سیستم به شما این امکان را می‌دهد که متوجه شوید چه برنامه‌هایی از پردازشکر و یا حافظه شما استفاده می‌کنند، می‌توانید برنامه‌های درحال اجرا را مدیریت کنید، فراروندهایی که پاسخگو نیستند را مجبور به توقف کنید، و الویت یا وضعیت فراروندهای موجود را تغییر دهید.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Zer aplikaziok ordenagailuaren prozesadorea edo memoria darabilten aurkitzen lagunduko dizu sistemaren monitoreak. Exekuzioan dauden aplikazioak kudea ditzake, erantzuten ez duten prozesuak gelditzera derrigortu eta lanean ari diren prozesuen egoera edo lehentasuna alda dezake.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Süsteemijälgija aitab teada saada, mis rakendused kasutavad arvuti protsessori jõudlust või mälu, sellega saab hallata töötavaid rakendusi, jõuga sulgeda mittetoimivaid protsesse ja muuta olemasolevate protsesside olekut või olulisust.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Monitor del sistema le puede ayudar a identificar qué aplicaciones están usando el procesador o la memoria del equipo, puede gestionar las aplicaciones en ejecución, forzar la detención de procesos que no responden y cambiar la prioridad de los procesos existentes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Sistemmonitoro povas helpi al vi malkovri kiujn aplikaĵojn uzas la procesoron aŭ memoron de via komputilo, povas mastrumi la rulantajn aplikaĵojn, devige ĉesigi nerespondajn procezojn, kaj ŝanĝi la staton aŭ prioritaton de ekzistaj procezoj.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">System Monitor can help you find out what applications are using the processor or the memory of your computer, can manage the running applications, force stop processes not responding, and change the state or priority of existing processes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Η Παρακολούθηση συστήματος μπορεί να σας βοηθήσει να βρείτε ποιες εφαρμογές χρησιμοποιούν τον επεξεργαστή ή τη μνήμη του υπολογιστή σας, μπορεί να διαχειριστεί τις εκτελούμενες εφαρμογές, να εξαναγκάσει σε διακοπή τις διεργασίες που δεν ανταποκρίνονται και να αλλάξει την κατάσταση ή την προτεραιότητα των υπαρχουσών διεργασιών.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Die Systemüberwachung hilft Ihnen herauszufinden, welche Anwendungen den Prozessor oder den Arbeitsspeicher Ihres Rechners verwenden. Zusätzlich können Sie laufenden Anwendungen verwalten, indem Sie nicht mehr reagierende Prozesse abwürgen oder den Zustand und die Priorität von existierenden Prozessen bearbeiten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Systemovervågning kan hjælpe dig med, at finde ud af hvilke programmer der bruger computerens processor eller hukommelse, at håndtere kørende programmer, at tvinge processer som ikke svarer til at stoppe, samt ændre tilstand eller prioritet for eksisterende processer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Sledování systému vám může pomoci najít, která aplikace vám vytěžuje procesor nebo paměť ve vašem počítači, můžete v něm spravovat běžící aplikace, násilně ukončovat procesy, které nereagují, a měnit stav a prioritu stávajících procesů.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca@valencia">El monitor del sistema vos pot ajudar a descobrir quina aplicació està fent servir el processador o la memòria de l'ordinador, vos permet gestionar les aplicacions en execució, pot aturar processos que no responguin i canviar l'estat i la prioritat dels processos existents.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El monitor del sistema us pot ajudar a descobrir quina aplicació està fent servir el processador o la memòria de l'ordinador, us permet gestionar les aplicacions en execució, pot aturar processos que no responguin i canviar l'estat i la prioritat dels processos existents.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Sistem monitor vam mozi pomoći da pronađete aplikacije koje koriste procesor ili memoriju vaseg računara, može upravljati pokrenutim aplikacijama, nasilno prekinuti aplikacije koje ne reaguju, ili promijeniti stanje ili prioritet postojecih procesa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bn_IN">সিস্টেম মনিটর কোন অ্যাপ্লিকেশনগুলি অাপনার কম্পিউটারের প্রসেসর বা মেমরি ব্যবহার করছে তা বুঝতে, চলমান অ্যাপ্লিকেশনগুলি পরিচালনা করতে, সাড়া দিচ্ছে না এমন প্রক্রিয়াগুলিকে বলপ্রয়োগ করে বন্ধ করতে, এবং বিদ্যমান প্রক্রিয়াগুলির অবস্থা বা অগ্রাধিকার পরিবর্তন করতে সাহায্য করবে।</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">„Наблюдение на системата“ може да ви помогне да разберете кои програми използват процесора или паметта, може да управлявате работещите процеси, да ги спирате, както и да променяте състоянието или приоритета им.</p>
    <p xml:lang="be">Сістэмны назіральнік можа дапамагчы вызначыць, якія праграмы займаюць працэсар або памяць камп'ютара, дазваляе кіраваць запушчанымі праграмамі, прымусова спыняць працэсы, якія не адказваюць на запыты сістэмы, а таксама змяняць стан або прыярытэт наяўных працэсаў.</p>
    <p xml:lang="as">চিস্টেম মনিটৰে আপোনাক কোন এপ্লিকেচনসমূহে প্ৰচেছৰ অথবা কমপিউটাৰৰ মেমৰি ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি আছে সন্ধান কৰাত সহায় কৰে, চলি থকা এপ্লিকেচনসমূহ ব্যৱস্থাপনা কৰিব পাৰে, প্ৰতিক্ৰিয়া নকৰা প্ৰক্ৰিয়াসমূহ বলৱৎভাৱে বন্ধ কৰিব পাৰে, আৰু স্থায়ী প্ৰক্ৰিয়াসমূহৰ অৱস্থা অথবা প্ৰাথমিকতা পৰিবৰ্তন কৰিব পাৰে।</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">يمكن لمراقب النظام مساعدتك في اكتشاف التطبيقات التي تستعمل معالج الحاسوب أو ذاكرته، و يمكنه إدارة التطبيقات التي تعمل، و إيقاف العمليات التي لا تستجيب بالقوة، و حتى تغيير حالة أو أولوية العمليات الموجودة.</p>
    <p xml:lang="an">O monitor d'o sistema te puet aduyar a identificar qué aplicacions son usando lo procesador u a memoria de l'equipo, puet chestionar as aplicacions en execución, aforzar l'aturada de procesos que no responden y cambiar o estau u a prioridat d'os procesos existents.</p>
    <p>
      The resource graphs feature shows you a quick overview of what is going on with your
      computer displaying recent network, memory and processor usage.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">資源圖表功能顯示出您的電腦目前情況的快速概覽，包含目前網路、記憶體與處理器的使用量。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_HK">資源圖表功能顯示出你的電腦目前情況的快速概覽，包含目前網絡、記憶體與處理器的使用量。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">资源图表功能为您展示了计算机当前运行状态的快速预览，包括近期网络、内存和处理器使用情况。</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">Tính năng hiển thị tài nguyên bằng đồ thị giúp bạn nhanh chóng hiểu được những gì đang diễn với mạng, bộ nhớ và bộ vi xử lý trên máy tính của mình.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Графіки ресурсів показують швидкий огляд того, що відбувається на вашому комп'ютері, зокрема використання мережі, пам'яті, процесора.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Kaynak grafiği size ağın, belleğin ve işlemcinin kullanımı hakkında ve sisteminizde ne olup bittiğine dair hızlı bir izlenim sunar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">กราฟทรัพยากรจะช่วยแสดงให้คุณเห็นภาพรวมคร่าวๆ ของสิ่งที่เกิดขึ้นกับคอมพิวเตอร์ของคุณ โดยแสดงการใช้งานล่าสุดของเครือข่าย หน่วยความจำ และตัวประมวลผล</p>
    <p xml:lang="tg">Хусусияти диаграммаи сарчашма хулосаи равандҳои истифодаи шабака, ҳофиза ва просессори компютери шуморо намоиш медиҳад.</p>
    <p xml:lang="te">ఇటీవలి నెట్వర్క్, మెమొరీ మరియు ప్రోసెసర్ వాడుకను ప్రదర్శిస్తూ ఏమి జరుగుతోందో రిసోర్స్ గ్రాఫ్ విశేషణం చూపును.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ta">வளங்களின் வரைபடம் உங்களுக்கு சமீபத்திய பிணையம், நினைவகம் மற்றும் செயலி பயனீட்டளவைக் காண்பிக்கிறது, இதன் மூலம் நீங்கள் உங்கள் கணினியில் என்ன நடக்கிறது என்பதை சட்டென மேலோட்டமாகத் தெரிந்துகொள்ள முடியும்.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Resursdiagrammen kan ge dig en överblick över vad som händer med din dator genom att visa nätverks-, minnes- och processoranvändning för den senaste tiden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">Funkcija grafika resursa vam pokazuje brzi pregled dešavanja na vašem računaru prikazujući nedavno korišćenje mreže, memorije i procesora.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Функција графика ресурса вам показује брзи преглед дешавања на вашем рачунару приказујући недавно коришћење мреже, меморије и процесора.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Možnost diagramov virov omogoča hiter pregled dogajanja v sistemu s prikazom omrežne in procesorske rabe ter zasedenosti pomnilnika.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Grafy prostriedkov zobrazujú rýchly prehľad toho, čo sa deje s vaším počítačom (nedávne využitie siete, pamäte a procesora).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Функция отображения графика ресурсов предоставляет краткий обзор того, что происходит с компьютером, показывая использования сети, памяти и процессора.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Caracteristica graficele resurselor vă arată o vedere de ansamblu rapidă a ceea ce se petrece cu calculatorul afișând rețeaua recentă, memoria și utilizarea procesorului.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">A funcionalidade de gráficos de recursos mostra a você uma rápida visão geral do que está acontecendo com o seu computador, ao exibir o uso de rede, memória e de processador.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">A funcionalidade de gráficos de recursos mostra uma rápida visão geral do que está a acontecer com o seu computador, bem como a utilização recente da rede, memória e processador.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Wykresy wykorzystania sieci, pamięci i procesora dają szybki przegląd tego, co dzieje się w komputerze.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pa">ਸਰੋਤ ਗਰਾਫ ਫੀਚਰ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਸੰਖੇਪ ਝਲਕ ਵੇਖਾਉਂਦਾ ਹੈ ਕਿ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਕੰਪਿਊਟਰ ਉੱਤੇ ਤਾਜ਼ਾ ਨੈੱਟਵਰਕ, ਮੈਮੋਰੀ ਤੇ ਪਰੋਸੈਸਰ ਵਰਤੋਂ ਕਿਵੇਂ ਹੋ ਰਹੀ ਹੈ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Lo grafic de las ressorsas aficha una vista d'ensemble de çò que se passa sus vòstre ordenador en fasent veire l'utilizacion recenta de la ret, de la memòria e del processor.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">De grafische weergave van het gebruik van systeembronnen geeft u een snel overzicht van de status van uw computer door recent netwerk-, geheugen- en processorgebruik te tonen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ne">संसाधन ग्राफिक्स सुविधाले कम्प्युटर सङ्ग हालको सञ्जाल, मेमोरी र प्रोसेसर प्रयोगको छिटो सिंहावलोकन देखाउँछ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Ressursgrafene gir deg et raskt overblikk av hva som skjer på din datamaskin og viser nylig bruk av nettverk, minne og prosessor.</p>
    <p xml:lang="mr">स्रोत ग्राफ्स गुणविशेष पूर्वावलोकन दाखवते ज्यामुळे संगणकावरील अलिकडील नेटवर्क, मेमरि आणि प्रोसेसरचा वापर दाखविले जाते.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ml">റിസോഴ്സ്ഗ്രാഫ് എന്ന ഫീച്ചര്‍ കമ്പ്യൂട്ടറില്‍ ഇപ്പോള്‍ എന്തുനടക്കുന്നു എന്ന വിഹഗവീക്ഷണം നല്‍കുന്നു. അതിനായി സമീപകാലത്തെ ശൃംഖല, മെമ്മറി,പ്രോസസര്‍ ഉപയോഗം എന്നിവ പ്രദര്‍ശിപ്പിക്കുന്നു.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">Resursu grafiks dod ātru pārskatu pār datora resursiem — tīkla, atmiņas un procesora noslodze.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Išteklių grafikai parodo greitą apžvalgą, kas vysta jūsų kompiuteryje, pateikdami paskutinį tinklo, atminties ir procesoriaus naudojimą.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">자원 그래프 기능을 사용하면 컴퓨터에 무슨 일이 발생하고 있는지 빠르게 파악할 수 있습니다. 여기서 최근 네트워크, 메모리, 프로세서 사용량을 표시합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="kn">ಸಂಪನ್ಮೂಲದ ನಕ್ಷೆಗಳ ಸೌಲಭ್ಯವು ನಿಮ್ಮ ಗಣಕದಲ್ಲಿನ ಇತ್ತೀಚಿನ ಜಾಲಬಂಧ, ಮೆಮೊರಿ ಮತ್ತು ಸಂಸ್ಕಾರಕದ ಬಳಕೆಯ ಮಾಹಿತಿಯ ಜೊತೆಗೆ ನಿಮ್ಮ ಗಣಕದಲ್ಲಿ ಏನು ನಡೆಯುತ್ತಿದೆ ಎನ್ನುವುದನ್ನು ತೋರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="km">លក្ខណ​ពិសេស​ក្រាហ្វិក​ធនធាន​គឺ​បង្ហាញ​ពី​ទិដ្ឋភាព​ទូទៅ​​រហ័ស​នៃ​អ្វី​ដែល​កំពុង​ដំណើរការ​លើ​កុំព្យូទ័រ​របស់​អ្នក បង្ហាញ​ពី​ការ​ប្រើប្រាស់​បណ្ដាញ អង្គ​ចងចាំ និង​ប្រព័ន្ធ​ដំណើរការ​បច្ចុប្បន្ន។</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">Ресурстар графиктері мүмкіндігі сізге жүйеңізде не болып жатқанын жуырдағы желі, жады және процессор қолданылуын көрсету арқылы хабарлайды.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">リソースグラフは、最近のネットワークやメモリ、CPU の使用状況を表示して、お使いのコンピューターで何が起きているかをすばやく把握できます。</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Il grafico delle risorse consente di avere una panoramica sullo stato del sistema visualizzando l'utilizzo della rete, della memoria e del processore.</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">Línuritin gefa þér fljótlegt yfirlit um hvað er í gangi í tölvunni, þar birtist nýleg virkni netkerfis, minnis og örgjörvanotkun.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Fitur grafik sumber daya menampilkan ikhtisar apa yang sedang terjadi pada komputer Anda, antaranya penggunaan jaringan, memori, serta prosesor.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A hálózat-, memória- és processzorhasználatot megjelenítő erőforrás-grafikonokon gyorsan áttekintheti, hogy mi történik a számítógépén.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">Značajka grafikona resursa prikazuje vam brz pregled o trenutnom stanju vašeg računala prikazujući nedavno korištenje mreže, memorije i upotrebe procesa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">संसाधन आलेख फीचर दिखाता है कि आपके कंप्यूटर के साथ क्या होने जा रहा है जो हालिया संजाल स्मृति और प्रोसेसर प्रयोग दिखाता है.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">תכונת גרפי משאבים מציגה לך סקירה מהירה של מה שקורה עם המחשב שלך. מציג שימוש אחרון ברשת, בזיכרון ובמעבד שלך.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">As gráficas de recursos móstranlle unha vista rápida de que está pasando no seu computador como o  uso recente da rede, memoria e procesador.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gd">Seallaidh gleus grafaichean nan goireasan dhut foir-shealladh luath dhe na tha a’ tachairt air a’ choimpiutair agad, a’ sealltainn na chaidh a chleachdadh dhen lìonra, cuimhne is pròiseasar o chionn ghoirid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fur">Il grafic des risorsis al permet di vê une panoramiche sul stât dal sisteme, visualizant la utilizazion de rêt, de memorie e dal processôr.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Le graphique des ressources affiche une vue d’ensemble de ce qui se passe sur votre ordinateur en montrant l’utilisation récente du réseau, de la mémoire et du processeur.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Resurssikäyrät näyttävät yhteenvedon verkon, muistin ja suorittimen käytöstä.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fa">امکان نمایش نمودار منابع‌، یک مرور کلی از اتفاقاتی که در حال حاضر در رایانه شما در حال رخ دادن است را با نمایش میزان استفاده از شبکه، حافظه و پردازشگر، به شما نشان می‌دهد.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Baliabideen grafikoen eginbideak ordenagailuan zer gertatzen ari den buruzko ikuspegi orokor azkar bat erakutsiko dizu, sarearen, memoriaren eta prozesadorearen azken erabilpena bistaratuz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Ressursigraafikud annavad kiire ülevaate arvutiga toimuvast kuvades hiljutist võrgu-, mälu- ja protsessorikasutust.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">La característica de gráficos de recursos muestra una vista general rápida de qué está pasando en el equipo mostrando el uso reciente de la red, el procesador y la memoria.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">La risurca grafikaĵa funkcio montras al vi rapidan superrigardon de la stato de via komputilo, montrante freŝdatan retan, memoran, kaj procesoran uzadon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">The resource graphs feature shows you a quick overview of what is going on with your computer displaying recent network, memory and processor usage.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το γράφημα των πόρων σας εμφανίζει μια γρήγορη επισκόπηση για το τι συμβαίνει στο σύστημά σας, εμφανίζοντας την πρόσφατη χρήση του δικτύου, της μνήμης και του επεξεργαστή.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Das Ressourcendiagramm vermittelt Ihnen einen schnellen Überblick über Ihren Rechner. Angezeigt wird der Verlauf von Netzwerk-, Arbeitsspeicher- und Prozessorauslastung.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Graffunktionen for ressourcer giver dig nemt et hurtigt overblik over hvad der foregår på din computer ved at vise nylig netværks-, hukommelses- og processorforbrug.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Na grafech využití prostředů, které zobrazují vytížení sítě, paměti a procesoru, získáte rychlý přehled, co se ve vašem počítači děje.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca@valencia">Els gràfics dels recursos vos permeten tindre una visió general de què està passant a l'ordinador, es mostra l'ús recent de la xarxa, la memòria i els processadors.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Els gràfics dels recursos us permeten tenir una visió general de què està passant a l'ordinador, es mostra l'ús recent de la xarxa, la memòria i els processadors.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Grafikoni funkcije resursa prikazuju brzi pregled sta se desava sa vasim računarom, prikazujući nedavno korištenje mreže, memorije i procesora.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bn_IN">রিসোর্স গ্র্যাফ বৈশিষ্ট্য সাম্প্রতিক নেটওয়ার্ক, মেমরি এবং প্রসেসরের ব্যবহার সমেত অাপনার কম্পিউটারে কী ঘটে চলেছে তার এক সংক্ষিপ্ত পূর্বরূপ দেখায়।</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Разделът „Ресурси“ показва общ изглед какво се случва с вашия компютър. Показва информация за мрежата, паметта и натоварването на процесора.</p>
    <p xml:lang="be">Графік выкарыстання рэсурсаў паказвае актыўнасць сістэмы, ужыванне сеткі, памяці і працэсара.</p>
    <p xml:lang="as">সম্পদ ৰেখাচিত্ৰ বৈশিষ্ট্যয় আপোনাৰ কমপিউটাৰৰ সৈতে কি হৈ আছে তাৰ এটা দ্ৰুত অভাৰভিউ দিব পাৰে, শেহতীয়া নেটৱৰ্ক, মেমৰি আৰু প্ৰচেছৰৰ ব্যৱহাৰ প্ৰদৰ্শন কৰাকৈ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">تعرض ميزة رسوم الموارد البيانية نظرة عامة على ما يحدث في حاسوبك و تعرض الاستعمال الحديث للشبكة و الذاكرة و المعالج.</p>
    <p xml:lang="an">A caracteristica de graficos d'os recursos amuestra una anvista cheneral rapida de qué ye pasando en l'equipo amostrando l'uso recient d'o ret, o procesador y a memoria.</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot height="650" width="1176" type="default">
      <image>https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/SystemMonitor?action=AttachFile&amp;do=get&amp;target=Processes.png</image>
      <caption>Process list view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_TW">程序列表檢視</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_CN">进程列表视图</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="vi">Xem danh sách tiến trình</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Огляд переліку процесів</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Süreç listesi görünümü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="th">หน้ารายชื่อโพรเซส</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Processlistvy</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr@latin">Pregled spiska procesa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr">Преглед списка процеса</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Pogled opravil</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Zobrazenie zoznamu procesov</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Вид списка процессов</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Vizualizare listă de procese</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt_BR">Visão da lista de processos</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Vista de lista de processos</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Widok listy procesów</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pa">ਪਰੋਸੈੱਸ ਸੂਚੀ ਦੀ ਝਲਕ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="oc">Vista de la lista dels processus</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Processenweergave</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ne">प्रक्रिया सूची दृश्य</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nb">Prosesslistevisning</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ml">പ്രക്രിയ പട്ടിക കാഴ്ച</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Procesu saraksta skats</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Procesų sąrašo rodinys</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">프로세스 목록 보기</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="kk">Үрдістер тізімі көрінісі</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ja">プロセス一覧ビュー</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista dei processi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="is">Listasýn á ferla</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Tilikan daftar proses</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Folyamatlista nézet</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hr">Zbijen pogled procesa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">תצוגת רשימת תהליכים</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Vista da lista de procesos</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gd">Sealladh nam pròiseasan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fur">Viodude de liste dai procès</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Vue de la liste des processus</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Näkymä prosessiluetteloon</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fa">نمای فهرست پردازش</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Prozesuen zerrendaren ikuspegia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista de lista de procesos</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Proceza lista vido</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en_GB">Process list view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Προβολή λίστας διεργασιών</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Prozesslistenansicht</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Proceslistevisning</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Seznamové zobrazení procesů</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca@valencia">Vista llista de processos</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista llista de processos</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Процеси</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="be">Агляд спіса працэсаў</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">عرض قائمة العمليات</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot height="650" width="1176">
      <image>https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/SystemMonitor?action=AttachFile&amp;do=get&amp;target=Resources.png</image>
      <caption>Resources overview</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_TW">資源概覽</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_CN">资源概览</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="vi">Tổng quan về Tài nguyên</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Огляд ресурсів</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Kaynaklar genel görünümü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="th">ภาพรวมทรัพยากร</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Resursöverblick</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr@latin">Pregled izvorišta</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr">Преглед изворишта</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Pregled virov</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Prehľad prostriedkov</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Обзор ресурсов</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Prezentare generală a resurselor</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt_BR">Visão geral dos recursos</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Visão geral de recursos</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Przegląd zasobów</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pa">ਸਰੋਤਾਂ ਦਾ ਸਾਰ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="oc">Vista d'ensemble de las ressorsas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Systeembronnenweergave</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ne">स्रोत अवलोकन</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nb">Oversikt over ressurser</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ml">വിഭവങ്ങളുടെ വിഹഗവീക്ഷണം</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Resursu pārskats</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Išteklių rodinys</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">자원 개요</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="kk">Ресурстарды шолу көрінісі</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ja">リソースの概要</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Panoramica risorse</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="is">Yfirlit yfir tilföng</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Ringkasan sumber daya</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Erőforrások áttekintés</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hr">Pogled resursa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">סקירת משאבים</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Vista xeral dos recursos</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gd">Sealladh nan goireasan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fur">Panoramiche risorsis</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Vue d’ensemble des ressources</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Näkymä resursseihin</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fa">نمای‌کلی منابع</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Baliabideen ikuspegia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista general de recursos</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Risurca superrigardo</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en_GB">Resources overview</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Επισκόπηση πόρων</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Ressourcenübersicht</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Ressourceoversigt</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Přehled prostředků</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca@valencia">Visió general dels recursos</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Visió general dels recursos</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Ресурси</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="be">Агляд рэсурсаў</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">نظرة عامة للموارد</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot height="650" width="1176">
      <image>https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/SystemMonitor?action=AttachFile&amp;do=get&amp;target=Disks.png</image>
      <caption>File Systems view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_TW">檔案系統檢視</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_CN">文件系统视图</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="vi">Xem Hệ thống tập tin</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Огляд файлової системи</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Dosya Sistemleri görünümü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="th">มุมมองระบบแฟ้ม</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Filsystemsvy</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr@latin">Pregled sistema datoteka</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr">Преглед система датотека</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Pogled sistemskih datotek</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Zobrazenie súborových systémov</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Обзор файловых систем</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Vizualizare sisteme de fișiere</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt_BR">Visão do sistemas de arquivos</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Visão de sistema de ficheiros</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Widok systemów plików</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pa">ਫਾਇਲ ਸਿਸਟਮਾਂ ਦੀ ਝਲਕ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="oc">Vista dels sistèmas de fichièrs</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Bestandssysteemoverzicht</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ne">फाइल प्रणाली दृश्य</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nb">Filsystemvisning</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ml">ഫയല്‍ സിസ്റ്റങ്ങള്‍ കാണുക</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Datņu sistēmu skats</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Failų sistemos rodinys</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">파일 시스템 보기</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="kk">Файлдық жүйелер көрінісі</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ja">ファイルシステムビュー</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista file system</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="is">Sýn á skráakerfi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Tilikan Sistem Berkas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Fájlrendszerek nézet</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hr">Pogled datotečnih sustava</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">תצוגת מערכת קבצים</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Vista dos sistemas de ficheiros</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gd">Sealladh nan siostaman fhaidhlichean</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fur">Viodude file system</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Vue des systèmes de fichiers</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Näkymä tiedostojärjestelmiin</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fa">نمای سیستم پرونده‌ها</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Fitxategi-sistemen ikuspegia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista de los sistemas de archivos</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Dosiersistema vido</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en_GB">File Systems view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Προβολή συστημάτων αρχείων</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Dateisystemansicht</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Filsystemsvisning</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Zobrazení souborových systémů</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca@valencia">Vista dels sistemes de fitxers</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista dels sistemes de fitxers</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Файлови системи</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="be">Агляд файлавых сістэм</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">عرض أنظمة الملفات</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <update_contact>robert.roth.off_at_gmail.com</update_contact>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <compulsory_for_desktop>GNOME</compulsory_for_desktop>
  <translation type="gettext">gnome-system-monitor</translation>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0</project_license>
  <developer_name>The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/gnome-system-monitor/issues</url>
  <!--GNOME Projects usually have no per-app donation page-->
  <url type="donation">http://www.gnome.org/friends/</url>
  <url type="help">https://help.gnome.org/users/gnome-system-monitor/stable/</url>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/SystemMonitor</url>
  <url type="translate">https://l10n.gnome.org/module/gnome-system-monitor/</url>
</component>
