<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>nm-connection-editor.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>NetworkManager</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">NetworkManager</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">NetworkManager</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Netværkshåndtering</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">NetworkManager</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Gestor de la red</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">NetworkManager</name>
  <name xml:lang="gd">Manaidsear lìonraidh</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">NetworkManager</name>
  <name xml:lang="hr">Mrežni upravitelj</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Hálózatkezelő</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">NetworkManager</name>
  <name xml:lang="is">NetworkManager netstýring</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">NetworkManager</name>
  <name xml:lang="ja">NetworkManager</name>
  <name xml:lang="kk">NetworkManager</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">NetworkManager</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Netwerkbeheer</name>
  <name xml:lang="oc">NetworkManager</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਨੈੱਟਵਰਕ-ਮੈਨੇਜਰ</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">NetworkManager</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Gestor de rede</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">NetworkManager</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Administrator de rețea</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">NetworkManager</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">NetworkManager</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Управник мреже</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr@latin">Upravnik mreže</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Nätverkshanteraren</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Ağ Yöneticisi</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_CN">网络管理器</name>
  <summary>NetworkManager connection editor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Editor de connexions del NetworkManager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Editor připojení NetworkManager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Netværkshåndtering — redigering af forbindelse</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Netzwerkverwaltung-Verbindungseditor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Editor de conexiones Network Manager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gd">Deasaiche ceanglaichean Manaidsear lìonraidh</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Editor de conexións de NetworkManager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hr">Mrežni upravitelj - uređivač povezivanja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Hálózatkezelő kapcsolatszerkesztő</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Penyunting koneksi NetworkManager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Editor connessione NetworkManager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">NetworkManager 接続エディター</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="kk">NetworkManager байланыстар түзеткіші</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">NetworkManager ryšio redaktorius</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Netwerkbeheer verbindingseditor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pa">ਨੈੱਟਵਰਕ-ਮੈਨੇਜਰ ਕਨੈਕਸ਼ਨ ਐਡੀਟਰ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Edytor połączeń usługi NetworkManager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Editor de conexão NetworkManager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Editorul de conexiuni „Administrator de rețea”</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Редактор подключений NetworkManager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Editor pripojení správcu siete NetworkManager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Уређивач веза управника мреже</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr@latin">Uređivač veza upravnika mreže</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Nätverkshanteraren (anslutningsredigerare)</summary>

  <description>
    <p>NetworkManager is a system service for managing and configuring your network connections and devices.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El NetworkManager és un servei de sistema per gestionar i configurar les vostres connexions de xarxa i els vostres dispositius.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">NetworkManager je systémová služba pro správu a nastavení vašich síťových připojení a zařízení.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Netværkshåndtering er en systemtjeneste til håndtering og konfigurering af dine netværksforbindelser og -enheder.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">NetworkManager ist ein Systemdienst zur Verwaltung und Einrichtung Ihrer Netzwerkverbindungen und -geräte.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">NetworkManager es un demonio del sistema para gestionar y configurar sus conexiones y sus dispositivos de red.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gd">'S e seirbheis an t-siostaim a th' ann am Manaidsear lìonraidh gus na ceanglaichean is uidheaman lìonraidh agad a stiùireadh 's a rèiteachadh.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">NetworkManager é un servizo do sistema para xestionar e configurar os dispositivos e conexións de rede.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">Mrežni upravitelj je usluga sustava za upravljanje i podešavanje vaših mrežnih povezivanja i uređaja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Hálózatkezelő egy rendszerszolgáltatás hálózati kapcsolatok és eszközök kezelésére és beállítására.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">NetworkManager adalah sebuah layanan sistem untuk mengelola dan menata perangkat dan koneksi jaringan Anda.</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">NetworkManager er kerfisþjónusta sem gerir kleift að sýsla með og stilla nettengingar og nettæki.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">NetworkManager è un servizio di sistema per gestire e configurare connessioni e dispositivi di rete.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">NetworkManager は、ネットワーク接続およびデバイスを管理、設定するためのシステムサービスです。</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">NetworkManager - бұл жүйелік байланыстарды және құрылғыларды басқару және баптауға арналған жүйелік қызмет.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">NetworkManager yra sisteminė tarnyba tinklo ryšių bei įrenginių valdymui bei konfigūravimui.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Netwerkbeheer is een systeemdienst voor het beheren en configureren van uw netwerkverbindingen en apparaten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pa">ਨੈੱਟਵਰਕ-ਮੈਨੇਜਰ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਨੈੱਟਵਰਕ ਕਨੈਕਸ਼ਨ ਅਤੇ ਜੰਤਰ ਦੇ ਪਰਬੰਧ ਅਤੇ ਸੰਰਚਨਾ ਲਈ ਸਿਸਟਮ ਸੇਵਾ ਹੈ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">NetworkManager jest usługą systemową do zarządzania i konfigurowania połączeń i urządzeń sieciowych.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Gestor de redes é um serviço do sistema para gerir e configurar os seus dispositivos e ligações de rede.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">NetworkManager é um serviço de sistema para gerenciamento e configuração de seus dispositivos e conexões de rede.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Administrator de rețea este un serviciu de sistem pentru gestionarea și configurarea conexiunilor de rețea și dispozitivelor.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">NetworkManager — системная служба для управления и настройки сетевых подключений и устройств.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">NetworkManager je systémová služba na správu a nastavenie vašich sieťových pripojení a zariadení.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Управник мреже је системска услуга за управљање и подешавање мрежних веза и уређаја.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">Upravnik mreže je sistemska usluga za upravljanje i podešavanje mrežnih veza i uređaja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Nätverkshanteraren är en systemtjänst för att hantera och konfigurera dina nätverksanslutningar och nätverksenheter.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Ağ Yöneticisi, ağ bağlantılarınızı ve cihazlarınızı yönetmek ve yapılandırmak için bir sistem hizmetidir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">NetworkManager 是管理和配置网络连接和设备的系统服务。</p>
    <p>The nm-connection-editor program works with NetworkManager to create and edit existing connection profiles for NetworkManager.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El programa nm-connection-editor funciona amb el NetworkManager per crear i editar perfils existents de connexions per al NetworkManager.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Program nm-connection-editor spolupracuje se službou NetworkManager při vytváření a změnách stávajících profilů připojení pro NetworkManager.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Programmet nm-connection-editor arbejder sammen med Netværkshåndtering om at oprette og redigere eksisterende forbindelsesprofiler til Netværkshåndtering.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">nm-connection-editor arbeitet gemeinsam mit NetworkManager zum Anlegen und Bearbeiten von vorhandenen Verbindungsprofilen für NetworkManager.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">El programa nm-connection-editor funciona con NetworkManager para crear y editar perfiles de NetworkManager.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gd">Obraichidh am prògram nm-connection-editor le Manaidsear lìonraidh gus pròifilean ceanglaidh a chruthachadh 's a dheasachadh airson Manaidsear lìonraidh.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">O programa nm-connection-editor traballa co NetworkManager para crear e editar os perfís das conexións existentes no NetworkManager.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">nm-connection-editor program radi s Mrežnim upraviteljem kako bi stvorio i uredio postojeće profile povezivanja Mrežnog upravitelja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Hálózati kapcsolatok program használható kapcsolati profilok létrehozására a Hálózatkezelőhöz, és a meglévők kezelésére.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Program nm-connection-editor bekerja dengan NetworkManager untuk membuat dan menyunting profil koneksi yang ada untuk NetworkManager.</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">Forritið nm-connection-editor virkar með NetworkManager við að búa til ný tengisnið og breyta þeim sem þegar eru fyrir hendi í NetworkManager.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Il programma nm-connection-editor funziona con NetworkManager per creare e modificare profili di connessioni per NetworkManager.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">nm-connection-editor プログラムは、NetworkManager と連携して NetworkManager 用の接続プロファイルを作成し、また既存の接続プロファイルを編集します。</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">nm-connection-editor бағдарламасы NetworkManager-мен бірге NetworkManager үшін байланыс профильдерін жасауға және түзетуге жұмыс істейді.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">nm-connection-editor programa dirba su NetworkManager ryšių profilių kūrimui bei redagavimui.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Het programma nm-connection-editor werkt met Netwerkbeheer om bestaande verbindingsprofielen voor Netwerkbeheer aan te maken en te bewerken.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Program nm-connection-editor umożliwia tworzenie i modyfikowanie istniejących profilów połączeń za pomocą usługi NetworkManager.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O programa nm-connection-editor trabalha com o Gestor de redes para criar e editar perfis de ligação existentes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">O programa nm-connection-editor funciona com NetworkManager para criar e editar perfis de conexão existentes para NetworkManager.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Programul nm-connection-editor funcționează cu Administrator de rețea pentru a creea și edita profile de conexiune pentru Administrator de rețea.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Программа nm-connection-editor работает с NetworkManager для создания и редактирования существующих профилей подключений для NetworkManager.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Program nm-connection-editor spolupracuje so správcom siete NetworkManager na vytváranie a úpravu sieťových profilov pre NetworkManager.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Програм ум-уређивач-веза ради са Управником мреже да би направио и уредио постојеће профиле везе за Управника мреже.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">Program um-uređivač-veza radi sa Upravnikom mreže da bi napravio i uredio postojeće profile veze za Upravnika mreže.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Programmet nm-connection-editor arbetar med Nätverkshanteraren för att skapa och redigera befintliga profiler för Nätverkshanteraren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">nm-connection-editor programı, Ağ Yöneticisi için bağlantı profilleri oluşturmak ve mevcut olanları düzenlemek için Ağ Yöneticisi ile birlikte çalışır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">nm-connection-editor 程序为网络管理器创建或编辑现有的连接配置文件。</p>
  </description>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image width="772" height="548">https://git.gnome.org/browse/network-manager-applet/plain/nm-connection-editor.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Projects/NetworkManager</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugzilla.gnome.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=NetworkManager</url>
  <update_contact>networkmanager-maint@gnome.bugs</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">nm-applet</translation>
  <developer_name>The NetworkManager Developers</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca">Els desenvolupadors del NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="cs">Vývojáři aplikace NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="da">Udviklerne af Netværkshåndtering</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="de">Die NetworkManager-Entwickler</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="es">Los desarrolladores de NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="gd">Luchd-leasachaidh na h-aplaid Manaidsear lìonraidh</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="gl">Os desenvolvedores de NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="hr">Razvijatelji mrežnog upravitelja</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="hu">A Hálózatkezelő fejlesztői</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="id">Para Pengembang NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="it">Gli sviluppatori di NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ja">NetworkManager 開発者</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="kk">NetworkManager жасағандар</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="lt">NetworkManager kūrėjai</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nl">De Netwerkbeheer-ontwikkelaars</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pa">ਨੈੱਟਵਰਕ-ਮੈਨੇਜਰ ਡਿਵੈਲਪਰ</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pl">Programiści projektu NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt_BR">Os desenvolvedores do NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ro">Dezvoltatorii Administrator de rețea</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ru">Разработчики NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sk">Vývojári správcu siete NetworkManager</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sr">Програмери управника мреже</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sr@latin">Programeri upravnika mreže</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sv">Utvecklarna av Nätverkshanteraren</developer_name>
</component>