<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2013-2016 Richard Hughes <richard@hughsie.com> -->
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.gnome.Software.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>GNOME Software</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_TW">GNOME 軟體</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_CN">GNOME 软件</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">GNOME Yazılımlar</name>
  <name xml:lang="th">"ซอฟต์แวร์" ของ GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">GNOME Programvara</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr@latin">Gnomovi programi</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Гномови програми</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Programska oprema GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Softvér prostredia GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Центр приложений GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Aplicații GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">GNOME Software</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Aplicações GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Menedżer oprogramowania GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਗਨੋਮ ਸਾਫਟਵੇਅਰ</name>
  <name xml:lang="oc">Logicials de GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Gnome Software</name>
  <name xml:lang="ne">जिनोम सफ्टवेयर</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">GNOME Programvare</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">GNOME programinė įranga</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">GNOME programmatūra</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">그놈 소프트웨어</name>
  <name xml:lang="kk">GNOME Software</name>
  <name xml:lang="ja">GNOME ソフトウェア</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">GNOME Software</name>
  <name xml:lang="is">GNOME hugbúnaður</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">GNOME Perangkat Lunak</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">GNOME Szoftverek</name>
  <name xml:lang="hr">GNOME softver</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">GNOME Software</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">GNOME Software</name>
  <name xml:lang="gd">Bathar-bog GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="ga">Bogearraí GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="fur">Software di GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Logiciels de GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Ohjelmistot</name>
  <name xml:lang="fa">برنامه‌های گنوم</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">GNOMEren softwarea</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Software de GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">GNOME-Programaro</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_GB">GNOME Software</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Λογισμικό GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">GNOME Software</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">GNOME Software</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Software GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca@valencia">Programari del GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Programari del GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">Gnomovi programi</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Управление на програмите</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">برمجيّات جنوم</name>
  <name xml:lang="af">GNOME Sagteware</name>
  <summary>Application manager for GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">為 GNOME 設計的應用程式管理員</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_HK">為 GNOME 設計的應用程式管理員</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">GNOME 应用程序管理器</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">GNOME için uygulama yöneticisi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="th">เครื่องมือจัดการโปรแกรมสำหรับ GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="te">గ్నోమ్ కోసం అనువర్తన నిర్వాహకం</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Programhanterare för GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr@latin">Gnomov upravnik programa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Гномов управник програма</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Upravljalnik programov za GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Správca aplikácií prostredia GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Менеджер приложений для GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Administrator de aplicații pentru GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Gerenciador de aplicativos para o GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Gestor de aplicações para o GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Menedżer programów dla środowiska GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pa">ਗਨੋਮ ਲਈ ਐਪਲੀਕੇਸ਼ਨ ਮੈਨੇਜਰ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="oc">Gestionari d'aplicacions per GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Toepassingsbeheer voor Gnome</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ne">जिनोमको लागि  अनुप्रयोग प्रबन्धक</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nb">Programhåndtering for GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">GNOME programų tvarkytuvė</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">GNOME lietotņu pārvaldnieks</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">그놈용 프로그램 관리자</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="km">កម្មវិធី​គ្រប់គ្រង​កម្មវិធី​សម្រាប់ GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="kk">GNOME үшін қолданбалар басқарушысы</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">GNOME 用アプリケーションマネージャー</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Gestore applicazioni per GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Manajer aplikasi bagi GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Alkalmazáskezelő a GNOME-hoz</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hr">Upravitelj aplikacijama za GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">מנהל יישומים עבור GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Xestor de aplicativos para GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gd">Manaidsear nan aplacaid airson GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fur">Gjestôr di aplicazions par GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Gestionnaire d’applications pour GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Sovellushallinta Gnomelle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fa">مدیر برنامه‌ها برای گنوم</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">GNOMEren aplikazio-kudeatzailea</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Gestor de aplicaciones para GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Aplikaĵo-administrilo por GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en_GB">Application manager for GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Διαχειριστής εφαρμογών για το GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Anwendungsverwaltung für GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Programhåndtering til GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Správa aplikací pro GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca@valencia">Gestor d'aplicacions per al GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Gestor d'aplicacions per al GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bs">GNOME aplikacijski menadžer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Програма за управление на програмите в GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="as">GNOME ৰ বাবে এপ্লিকেচন ব্যৱস্থাপক</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">مدير تطبيقات لجنوم</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="af">Programbestuurder vir GNOME</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Software allows you to find and install new applications and system
      extensions and remove existing installed applications.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">《軟體》讓您可以找尋、安裝新程式與系統擴充套件，以及移除所安裝的應用程式。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_HK">《軟件》讓你可以找尋、安裝新程式與系統擴充套件，以及移除所安裝的應用程式。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">“软件”允许您查找并安装新的应用程序和系统扩展，移除已安装的应用程序。</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Yazılımlar uygulaması, yeni uygulamalar ve sistem uzantılarını bulup kurmanıza ve halihazırda kurulu olan uygulamaları kaldırmanıza olanak tanır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">"ซอฟต์แวร์" ช่วยคุณหาและติดตั้งโปรแกรมและส่วนขยายของระบบเพิ่มเติม และถอดถอนโปรแกรมที่ติดตั้งแล้ว</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Programvara gör det möjligt att hitta och installera nya program och systemkomponenter, samt att ta bort befintligt installerade program.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">Programi vam dozvoljavaju da pronađete i instalirate nove programe i proširenja sistema i da uklonite postojeće instalirane programe.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Програми вам дозвољавају да пронађете и инсталирате нове програме и проширења система и да уклоните постојеће инсталиране програме.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Program omogoča iskanje, nameščanje in odstranjevanje novih programov in sistemskih razširitev.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Aplikácia Softvér vám umožňuje nájsť a nainštalovať nové aplikácie a systémové rozšírenia a odstrániť existujúce nainštalované aplikácie.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Менеджер приложений позволяет находить и устанавливать новые приложения и системные расширения, а также удалять уже установленные приложения.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Aplicații vă permite să gasiți și să instalați aplicații noi și extensii de sistem sau să eliminați aplicații deja instalate.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">O aplicativo Programas permite que você encontre e instale novos aplicativos e extensões do sistema, além de remover aplicativos já instalados.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">A aplicação Aplicações permite encontrar e instalar novas aplicações e extensões do sistema, além de remover aplicações já instaladas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Menedżer oprogramowania umożliwia wyszukiwanie i instalowanie nowych programów i rozszerzeń systemu oraz usuwanie już zainstalowanych programów.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pa">ਸਾਫਟਵੇਅਰ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਨਵੇਂ ਐਪਲੀਕੇਸ਼ਨ ਤੇ ਸਿਸਟਮ ਇਕਸਟੈਂਸ਼ਨ ਲੱਭਣ ਤੇ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰਨ ਅਤੇ ਮੌਜੂਦਾ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਹੋਈਆਂ ਐਪਲੀਕੇਸ਼ਨ ਹਟਾਉਣ ਲਈ ਸਹਾਇਕ ਹੈ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Logicials servís a recercar e installar de novèlas aplicacions e extensions del sistèma, e tanben a suprimir las que son installadas sus vòstre ordenador.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Met Gnome Software kunt u nieuwe toepassingen en systeemuitbreidingen vinden en installeren, en bestaande geïnstalleerde toepassingen verwijderen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Programvare lar deg finne og installere nye programmer og systemutvidelser samt fjerne eksisterende installerte programmer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Programinė įranga leidžia jums rasti ir įdiegti naujos programas bei sistemos plėtinius, taip pat pašalinti įdiegtas programas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">“Programmatūra” jums ļauj atrast un instalēt jaunas lietotnes un sistēmas paplašinājumus, kā arī izņemt jau instalētās lietotnes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">소프트웨어에서 새 프로그램과 시스템 확장을 찾아 설치할 수 있고, 기존에 설치한 프로그램을 제거할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="km">កម្មវិធីអនុញ្ញាត​ឲ្យ​អ្នក​រក និង​ដំឡើង​កម្មវិធីថ្មីៗ​ ព្រមទាំង​ផ្នែក​បន្ថែម​ប្រព័ន្ធ​ និង​លុប​កម្មវិធី​ដែល​បានឡើង​មាន​ស្រាប់​ចេញ។</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">Software қолданбасы сізге жаңа қолданбалар мен жүйелік кеңейтулерді тауып, орнатуды және орнатылған қолданбаларды өшіруді мүмкін қылады.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">GNOME ソフトウェアでは、新しいアプリケーションやシステム拡張の検索、インストールができます。また、インストール済みアプリケーションの削除も可能です。</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Software consente di trovare e installare nuove applicazioni, estensioni di sistema e rimuovere applicazioni già esistenti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Perangkat Lunak memungkinkan Anda menemukan dan memasang aplikasi dan ekstensi sistem baru dan menghapus aplikasi yang telah dipasang.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Szoftverek lehetővé teszi új alkalmazások és rendszerkiterjesztések keresését, telepítését, valamint a meglévő telepített alkalmazások eltávolítását.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">Softver vam omogućuje pretraživanje i instalaciju novih aplikacija proširenja sustava i uklanjanje postojećih instaliranih aplikacija.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">תכנה מאפשר לך למצוא ולהתקין יישומים חדשים והרחבות מערכת ולהסיר יישומים מותקנים קיימים.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Software permítelle atopar e instalar novos aplicativos e extensións do sistema e eliminar aplicativos instalados actualmente.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gd">Leigidh Bathar-bog leat aplacaidean is leudachain an t-siostaim ùra a lorg ’s a stàladh agus aplacaidean a chaidh a stàladh a thoirt air falbh.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fur">Software al permet di cjatâ e instalâ gnovis aplicazions e estensions di sisteme e gjavâ aplicazions esistentis.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Logiciels sert à rechercher et installer de nouvelles applications et extensions du système, ainsi qu’à supprimer celles qui sont installées sur votre ordinateur.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Ohjelmistot mahdollistaa uusien sovellusten löytämisen ja asennuksen sekä nykyisten sovellusten poistamisen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fa">«برنامه‌ها» به شما امکان نصب برنامه‌های جدید، افزونه‌های سیستم و حذف نرم‌افزارهای نصب شده را می‌دهد.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">'Softwarea' aplikazioak aplikazio berriak eta sistemaren hedapenak bilatzea eta instalatzea, edo eta instalatutako aplikazioak kentzea, baimentzen dizu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Software le permite buscar e instalar aplicaciones nuevas y extensiones del sistema y quitar aplicaciones instaladas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">Software allows you to find and install new applications and system extensions and remove existing installed applications.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Η εφαρμογή Λογισμικό σας επιτρέπει να βρείτε και να εγκαταστήσετε νέες εφαρμογές και επεκτάσεις συστήματος και να αφαιρέσετε υπάρχουσες εγκατεστημένες εφαρμογές.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Software ermöglicht es Ihnen, neue Anwendungen und Systemerweiterungen zu finden und zu installieren sowie bereits installierte Anwendungen zu entfernen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Software lader dig finde og installere nye programmer og systemudvidelser, samt fjerne allerede installerede programmer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Aplikace Software umožňuje vyhledávat a instalovat aplikace a systémová rozšíření a odebírat stávající nainstalované aplikace.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca@valencia">El Programari vos permet buscar i instal·lar aplicacions noves i extensions del sistema així com eliminar aplicacions ja instal·lades.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Programari us permet cercar i instal·lar aplicacions noves i extensions del sistema així com eliminar aplicacions ja instal·lades.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Programi vam omogućavaju da nađete i instalirate nove aplikacije i sistemska proširenja i uklanjanje postojećih instaliranih aplikacija.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">С тази програма можете да търсите и инсталирате нови приложения и системни разширения, както и да премахвате вече инсталираните приложения.</p>
    <p xml:lang="as">চফ্টৱেৰে আপোনাক নতুন এপ্লিকেচনসমূহ আৰু চিস্টেম স্প্ৰসাৰনসমূহ সন্ধান কৰি ইনস্টল কৰাৰ আৰু স্থায়ী ইনস্টল্ড এপ্লিকেচনসমূহ আতৰোৱাৰ সুবিধা দিয়ে।</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">يسمح لك «برمجيّات» بالبحث عن تطبيقات جديدة وامتدادات للنّظام وإزالة التّطبيقات المثبّتة.</p>
    <p xml:lang="af">Sagteware laat mens nuwe programme en uitbreidings vind en installeer en kan ook reeds geïnstalleerde programme verwyder.</p>
    <p>
      GNOME Software showcases featured and popular applications with useful
      descriptions and multiple screenshots per application.
      Applications can be found either through browsing the list of categories
      or by searching.
      It also allows you to update your system using an offline update.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">GNOME《軟體》陳列各種具有特色，以及廣受歡迎的應用程式，並附上有用的描述與多張螢幕擷圖。除了瀏覽類別清單之外，您還可以透過搜尋的方式來找出想要的應用程式。此外，它也可讓您採用離線更新的方式更新系統。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_HK">GNOME Software 陳列各種具有特色，以及廣受歡迎的應用程式，並附上有用的描述與多張螢幕擷圖。除了瀏覽類別清單之外，你還可以透過搜尋的方式來找出想要的應用程式。此外，它也可讓你採用離線更新的方式更新系統。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">GNOME 软件 向您展示特色和流行的应用程序，并提供每个应用程序的描述、截图等有用信息。您可以通过浏览分类列表或搜索来找到应用程序。您还可以用它离线更新您的系统。</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">GNOME Yazılımlar; seçkin ve popüler uygulamaları, her uygulama için kullanışlı bir açıklama ve çoklu ekran görüntüleri ile birlikte beğeninize sunar. Uygulamalar, kategori listesinde gezinerek ya da arama yoluyla bulunabilir. Ayrıca çevrim dışı bir güncellemeyi kullanarak sisteminizi güncellemenize olanak tanır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">โปรแกรม "ซอฟต์แวร์" ของ GNOME จัดแสดงโปรแกรมที่เด่นและยอดนิยม พร้อมคำบรรยายที่เป็นประโยชน์และภาพหน้าจอหลายภาพต่อโปรแกรม คุณสามารถหาโปรแกรมผ่านการท่องดูตามหมวดหมู่หรือด้วยการค้นหาก็ได้ นอกจากนี้ ยังให้คุณปรับรุ่นระบบของคุณโดยใช้การปรับรุ่นแบบออฟไลน์ได้</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">GNOME Programvara förevisar föreslagna och populära program med användbara beskrivningar och ett flertal skärmbilder per program. Program kan antingen hittas genom att bläddra igenom kategorilistan eller genom att söka. Det gör det även möjligt att uppdatera systemet genom ett frånkopplat uppdateringsförfarande.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">Gnomovi programi prikazuju izdvojene i popularne programe sa korisnim opisima i nekoliko snimaka ekrana po programu. Programi mogu biti pronađeni pregledanjem spiska kategorija ili pretraživanjem. Takođe vam omogućava održavanje ažurnog sistema korišćenjem tehnologije vanmrežnih ažuriranja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Гномови програми приказују издвојене и популарне програме са корисним описима и неколико снимака екрана по програму. Програми могу бити пронађени прегледањем списка категорија или претраживањем. Такође вам омогућава одржавање ажурног система коришћењем технологије ванмрежних ажурирања.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Program za nameščanje programske opreme namizja GNOME omogoča ogled in iskanje paketov preko kratkih opisov, zaslonskih posnetkov vmesnika in drugih možnosti. Pakete je mogoče iskati tudi z brskanjem po seznamu kategorij. Obenem omogoča tudi posodabljanje sistema s posodobitvami brez povezave.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Softvér prostredia GNOME predstavuje obľúbené aplikácie a aplikácie základnej výbavy s užitočnými popismi a snímkami obrazovky danej aplikácie. Aplikácie sa dajú nájsť buď prezeraním zoznamu kategórií alebo pomocou vyhľadávača. Tiež umožňuje aktualizovať váš systém za pomoci aktualizácií nevyužívajúcich pripojenie k sieti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Центр приложений GNOME предоставляет рекомендуемые и популярные приложения с описанием и несколькими картинками к ним. Приложения можно находить, просматривая по категориям, либо с помощью функции поиска. Также центр приложений позволяет обновлять систему с помощью отложенных обновлений.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Aplicații GNOME prezintă aplicații recomandate și populare care conțin descrieri folositoare și capturi de ecran multiple pentru fiecare aplicație. Acestea pot fi găsite fie prin răsfoirea listei categoriilor fie printr-o simplă căutare. Vă permite, de asemenea, să actualizați sistemul prin intermediul unei actualizări în modul deconectat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Programas do GNOME mostra aplicativos populares em destaque com descrições úteis e múltiplas capturas de tela per aplicativo. Aplicativos podem ser encontradas tanto navegando a lista de categorias quanto pesquisando. Ele também permite que você atualize seu sistema usando uma atualização sem estar conectado a internet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Aplicações GNOME apresenta aplicações populares em destaque com descrições úteis e múltiplas capturas de ecrã por aplicação. Aplicações podem ser encontradas tanto navegando a lista de categorias com procurando. Também permite que atualize o seu sistema utilizando uma atualização sem estar ligado à Internet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Menedżer oprogramowania dla środowiska GNOME prezentuje polecane i popularne programy z przydatnymi opisami i wieloma zrzutami ekranu. Programy mogą być wyszukiwane lub przeglądane według kategorii. Możliwe jest także aktualizowanie systemu za pomocą funkcji aktualizacji w trybie offline.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pa">ਗਨੋਮ ਸਾਫਟਵੇਅਰ ਖਾਸ ਅਤੇ ਹਰਮਨਪਿਆਰੀਆਂ ਐਪਲੀਕੇਸ਼ਨਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਹਰੇਕ ਐਪਲੀਕੇਸ਼ਨ ਲਈ ਫਾਇਦੇਮੰਦ ਵੇਰਵੇ ਅਤੇ ਕਈ ਤਸਵੀਰਾਂ ਨਾਲ ਵੇਖਾਉਂਦਾ ਹੈ। ਐਪਲੀਕੇਸ਼ਨਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਵਰਗਾਂ ਦੀ ਸੂਚੀ ਵਿਚੋਂ ਚੁਣਿਆ ਜਾਂ ਖੋਜ ਕਰਕੇ ਲੱਭਿਆ ਜਾ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ। ਇਹ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਸਿਸਟਮ ਨੂੰ ਆਫਲਾਈਨ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਦੀ ਵਰਤੋਂ ਕਰਕੇ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਵੀ ਸਹਾਇਕ ਹੈ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="oc">Logicials de GNOME presenta una veirina d'aplicacions conegudas amb l'ajuda de descripcions utilas e de mantuna captura d'ecran per caduna d'elas. Podètz recercar de logicials siá en consultant la lista de las categorias, siá en interrogant lo motor de recèrca. Logicials permet tanben de metre a jorn vòstre sistèma fòra linha.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Gnome Software geeft aanbevolen en populaire toepassingen weer met nuttige beschrijvingen en meerdere schermafdrukken per toepassing. U vindt toepassingen door ofwel de lijst van categorieën te bekijken of door te zoeken. U kunt ook uw systeem bijwerken met behulp van een offline-update.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">GNOME programvare viser utvalgte og populære programmer med nyttige beskrivelser og flere skjermbilder for hvert program. Programmer kan finnes ved å bla gjennom listen med kategorier eller ved å søke. Det lar deg også oppdatere systemet ved bruk av frakoblet oppdatering.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">GNOME programinė įranga parodo siūlomas bei populiarias programas su naudingais aprašymais bei kelios ekrano nuotraukomis kiekvienai programai. Programas galima rasti naršant po kategorijų sąrašą arba ieškant. Taip pat galima atnaujinti sistemą naudojant atnaujinimą atsijungus.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">GNOME “Programmatūra” rāda izceltās un populārās lietotnes, ar noderīgiem aprakstiem un vairākiem ekrānattēliem uz lietotni. Lietotnes var atrast vai nu pārlūkojot kategoriju sarakstu, vai arī meklējot. Tā jums ļauj arī atrast sistēmas atjauninājumus, izmantojot nesaistes atjaunināšanu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">그놈 소프트웨어 프로그램은 각각의 추천 항목과 인기 있는 프로그램을 유용한 설명과 여러가지 미리보기 화면을 곁들여 선보입니다. 분류 목록을 탐색하거나 검색을 통해 프로그램을 찾을 수 있습니다. 오프라인 업데이트를 사용하여 시스템을 업데이트할 수도 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="km">កម្មវិធី GNOME បង្ហាញ​កម្មវិធី​បាន​ជ្រើសរើស និង​មាន​ប្រជាប្រិយ​​រួម​នឹង​ការ​ពណ៌នា​មាន​ប្រយោជន៍​ ព្រម​ទាំង​រូបថត​អេក្រង់​ជា​ច្រើន​ក្នុង​កម្មវិធី​មួយៗ​។ កម្មវិធី​អាច​រក​បាន​ទាំង​តាម​ការរុករក​បញ្ជី​​តាម​ប្រភេទ ឬ​ដោយ​ស្វែងរក​។ វា​ក៏​អនុញ្ញាត​ឲ្យ​អ្នក​ធ្វើ​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​ប្រព័ន្ធ​របស់​អ្នក​ដោយ​ប្រើ​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​ក្រៅ​បណ្ដាញ​។</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">GNOME Software қолданбасы ұсынылатын және әйгілі қолданбаларды көрсетіп отырады, олардың пайдалы сипаттамасы және әрбіреуінің бірнеше скриншоты бар болады. Қолданбаларды санаттар тізімдерін шолу арқылы немесе тікелеі іздеу арқылы табуға болады. Сонымен қатар, бұл қолданба арқылы жүйеңізді желіден тыс жаңартуларымен жаңартуға болады.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">GNOME ソフトウェアでは、注目アプリケーションやよく使用されるアプリケーションを、役立つ説明や豊富なスクリーンショットとともにわかりやすく紹介しています。お探しのアプリケーションを探すのに適した、カテゴリーリストや検索機能も備えています。また、オフラインアップデートによるシステムの更新も可能です。</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">GNOME Software mette in evidenza in bacheca le applicazioni popolari con descrizioni utili e molte schermate per ogni applicazione. Le applicazioni possono essere trovate sia esplorando l'elenco delle categorie sia usando la ricerca. Consente anche di aggiornare il sistema usando un aggiornamento fuori rete.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">GNOME Perangkat Lunak memajang aplikasi-aplikasi populer dan pilihan dengan deskripsi yang berguna dan beberapa cuplikan layar per aplikasi. Aplikasi bisa ditemukan dengan meramban daftar kategori atau dengan mencari. Itu juga memungkinkan Anda memutakhirkan sistem Anda memakai pembaruan luring.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A GNOME Szoftverek bemutatja a kiemelt és népszerű alkalmazásokat, hasznos leírásokat és alkalmazásonként több képernyőképet is megjelenít. Az alkalmazások a kategóriák listáinak tallózásával vagy kereséssel találhatók meg. A program lehetővé teszi a rendszer frissítését kapcsolat nélküli frissítés használatával is.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">GNOME Softver prikazuje istaknute i popularne aplikacije s korisnim opisima i snimkama aplikacija. Aplikacije se mogu pronaći pregledavanjem popisa kategorija ili pretraživanjem. Isto tako vam omogućuje nadopunu vašeg sustava kada nemate pristup Internetu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">‏GNOME תכנה מציג יישומים מומלצים ופופולריים עם תיאור שימושי ומספר צילומי מסך לכל יישום. נתן למצוא יישומים דרך קטגוריות או דרך חיפוש.  כמו כן נתן אף לעדכן את המערכת שלך באמצעות עדכונים לא מקוונים.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">GNOME Software móstralle aplicativos populares e destacados con descricións útiles e varias capturas por aplicativo. Pode atopar aplicativos explorando a lista de categorías ou buscándoos. Tamén lle permite actualizar o seu sistema usando unha actualización fóra de liña.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gd">Seallaidh Bathar-bog GNOME aplacaidean brosnaichte is mòr-chòrdte dhut le tuairisgeul feumail is iomadh glacadh-sgrìn airson gach aplacaid. Gheibh thu greim air tu aplacaidean le brabhsadh tron na roinnean-seòrsa no le lorg. ’S urrainn dhut an siostam agad ùrachadh le ùrachadh far loidhne leis cuideachd.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fur">GNOME Software al met in evidence te bacheche lis aplicazions popolârs cun descrizions utilis e tantis videadis par ogni aplicazion. Lis aplicazions a puedin jessi cjatadis sedial esplorant la liste des categoriis sedial doprant la ricercje. Al permet ancje di inzornâ il sisteme doprant un inzornament fûr rêt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Logiciels de GNOME présente une vitrine d’applications connues à l’aide de descriptions utiles et de plusieurs captures d’écran pour chacune d’elle. Vous pouvez rechercher des logiciels soit en consultant la liste des catégories, soit en interrogeant le moteur de recherche. Logiciels permet aussi de mettre à jour votre système hors ligne.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Ohjelmistot esittelee suosittuja sovelluksia lukuisten kuvakaappausten ja kuvauksen kera. Sovellukset ovat löydettävissä eri luokkia selaamalla tai nimellä etsimällä.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fa">«برنامه‌های گنوم» برنامه‌های محبوب و برتر را همراه با توضیحات مفید و چندین نما از هر برنامه نمایش می‌دهد.برنامه‌ها می‌توانند از طریق مرور دسته‌بندی‌ها یا با استفاده از جست‌وجو پیدا و نصب شوند. همچنین به شما اجازه بروزرسانی سیستم از طریق بصورت برون‌خط را نیز می‌دهد.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">GNOMEren Softwarea aplikazio ospetsuak azalpen erabilgarriekin eta aplikazioko hainbat argazkirekin bistaratzen ditu. Aplikazioak kategorien zerrendan arakatuz aurki daitezke, edo bilaketa eremua erabiliz. Lineaz kanpoko eguneraketaren bidez sistema eguneratzea baimentzen du.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">GNOME Software muestra aplicaciones destacadas y populares con descripciones útiles y varias capturas de pantalla para cada aplicación. Las aplicaciones se pueden encontrar a navegando por la lista de categorías o buscando. También le permite actualizar su sistema mediante una actualización en modo desconectado.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">GNOME Software showcases featured and popular applications with useful descriptions and multiple screenshots per application. Applications can be found either through browsing the list of categories or by searching. It also allows you to update your system using an offline update.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το Λογισμικό GNOME προβάλλει χαρακτηριστικά και δημοφιλείς εφαρμογές με χρήσιμες περιγραφές και πολλαπλά στιγμιότυπα οθόνης ανά εφαρμογή. Οι εφαρμογές μπορούν να βρεθούν είτε μέσα από περιήγηση της λίστας των κατηγοριών ή με αναζήτηση. Σας επιτρέπει επίσης να ενημερώνετε το σύστημά σας χρησιμοποιώντας μια ενημέρωση χωρίς σύνδεση.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">GNOME Software präsentiert vorgestellte und beliebte Anwendungen mit nützlichen Beschreibungen und mehreren Bildschirmfotos je Anwendung. Anwendungen können entweder durch Stöbern in den verschiedenen Kategorien oder mithilfe der Suchfunktion gefunden werden. Zudem ermöglicht es Ihnen, Ihr System mittels einer Offline-Aktualisierung auf den neuesten Stand zu bringen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">GNOME Software særfremviser udvalgte og populære programmer med nyttige beskrivelser og adskillige skærmbilleder per program. Programmer kan findes enten ved gennemsyn af listen af kategorier, eller gennem søgning. Dette program giver dig også mulighed for at opdatere dit system ved brug af offlineopdatering.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Software GNOME vám představí významné a oblíbené aplikace pomocí srozumitelného popisu a několika snímků obrazovky. Aplikace můžete najít buď ručním procházení podle kategorií nebo pomocí textového vyhledávání. Rovněž můžete aktualizovat svůj systém a to i bez aktuálního připojení k Internetu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca@valencia">El Programari del GNOME mostra aplicacions populars i destacades amb descripcions útils i amb múltiples captures de pantalla per aplicació. Les aplicacions es poden trobar tan navegant per la llista de categories com cercant. També vos permet actualitzar el sistema utilitzant l'actualització fora de línia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Programari del GNOME mostra aplicacions populars i destacades amb descripcions útils i amb múltiples captures de pantalla per aplicació. Les aplicacions es poden trobar tan navegant per la llista de categories com cercant. També us permet actualitzar el sistema utilitzant l'actualització fora de línia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">GNOME Softver prikazuje istaknute i popularne aplikacije s korisnim opisima i više snimki ekrana po aplikaciji. Aplikacije se mogu naći bilo kroz pregledavanje listi ili pretraživanjem. Također omogućava da izvršite ažuriranje sistema koristeći ažuriranje bez pristupa internet mreži.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Програмата показва на преден план избрани и популярни приложения, като за всяко може да се види описание и няколко снимки. Приложенията могат да бъдат намерени чрез преглеждане на категоризирания списък или чрез търсене. Освен това, програмата може да обновява системата без връзка с мрежата.</p>
    <p xml:lang="as">GNOME চফ্টৱেৰে উপযোগী বিৱৰণসমূহ আৰু প্ৰতি এপ্লিকেচন একাধিক স্ক্ৰিনশ্বটৰ সৈতে জনপ্ৰিয় এপ্লিকেচনসমূহ দেখুৱায়। এপ্লিকেচনসমূহক বিভাগসমূহৰ তালিকা ব্ৰাউছ কৰি অথবা সন্ধান কৰি বিচাৰি পোৱা যাব। ই লগতে এটা অফলাইন আপডেইট ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি আপোনাক চিস্টেম আপডেইট কৰাৰ সুবিধা দিয়ে।</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">يعرض «برمجيّات جنوم» التّطبيقات المُختارة والشّعبيّة بأوصاف مفيدة وعدّة لقطات شاشة لكلّ تطبيق. يمكن العثور على التّطبيقات من تصفّح قائمة الفئات أو بالبحث. يسمح لك «برمجيّات جنوم» أيضًا بتحديث النّظام باستخدام تحديث دون اتّصال.</p>
    <p xml:lang="af">GNOME-sagteware stal uitgesoekte en populêre toepassings uit met nuttige beskrywings en heelwat skermskote per toepassing. Toepassings kan ontdek word deur deur die kategorielys te blaai of deur te soek. Mens kan ook die stelsel bywerk met 'n vanlynbywerking.</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot height="675" width="1200" type="default">
      <image>https://git.gnome.org/browse/gnome-software/plain/data/appdata/ss-overview.png</image>
      <caption>Overview panel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_TW">概覽面板</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_CN">概览面板</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Genel bakış bölmesi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Översiktspanel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr@latin">Panel pregleda</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr">Панел прегледа</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Okno predogleda</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Panel s náhľadom</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Панель обзора</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Panoul de ansamblu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt_BR">Painel de visão geral</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Panel przeglądu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pa">ਸਾਰ ਪੈਨਲ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="oc">Panèl de vista d'ensemble</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Overzichtspaneel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ne">समिक्षा प्यानल</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nb">Oversiktspanel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Apžvalgos skydelis</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Pārskata rūts</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">개요 패널</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="kk">Шолу панелі</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ja">概要パネル</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Riquadro panoramica</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Panel ringkasan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Áttekintés panel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hr">Panel prikaza</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">דף סקירה</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Páxina de vista xeral</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gd">Panail an fhoir-sheallaidh</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fur">Panel di panoramiche</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Panneau de vue d’ensemble</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Yhteenvetosivu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fa">تابلو نمای کلی</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Ikuspegi orokorraren panela</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Página de vista general</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en_GB">Overview panel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Πίνακας επισκόπησης</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Übersichtsseite</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Oversigtspanel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Panel s přehledem</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca@valencia">Quadre de resum</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Quadre de resum</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Преглед</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">لوحة النّظرة العامّة</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="af">Oorsigpaneel</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot height="675" width="1200">
      <image>https://git.gnome.org/browse/gnome-software/plain/data/appdata/ss-details.png</image>
      <caption>Details panel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_TW">細節面板</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_CN">详情面板</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Ayrıntılar bölmesi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Detaljpanel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr@latin">Panel pojedinosti</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr">Панел појединости</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Okno podrobnosti</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Panel s podrobnosťami</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Панель подробностей</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Panoul cu detalii</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt_BR">Painel de detalhes</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Panel informacji o programie</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pa">ਵੇਰਵਾ ਪੈਨਲ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="oc">Panèl de las descripcions</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Paneel met details</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ne">विस्तृत विवरणहरू</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nb">Panel med detaljer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Detalių skydelis</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Sīkākas informācijas rūts</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">세부 정보 패널</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="kk">Көбірек ақпарат панелі</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ja">詳細パネル</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Riquadro dettagli</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Panel rincian</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Részletek panel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hr">Panel pojedinosti</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">דף פרטים</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Páxina de detalles</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gd">Panail an fhiosrachaidh</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fur">Panel di detais</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Panneau des descriptions</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Tietosivu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fa">تابو جزئیات</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Xehetasunen panela</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Panel de detalles</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en_GB">Details panel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Πίνακας λεπτομερειών</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Seite mit Details</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Detaljepanel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Panel s podrobnostmi o softwaru</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca@valencia">Quadre de detalls</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Quadre de detalls</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Подробности</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">لوحة التّفاصيل</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="af">Besonderhedepaneel</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot height="675" width="1200">
      <image>https://git.gnome.org/browse/gnome-software/plain/data/appdata/ss-installed.png</image>
      <caption>Installed panel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_TW">已安裝面板</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_CN">已安装面板</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Kurulan bölmesi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Installerat-panel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr@latin">Panel instaliranih</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr">Панел инсталираних</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Okno nameščenih programov</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Panel s nainštalovaným softvérom</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Панель установленного</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Panoul cu instalate</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt_BR">Painel de instalados</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Panel zainstalowanych programów</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pa">ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਹੋਏ ਪੈਨਲ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="oc">Panèl de las installacions</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Paneel met geïnstalleerde toepassingen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ne">स्थापित प्यानल</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nb">Panel med installert programvare</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Įdiegtų skydelis</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Instalēto lietotņu rūts</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">설치한 항목 패널</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="kk">Орнатылған панелі</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ja">インストールパネル</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Riquadro installato</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Panel terpasang</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Telepített panel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hr">Panel instaliranog</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">דף התקנה</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Páxina de instalados</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gd">Panail na feadhainn stàlaichte</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fur">Panel instalâts</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Panneau des installations</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Asennussivu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fa">تابلو نصب شده‌ها</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Instalatutakoen panela</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Panel de instalados</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en_GB">Installed panel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Πίνακας εγκατεστημένων</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Seite der Installationen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Installerede-panel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Panel s nainstalovaným softwarem</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca@valencia">S'ha instal·lat el quadre</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">S'ha instal·lat el quadre</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Инсталирани</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">لوحة المثبّتة</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="af">Geïnstalleerpaneel</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot height="675" width="1200">
      <image>https://git.gnome.org/browse/gnome-software/plain/data/appdata/ss-updates.png</image>
      <caption>Updates panel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_TW">更新面板</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_CN">更新面板</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Güncellemeler bölmesi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Uppdateringspanel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr@latin">Panel ažuriranja</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr">Панел ажурирања</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Okno posodobitev</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Panel s aktualizáciami</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Панель обновлений</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Panoul cu actualizări</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt_BR">Painel de atualizações</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Panel aktualizacji</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pa">ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਪੈਨਲ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="oc">Panèl de las mesas a jorn</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Updatespaneel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ne">अपडेट प्यानल</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nb">Panel med oppdateringer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Atnaujinimų skydelis</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Atjauninājumu rūts</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">업데이트 패널</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="kk">Жаңартулар панелі</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ja">更新パネル</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Riquadro aggiornamenti</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Panel pembaruan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Frissítések panel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hr">Panel nadopuna</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">דף עדכון</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Panel de actualizacións</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gd">Panail nan ùrachaidhean</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fur">Panel inzornaments</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Panneau des mises à jour</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Päivityssivu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fa">تابلو بروزرسانی شده‌ها</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Eguneraketen panela</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Panel de actualizaciones</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en_GB">Updates panel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Πίνακας ενημερώσεων</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Seite mit Aktualisierungen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Opdateringspanel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Panel s aktualizacemi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca@valencia">Quadre d'actualitzacions</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Quadre d'actualitzacions</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Обновления</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">لوحة التّحديثات</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="af">Bywerkingspaneel</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot height="675" width="1200">
      <image>https://git.gnome.org/browse/gnome-software/plain/data/appdata/ss-updates-details.png</image>
      <caption>The update details</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_TW">更新的詳細資訊</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_CN">更新详情</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Güncelleme ayrıntıları</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Detaljerna för uppdateringen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr@latin">Pojedinosti ažuriranja</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sr">Појединости ажурирања</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Podrobnosti posodobitve</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Podrobnosti o aktualizácii</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Подробности об обновлении</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Detaliile actualizărilor</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt_BR">Os detalhes da atualização</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Informacje o aktualizacji</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pa">ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਦੇ ਵੇਰਵੇ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="oc">Detalhs de la mesa a jorn</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Details van de update</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ne">अद्यावधिक विवरण</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nb">Vis detaljer for oppdatering</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Atnaujinimo detalės</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Atjauninājumu informācija</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">업데이트 세부 항목</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="kk">Жаңарту ақпараты</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ja">更新の詳細</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">I dettagli dell'aggiornamento</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Detil pembaruan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">A frissítés részletei</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hr">Pojedinosti nadopune</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">פרטי עדכון</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Os detalles da actualización</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gd">Fiosrachadh an ùrachaidh</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fur">I detais dal inzornament</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Détails de la mise à jour</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Päivityksen tiedot</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fa">جزئیات بروزرسانی</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Eguneraketen xehetasunak</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Los detalles de la actualización</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en_GB">The update details</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Λεπτομέρειες ενημέρωσης</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Details zur Aktualisierung</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Opdateringsdetaljerne</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Podrobnosti o aktualizaci</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca@valencia">Detalls de l'actualització</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Detalls de l'actualització</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Подробности за обновлението</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">تفاصيل التحديث</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="af">Die bywerkingsbesonderhede</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <!--
   Validate with `appstream-util validate *.appdata.xml`
  -->
  <releases>
    <release date="2018-04-09" version="3.28.1">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is a stable release with the following changes:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix a regression with opening results from gnome-shell search</li>
          <li>Show "Source: " tag in gnome-shell search when we have multiple matches</li>
          <li>Improve unknown license tag color scheme on details page</li>
          <li>Don't show installed icon on app tiles while still installing</li>
          <li>Fix empty items appearing under OS Updates</li>
          <li>Fix a regression that caused duplicate results in codec search</li>
          <li>Fix an issue with passing username/password to packagekit proxy</li>
          <li>Avoid crashing during first run with no network access</li>
          <li>A number of rpm-ostree fixes, making it possible to trigger offline updates</li>
          <li>Stop searching multiple times on search page</li>
          <li>Update Fedora third party repositories "Find out more..." link</li>
          <li>Fix an issue with in-app notifications failing with invalid markup errors</li>
          <li>Improve purchase failure handling for the snap store</li>
          <li>Fix a possible crash in snap plugin when adding screenshots</li>
          <li>Various other crash and correctness fixes</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-03-12" version="3.28.0">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is the first stable release for GNOME 3.28,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix the build on NixOS</li>
          <li>Fix purchasing not working after authentication</li>
          <li>Revert a commit that led to flatpak updates failing without any feedback</li>
          <li>Make front page featured tile corners round to match other tiles</li>
          <li>Fix in-app notification close button alignment</li>
          <li>Several fixes to make error notifications more useful</li>
          <li>snap: Fix invalid metadata after cancelled refine</li>
          <li>snap: Launch command line snaps with 'snap run'</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-03-05" version="3.27.92">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.27 development series,
          marking the end of the development cycle. Next release will be 3.28.0!
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Removal of global plugin cache, simplifying gnome-software internals</li>
          <li>Software Repositories dialog got another batch of improvements and UI changes</li>
          <li>GNOME Shell Extensions repository and fwupd repositories are now shown in the Software Repositories dialog</li>
          <li>Shell extensions handling through PackageKit was improved, fixing a long standing bug where we were unable to remove shell extension packages</li>
          <li>Category page rewrite that landed earlier this cycle went through UI review and got a number of fixes</li>
          <li>Package version comparison in the updates dialog was fixed and should no longer incorrectly show updates as downgrades</li>
          <li>Distro upgrade notifications are now rate limited to once per week</li>
          <li>Install buttons in codec install view that got lost in the 3.22 cycle are now back</li>
          <li>Various paper cuts with distro upgrades were fixed</li>
          <li>Various fixes to installing apps from yum repos that have enabled=0 enabled_metadata=1</li>
          <li>Various other correctness and warning fixes</li>
          <li>Distros: Minimum supported fwupd version is now 1.0.3</li>
          <li>Distros: We've released PackageKit 1.1.9 that has string changes to match gnome-software 3.28</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-02-14" version="3.27.90">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.27 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>The Software Sources dialog was renamed to Software Repositories and rewritten</li>
          <li>Fedora Workstation third party repository handling was rewritten and should be more robust</li>
          <li>Improved handling of metered network connections, making sure we cancel any downloads when changing to a metered connection</li>
          <li>Limit the number of parallel operations depending on the installed CPU</li>
          <li>Improved handling of pending installs when there's no network connection</li>
          <li>Unused ostree and rpm plugins were dropped</li>
          <li>Switch from GtkSpell to gspell</li>
          <li>Improve alignment on the updates page</li>
          <li>Do not show missing screenshot error for fonts that have screenshots</li>
          <li>Fix various issues on Ubuntu when purchasing apps</li>
          <li>Fix an issue that led to duplicate categories appearing on the overview page</li>
          <li>Various memory leak and correctness fixes</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2018-01-08" version="3.27.4">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.27 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add missing locking to gs_plugin_cache_remove(), fixing a possible crash</li>
          <li>Fix various memory leaks spotted by valgrind</li>
          <li>Fix a possible crash triggered by the fwupd plugin</li>
          <li>Do not emit critical warnings when reviewing OS Updates</li>
          <li>fwupd: Use the custom user-agent when downloading firmware</li>
          <li>overview page: Fix a crash when we have no featured apps</li>
          <li>packagekit: Implement repository enabling</li>
          <li>Fix hover CSS for "unknown" and "nonfree" license buttons</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2017-11-13" version="3.27.3">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.27 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix crashes in the repos plugin due to missing locking</li>
          <li>Add translated strings for the new OARS v1.1 additions</li>
          <li>Work around Firefox deleting rpm/deb files downloaded to /tmp when closing</li>
          <li>Log errors to console when starting from command line</li>
          <li>Do not enable distro-upgrades when updates are disabled</li>
          <li>Do not require the user to keep clicking 'More reviews' after each click</li>
          <li>Fix a critical when updating (flatpak) packages live</li>
          <li>fwupd: Do not crash when trying to list a locked device</li>
          <li>fwupd: Prepend the vendor name to the device name if not included</li>
          <li>Improve SPDX ID parsing when working out if it is 'free'</li>
          <li>packagekit: Do not crash when getting an invalid ID from PackageKit</li>
          <li>packagekit: Support apt:// URLs</li>
          <li>Various fixes to the snap plugin</li>
          <li>Do not crash when closing the source dialog while it is loading</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2017-11-13" version="3.27.2">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.27 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Redesigned category view</li>
          <li>Better notifications for completed distro upgrades</li>
          <li>Number of test suite fixes to pave way for continous integration tests</li>
          <li>Improved support for running on low res displays</li>
          <li>Various fixes to internal state handling</li>
          <li>Allow linking to specified proprietary licenses</li>
          <li>Don't use versioned subdirectories under ~/.cache/gnome-software</li>
          <li>Only show in-app notifications for interactive user actions</li>
          <li>Various fixes for flatpak, fwupd, and snap support</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2017-11-09" version="3.26.2">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is a stable release with the following changes:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Various fixes to cancellable handling, making it more robust to cancel install/remove operations</li>
          <li>Fix a common crash in Fedora distro upgrades plugin</li>
          <li>Fix showing N+2 Fedora upgrades</li>
          <li>Fix flatpak updates inadvertently triggering a reboot</li>
          <li>Revert plugin GType registering changes that broke app "adopting"</li>
          <li>Various flatpak plugin fixes</li>
          <li>Various snap plugin fixes</li>
          <li>Bump fwupd required dep to 0.9.7 and support building with new 1.0.0 API</li>
          <li>Avoid erroring out for operations that return more than 500 results (distro upgrades, getting gnome-shell extensions list)</li>
          <li>Fix a few memory leaks</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2017-10-02" version="3.26.1">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is a stable release with the following changes:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix memory leak in "external appstream" plugin</li>
          <li>Don't translate an icon name in the Punjabi translation</li>
          <li>Fix critical warning in the fwupd plugin if the update URI isn't set</li>
          <li>Fix Addon categories not showing</li>
          <li>Fix crash in PackageKit plugin if reporting progress with no current application</li>
          <li>Revert a change in the snapd plugin which can cause operations to fail or hang in some situations</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2017-09-11" version="3.26.0">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is the first stable release for GNOME 3.26,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Use the new fwupd API in 0.9.7 to avoid when a reboot is required</li>
          <li>Pass the complete proxy settings to PackageKit</li>
        </ul>
        <p>The following bugs are also fixed:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Do not crash when emitting an uncommon error message</li>
          <li>Do not show a critical warning with new versions of fwupd</li>
          <li>Do not show an error for a remote-less flatpakref application</li>
          <li>Don't refine PackageKit packages after we've been cancelled</li>
          <li>Fix a possible crash on 32 bit systems</li>
          <li>Fix GNOME Shell search results for snap applications</li>
          <li>Properly disable shell-extensions when not running GNOME Shell</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2017-08-21" version="3.25.91">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.25 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add a simple donation button on the details page</li>
        </ul>
        <p>The following bugs are also fixed:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Allow plugins to say that installation cannot be cancelled</li>
          <li>Fix displaying the info bar for the Shell Extensions category</li>
          <li>Use first featured snap as the featured app</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2017-08-07" version="3.25.90">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.25 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add a simple donation button on the details page</li>
        </ul>
        <p>The following bugs are also fixed:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Do not crash if the child schema is invalid</li>
          <li>Don't log a warning when clicking the the 'more results' search entry</li>
          <li>Fixed subcategory names localization</li>
          <li>Ensure flatpak remote names are valid</li>
          <li>Fix critical warning with new versions of the fwupd daemon</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2017-07-21" version="3.25.4">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.25 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add new rpm-ostree integration for Fedora Atomic Workstation</li>
          <li>Install the Flatpak runtime as part of the application install phase</li>
          <li>Split OS updates up into multiple sections and show the target version</li>
          <li>Support compatibility IDs when getting reviews from the ODRS</li>
        </ul>
        <p>The following bugs are also fixed:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Cancel plugin jobs if they take too much time</li>
          <li>Correctly find already installed flatpak runtimes</li>
          <li>Do not show an error for a flatpakref when broken remotes exist</li>
          <li>Don't show the screenshot section for runtimes</li>
          <li>Fix authentication prompt not showing when using snapd</li>
          <li>Make license buttons buttons actually look clickable</li>
          <li>Make the review moderator panel easier to use</li>
          <li>Only show snaps as sandboxed if snapd supports confinement</li>
          <li>Respect the per-user or per-system install preferences</li>
          <li>Return the correct installed state for user/system flatpak remotes</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2017-06-22" version="3.25.3">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.25 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add a banner designer utility</li>
          <li>Add the initial support to support purchasable apps</li>
          <li>Automatically install flatpak icon themes and GTK themes</li>
          <li>Restyle the updates panel to have a separate sections</li>
          <li>Show a notification in the updates page when the OS is end of life</li>
          <li>Show recently updated applications on the overview page</li>
        </ul>
        <p>The following bugs are also fixed:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add snap self tests and provide more data to the details panel</li>
          <li>Allow compiling with newer versions of meson</li>
          <li>Do not crash when sending progress reports while refreshing</li>
          <li>Don't trigger systemd for every single offline update</li>
          <li>Ensure all related flatpak applications get installed</li>
          <li>Ensure we use the gnome-desktop support if enabled</li>
          <li>Fix searching for codecs on Ubuntu</li>
          <li>Show a better status messages when downloading metadata</li>
          <li>Show a pulsing progressbar if plugins do not report progress</li>
          <li>Show the PackageKit interactive dialog when required</li>
          <li>Support updating metadata from multiple fwupd remotes</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2017-05-08" version="3.25.2">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.25 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Allow AppStream to be downloaded out-of-band per-user</li>
        </ul>
        <p>The following bugs are also fixed:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Do not initialize plugins in every instance</li>
          <li>Fix the 'Show Details' context menu item in GNOME Shell</li>
          <li>Use headerbar in toolbar-mode in Unity</li>
          <li>Do not allow plugins to set the origin title in the UI</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2017-04-28" version="3.25.1">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.25 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Truncate the search results if there are a large number</li>
          <li>Use the complete source as a search keyword</li>
        </ul>
        <p>The following bugs are also fixed:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fall back to a stock icon for hardware drivers</li>
          <li>Fix a crash when removing an addon</li>
          <li>Fix a critical warning in the shell search provider</li>
          <li>Fix popular-overrides to show the correct applications</li>
          <li>Fix various failures to read from snapd</li>
          <li>Make offline updates work when online updates are available</li>
          <li>Never include the size of the runtime in the installed size</li>
          <li>Respect the install preference when for flatpakref files</li>
          <li>Use the developer name in preference to the project group</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2017-03-13" version="3.23.92">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.23 development series,
          with the following bug fixes:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Allow installing broken flatpakref files</li>
          <li>Do not reload the updates list when updates are in progress</li>
          <li>Reset the headerbar title when switching to the details page</li>
          <li>Unconditionally show things that are in progress in the Installed page</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2017-02-27" version="3.23.91">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.23 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add support for RuntimeRepo in flatpakref files</li>
          <li>Allow the user to restart the currently running gnome-software instance</li>
          <li>Never show components without AppData files</li>
        </ul>
        <p>The following bugs are also fixed:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Initialize progress to zero right before and after processing an action</li>
          <li>Animate the removal of live updates</li>
          <li>Add YaST as a default folder in gnome-shell overview</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2017-02-13" version="3.23.90">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.23 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Handle apt and snap URLs</li>
          <li>Show the updates panel with sections</li>
          <li>Sort the apps in the installed panel by kind</li>
        </ul>
        <p>The following bugs are also fixed:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add a more detailed error message when AC power is required</li>
          <li>Do not hardcode the gnome-software application name</li>
          <li>Ensure firmware is downloaded when not cached</li>
          <li>Fix a rather large memory leak when loading Steam data</li>
          <li>Fix launching Flatpak apps after updating</li>
          <li>Install needed Flatpak runtimes when updating an app</li>
          <li>Only show the scary firmware warning for removable devices</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2016-12-15" version="3.23.3">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.23 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add an --install and --interaction CLI options</li>
          <li>Add the installed size of the apps in the installed view</li>
          <li>Always set a description for each notification</li>
          <li>Show an in-app notification when installed plugins are changed</li>
          <li>Use a set of stars to show the different star ratings</li>
        </ul>
        <p>The following bugs are also fixed:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add a missing error check to fix a common crash on LiveDVD media</li>
          <li>Add thread locking in GsApp to fix some common crashes</li>
          <li>Allow upgrading to Fedora EOL releases</li>
          <li>Don't allow review actions when offline</li>
          <li>Ensure we actually schedule firmware updates for download</li>
          <li>Fix the getting of PackageKit and flatpak update details</li>
          <li>Hide some notifications when the new app is launched or the window is closed</li>
          <li>Hide the screenshot placeholder for input methods and langpacks</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2016-11-21" version="3.23.2">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.23 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add a setting for downloading updates on metered connections</li>
          <li>Add content rating interface for games</li>
          <li>Add support for pending updates that are applied on demand</li>
          <li>Add support for the flatpak DefaultBranch feature</li>
          <li>Allow showing an application review without a display name</li>
          <li>Convert the modal failure dialogs to in-app notifications</li>
          <li>Switch to using the ODRS server hosted by GNOME</li>
        </ul>
        <p>The following bugs are also fixed:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Always get the newest screenshot for GNOME Shell extensions</li>
          <li>Avoid redownloading the same screenshots for different images</li>
          <li>Don't download updates when low on power</li>
          <li>Fix the growth in memory usage for every search request</li>
          <li>Never show a 'back' button when showing search results</li>
          <li>Show the search bar when the user does ctrl+f</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2016-11-07" version="3.22.2">
      <description>
        <p>This stable release fixes the following bugs:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Large number of fixes and improvements for flatpak support</li>
          <li>Improved handling for flatpak repos with multiple branches</li>
          <li>Initial support for installing flatpakrepo files</li>
          <li>Fix a crash when searching for codecs</li>
          <li>Fix a crash when de-duplicating applications</li>
          <li>Speed improvements for loading appstream data</li>
          <li>Refactor snapd handling code using snapd-glib</li>
          <li>Show the search bar when the user does Ctrl+f</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2016-10-12" version="3.22.1">
      <description>
        <p>This stable release fixes the following bugs:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix several issues with flatpak bundles</li>
          <li>Fix installing local packages</li>
          <li>Fix a crash when failing to get an installed flatpak ref</li>
          <li>Speed up loading the details and overview pages</li>
          <li>Switch to using the ODRS server hosted by GNOME</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2016-09-19" version="3.22.0">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is the first stable release for GNOME 3.22 and updates several
          translations.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2016-09-13" version="3.21.92">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.21 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add a new section name in the Addons category for drivers</li>
          <li>Add a plugin to match a hardware modalias</li>
        </ul>
        <p>The following bugs are also fixed:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Do not hide the origin when installing or removing an app</li>
          <li>Do not show the screenshot fallback image for firmware or drivers</li>
          <li>Fix launching app's details from the installed notification</li>
          <li>Fix showing the source line in the installed panel</li>
          <li>Unbreak the GNOME Shell search provider</li>
          <li>Use the same padding as a GtkStackSwitcher</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations for many languages.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2016-08-31" version="3.21.91">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.21 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add functionality to enable non-free sources</li>
          <li>Show the device bootloader screenshot when required</li>
        </ul>
        <p>The following bugs are also fixed:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Always return consistent results by allowing plugins to share a cache</li>
          <li>Ensure the search text is showing when going back to search results</li>
          <li>Only enable the firmware 'Install' button when the device is in the right mode</li>
          <li>Remove an app from the installed view when it's uninstalled</li>
          <li>Show percentage progress when installing firmware</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations for many languages.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2016-08-15" version="3.21.90">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.21 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Limit the ODRS moderation queue to a specific language</li>
        </ul>
        <p>The following bugs are also fixed:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Correctly load .flatpakrepo files</li>
          <li>Don't get the download size for installed flatpak packages</li>
          <li>Fix showing the progress bar when installing apps</li>
          <li>Never try to modify the application name</li>
          <li>Only notify about upgrades once per month</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations for many languages.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2016-07-18" version="3.21.4">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.21 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add a cancel button and progress information to the details page</li>
          <li>Add a dialog to confirm upgrade removals</li>
          <li>Add support for authenticating in plugins</li>
          <li>Add support for snaps</li>
          <li>Enable gtk-doc generation for documentation</li>
          <li>Show a new-style category list on the overview page</li>
          <li>Show origin information when applications are available from multiple sources</li>
          <li>Show sandboxing information for selected applications</li>
          <li>Show the star ratings in more places</li>
          <li>Support installing .flatpakrepo files</li>
          <li>Support launching applicatins using a appstream:// URL</li>
        </ul>
        <p>The following bugs are also fixed:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Allow plugins to be enabled and disabled at runtime</li>
          <li>Always show the 'MyLanguage' kudo when in en_US locale</li>
          <li>Correctly trigger systemd offline updates when only processing OS updates</li>
          <li>Disable app folders feature when run outside GNOME</li>
          <li>Do not show buttons on the search results</li>
          <li>Do not use deprecated CSS properties</li>
          <li>Do not use deprecated fwupd API</li>
          <li>Ensure reviews are shown in the correct order</li>
          <li>Fix a crash when double clicking files</li>
          <li>Fix several UX issues when upgrading</li>
          <li>Show the 'More Reviews' button in the details panel</li>
          <li>Try really hard to have two rows of important categories</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations for many languages.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2016-05-23" version="3.21.2">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.21 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add a --details-pkg option to the gnome-software binary</li>
          <li>Add support for flatpak packages</li>
          <li>Add a plugin to auto-add some license information</li>
          <li>Add depends, requires and conflicts at initialize time</li>
          <li>Add support for application key colors</li>
          <li>Export a set of headers to allow external plugins to be built</li>
        </ul>
        <p>The following bugs are also fixed:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Do not crash if plugins are badly behaved</li>
          <li>Do not directly load pixbufs in the AppStream plugin</li>
          <li>Do not unconditionally invalidate the updates list on hardware hotplug</li>
          <li>Find the best AppSteam component when matching any prefixes</li>
          <li>Fix crash due to network change before app activation</li>
          <li>Fix launching various KDE4 applications</li>
          <li>Support getting cached content from /var/cache and /usr/share</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations for many languages.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2016-04-25" version="3.21.1">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.21 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add an initial loading panel when there is no metadata</li>
          <li>Add an outline ostree plugin that just adds remotes as sources</li>
          <li>Add an unreviewable application quirk</li>
          <li>Add initial Steam support</li>
          <li>Add support for app shortcut addition/removal</li>
          <li>Add support for GNOME Shell extensions</li>
          <li>Allow free-but-unspecified SPDX tokens</li>
          <li>Allow widgets to use custom CSS in a generic way</li>
          <li>Do the PackageKit refresh as a background transaction</li>
          <li>Hide "Software Sources" menu when its action is disabled</li>
          <li>Make the distro upgrades dialog match the new mockup</li>
          <li>Split the 'size' property into size-installed and size-download</li>
          <li>Use a link instead of a button for history</li>
          <li>Use AppStream files for the popular, featured and extra category data</li>
          <li>Use dpkg-deb info to create a GsApp when double clicking on a .deb file</li>
          <li>Use FwupdClient from fwupd 0.7.0</li>
          <li>Use GdkPixbuf to parse icns files</li>
          <li>Use gsettings to enable/disable the 'sources' action</li>
          <li>Use the Fedora themed image for the upgrade banner</li>
          <li>When there are no trusted sources mark everything as non-3rd-party</li>
        </ul>
        <p>The following bugs are also fixed:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Actually show the error dialog for an invalid file</li>
          <li>Allow all functions called by g_module_symbol() to fail</li>
          <li>Allow popular and featured apps to match any prefix</li>
          <li>Do not maintain a cache of applications in the plugin loader</li>
          <li>Do not make the ODRS plugin depend on xdg-app</li>
          <li>Do not re-request the distro-upgrade when switching pages</li>
          <li>Do not show ratings and reviews for some component kinds</li>
          <li>Do not show the distro-upgrade notification if the window is open</li>
          <li>Do not use the header bar on Unity</li>
          <li>Fix a crash when double clicking package files</li>
          <li>Fix live installing firmware</li>
          <li>Get the correct icon size when installing xdg-app bundles on HiDPI</li>
          <li>Hide the kudo details panel for non desktop components</li>
          <li>Load screenshots directly if their URLs point to local files</li>
          <li>Lower the limits for review text</li>
          <li>Make all the plugins more threadsafe</li>
          <li>Make the provenance plugin non-specific to Fedora</li>
          <li>Move header bar button creation into individual pages</li>
          <li>Move the Install &amp; Restart button below the upgrade banner</li>
          <li>Never show star ratings on the category app tiles</li>
          <li>Only show one modal dialog at a time</li>
          <li>Only show the session manager restart if there were any non-live updates</li>
          <li>Properly support multi-line .deb descriptions</li>
          <li>Show a 'Install All' button when all the updates can be installed live</li>
          <li>Show a modal dialog when downloading the distro-upgrade failed</li>
          <li>Show the upgrades banner even if there are no updates to show</li>
          <li>Use a cache file to respect the fedora-distro-upgrades cache-age</li>
          <li>Use GFile instead of a filename when converting apps</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations for many languages.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2016-02-29" version="3.19.91">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.19 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add an 'All' subcategory in the category shell</li>
          <li>Add ratings and review functionality for Ubuntu</li>
          <li>Install the xdg-app runtime as required automatically</li>
          <li>Show a confirmation dialog before reporting a review</li>
          <li>Show a guide label for the different star values</li>
          <li>Support installing local xdg-app bundles</li>
        </ul>
        <p>The following bugs are also fixed:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Correctly identify local packages with sources</li>
          <li>Do not add multiple search results for the same app</li>
          <li>Do not show xdg-app runtimes in the installed panel</li>
          <li>Escape markup before showing modal dialogs</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations for many languages.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2016-02-15" version="3.19.90">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.19 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add end-user application review functionality</li>
          <li>Add support for upgrading the OS from one release to another</li>
          <li>Add support for xdg-app and Limba bundles</li>
          <li>Add tags to applications, and explain them in the details page</li>
          <li>Update the list of featured applications on the front page</li>
        </ul>
        <p>The following bugs are also fixed:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add a missing tag to the software center metadata file</li>
          <li>PackageKit support is now optional</li>
          <li>Temporarily remove the remove button in the sources dialog</li>
          <li>Use versioned user cache directories to pick up new screenshots</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations for many languages.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1452867221" version="3.19.4">
      <description>
        <p>
          This is an unstable release in the 3.19 development series,
          with the following improvements:
        </p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add a link to Wikipedia to explain proprietary and public domain software</li>
          <li>Allow administrators to override the default popular applications</li>
          <li>Improve the interface for device firmware updates and some can be done live</li>
          <li>Make sure Characters and Disks show up in Utilities</li>
          <li>Show 3rd party applications in the search results</li>
          <li>Show a nicer installation dialog when installing local files</li>
          <li>Speed up the application first-start and also speed up switching pages</li>
          <li>Try to show if an application is free software</li>
        </ul>
        <p>The following bugs are also fixed:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Do not crash on refresh if the fwupd daemon is not available</li>
          <li>Fix installing web applications</li>
          <li>Rework several windows to fit better on small screens</li>
          <li>Use the correct user agent string when downloading firmware</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations for many languages.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1446724044" version="3.18.3">
      <description>
        <p>This stable release fixes the following bugs:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Use the correct user agent string when downloading firmware</li>
          <li>Fix a crash in the limba plugin</li>
          <li>Fix installing web applications</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations for many languages.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1444908967" version="3.18.2">
      <description>
        <p>This stable release fixes the following bugs:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix a regression that could lead to never finding any updates</li>
          <li>Fix an issue with getting package details for apps without AppData</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations for many languages.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1444738225" version="3.18.1">
      <description>
        <p>This stable release fixes the following bugs:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Do not force the cache refresh and delete otherwise valid packages</li>
          <li>Fix several potential crashes when navigating and when installing</li>
          <li>Get the new application icon for local packages after installation</li>
          <li>Improve cold start time by only parsing AppStream data once</li>
          <li>Make sure Characters and Disks show up in Utilities</li>
          <li>Only download the fwupd metadata signature once per day</li>
          <li>Show an empty space for no category results</li>
          <li>Show applications without AppData in the installed panel</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations for many languages.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1442827658" version="3.18.0">
      <description>
        <p>This is the first stable release for the GNOME 3.18 desktop!</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1442313469" version="3.17.92">
      <description>
        <p>This is an unstable release in the 3.17 development series, with the following improvements:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix getting firmware updates by parsing the metadata correctly</li>
          <li>Make the application menu path correct in RTL locales</li>
          <li>Don't keep the application running forever when run as a search provider</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations for many languages.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1441303652" version="3.17.91">
      <description>
        <p>This is an unstable release in the 3.17 development series, with the following improvements:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Better theming for the category sidebar</li>
          <li>Use standard size icon in the about dialog</li>
          <li>Support mouse back button for going back in dialogs</li>
          <li>Fix incorrect alignment on the front page in RTL languages</li>
          <li>Misc other minor bugs fixed</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations for many languages.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1439990842" version="3.17.90">
      <description>
        <p>This is an unstable release with the following bugs fixed:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Use CSS to style the error message details</li>
          <li>Correctly align labels in the Add to Folder dialog</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations for many languages.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1439370225" version="3.17.3">
      <description>
        <p>This is an unstable release in the 3.17 development series, with the following improvements:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add basic support for Limba bundles</li>
          <li>Automatically download new firmware metadata from LVFS</li>
          <li>Hide updates UI on managed systems</li>
          <li>Show a new notification when security updates remain unapplied</li>
          <li>Show installation progress when installing applications</li>
          <li>Use some new applications to the picked category</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Bugs fixed in this release:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Do not show applications that are not available when searching by category</li>
          <li>Don't crash when launching an app that has no desktop ID</li>
          <li>Don't show applications without AppData in the category view</li>
          <li>Fix a possible race and crash when loading icons</li>
          <li>Fix locking in the AppStream code to fix several crashes</li>
          <li>Use better error messages on offline update failure</li>
          <li>Withdraw the notification when prepared update gets invalidated</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations for many languages.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1433526589" version="3.17.2">
      <description>
        <p>This is an unstable release in the 3.17 development series, with the following improvements:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Make fwupd dependency automagic</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Bugs fixed in this release:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix a regression from the previous unstable release that made it impossible to install updates</li>
          <li>Fix a crash in the screenshot loader</li>
          <li>Fix a crash in the sources dialog</li>
          <li>Fix a crash when installing rpms that lack description</li>
          <li>Wrap long descriptions in the update dialog</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations for many languages.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1432590395" version="3.17.1">
      <description>
        <p>This is the first unstable release in the 3.17 development series, with a number of new features:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Support getting firmware updates through the fwupd daemon</li>
          <li>Use a smaller number of tiles on the front page on small monitors</li>
          <li>Rework internal modulesets, making it easier to edit the list of featured apps</li>
          <li>Revert back to using a hand-picked list of featured apps</li>
          <li>Several improvements to the sources dialog</li>
          <li>Show better human readable names when searching for font scripts</li>
          <li>Show a spinner while loading the data for the update history dialog</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations for many languages.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1431345463" version="3.16.2">
      <description>
        <p>This release fixes the following bugs:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Remove redundant OK button from the updates installed notification</li>
          <li>Display a better human readable title for printer drivers</li>
          <li>Show a better UI for offline update failure dialog</li>
          <li>Set default actions for the update done notifications</li>
          <li>Allow searching for packages via the API without appdata</li>
          <li>Fix showing webapps with non-local icons</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations for many languages.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1429029680" version="3.16.1">
      <description>
        <p>This release fixes the following bugs:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Correctly save HiDPI images to HiDPI directories</li>
          <li>Scroll the contents of the error message dialog</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations for many languages.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1427103917" version="3.16.0">
      <description>
        <p>This stable release marks the release of GNOME 3.16!</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1426498834" version="3.15.92">
      <description>
        <p>This unstable release adds the following features:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>React to theme changes</li>
          <li>Rebase the HighContrast theme</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release fixes the following bug:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix HiDPI scale factor calculation</li>
          <li>Align section headings in all views</li>
          <li>Fix 'installed' overlays when using the HighContrast theme</li>
          <li>Fall back to showing the top level category when no sub category exists</li>
          <li>Fix a crash when using the pending applications feature</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release also updates translations for many languages.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1425309931" version="3.15.91">
      <description>
        <p>This unstable release adds the following features:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Enable kinetic scrolling in updates dialog</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release fixes the following bug:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Always ensure that the back entry focus widget is valid</li>
          <li>Don't show small screenshots on HiDPI hardware</li>
          <li>Fix a crash when starting GNOME Software for the first time</li>
          <li>Only show compatible projects when getting the featured list</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1424116753" version="3.15.90">
      <description>
        <p>This unstable release adds the following features:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add a new panel for displaying session service results</li>
          <li>Add a new version of the Modify interface</li>
          <li>Require AppData for all available packages</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release fixes the following bug:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Use the new mockups for the 3rd party source install dialogs</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1421625600" version="3.15.4">
      <description>
        <p>This unstable release adds the following features:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix searching with very small search terms</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release fixes the following bugs:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Do case-insensitive searching of suitable keywords</li>
          <li>Fix a crash in the screenshot loader</li>
          <li>Fix a crash when clicking the back button</li>
          <li>Fix searching for keyworks with special chars</li>
          <li>Show an error message when we fail to load details about a local file</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release timestamp="1416787200" version="3.15.2">
      <description>
        <p>This unstable release adds the following features:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Show a blurred low-resolution screenshot while loading the HiDPI one</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This release fixes the following bugs:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Do not show a random white line above the star rating widget</li>
          <li>Do not show empty app boxes if no popular results are available</li>
          <li>Do not try to download local web-app icons</li>
          <li>Use blue stars for the user-ratings rather than gold</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <provides>
    <id>gnome-software.desktop</id>
  </provides>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>AppMenu</kudo>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
    <kudo>Notifications</kudo>
    <kudo>SearchProvider</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugzilla.gnome.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=gnome-software</url>
  <url type="donation">http://www.gnome.org/friends/</url>
  <url type="help"/>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Design/Apps/Software</url>
  <url type="translate">https://wiki.gnome.org/TranslationProject</url>
  <update_contact>richard_at_hughsie.com</update_contact>
  <compulsory_for_desktop>GNOME</compulsory_for_desktop>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <translation type="gettext">gnome-software</translation>
  <developer_name>The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="zh_CN">GNOME 项目</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="tr">GNOME Projesi</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sv">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sr@latin">Gnomov projekat</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sk">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ro">Proiectul GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt_BR">O projeto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pl">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pa">ਗਨੋਮ ਪਰੋਜੈੱਕਟ</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="oc">Lo projècte GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nl">Het Gnome-project</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ne">जिनोम परियोजना</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nb">GNOME prosjektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="lt">GNOME projektas</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="lv">GNOME projekts</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ko">그놈 프로젝트</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="kk">GNOME жобасы</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ja">The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="it">Il progetto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="is">GNOME verkefnið</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="id">Proyek GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="hu">A GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="hr">GNOME projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="he">מיזם GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="gl">O Proxecto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="gd">Pròiseact GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fur">Il progjet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fr">Le projet GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fi">Gnome-projekti</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fa">پروژه گنوم</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="eu">GNOME proiektua</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="es">El proyecto GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="en_GB">The GNOME Project</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="el">Το έργο GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="de">Das GNOME-Projekt</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="da">GNOME-projektet</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="cs">Projekt GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca@valencia">El projecte GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca">El projecte GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="bg">Проектът GNOME</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ar">مشروع جنوم</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="af">Die GNOME Projek</developer_name>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-sexual">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">mild</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
</component>
