<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" xmlns:its="http://www.w3.org/2005/11/its" xmlns="https://specifications.freedesktop.org/metainfo/1.0" type="addon">
  <id>org.gnome.Terminal.Nautilus</id>
  <extends>org.gnome.Nautilus.desktop</extends>
  <metadata_license>GFDL-1.3</metadata_license>
  
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Terminal plugin for Files</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">ملحق طرفيّة لمدير الملفات</name>
  <name xml:lang="be">Плугін тэрмінала для Файлаў</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Приставка за „Файлове“</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Connector de terminal per als fitxers</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca@valencia">Connector de terminal per als fitxers</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Zásuvný modul Terminál pro Soubory</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Terminal-plugin til Filer</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Terminal-Erweiterung für »Dateien«</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Πρόσθετο τερματικού για το Αρχεία</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_GB">Terminal plugin for Files</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Complemento de terminal para Archivos</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Terminalaren osagarria Fitxategientzako</name>
  <name xml:lang="fa">افزونه پایانه برای برنامه «پرونده‌ها»</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Pääteliitännäinen tiedostoselaimeen</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Greffon de terminal pour Fichiers</name>
  <name xml:lang="fur">Plugin terminâl par File</name>
  <name xml:lang="gd">Plugan an tèirmineil airson Faidhlichean</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Engadido de Terminal para Ficheiros</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">Terminal plugin for Files</name>
  <name xml:lang="hr">Terminal priključak za Datoteke</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Terminál bővítmény a Fájlokhoz</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Plugin Terminal bagi Berkas</name>
  <name xml:lang="is">Skjáhermiviðbót fyrir skráastjóra</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Plugin del terminale per File</name>
  <name xml:lang="ja">ファイルアプリケーション向けの端末プラグイン</name>
  <name xml:lang="kk">Файлдар қолданбасы үшін терминал плагині</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">파일 보기용 터미널 플러그인</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Terminalo įskiepis, skirtas Failams</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">Termināļa spraudnis “Datnēm”</name>
  <name xml:lang="ml">ഫയലുകള്‍ക്ക് വേണ്ടിയുള്ള ടെര്‍മിനല്‍ പ്ലഗ്ഗിന്‍</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">Terminaltillegg for Filer</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Terminal-plug-in voor Bestanden</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਫਾਇਲਾਂ ਲਈ ਟਰਮੀਨਲ ਪਲੱਗਇਨ</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Wtyczka terminala dla Menedżera plików</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Plugins do terminal para Ficheiros</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Plug-in do terminal para Arquivos</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Modulul terminal pentru Fișiere</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Модуль терминала для Nautilus</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Zásuvný modul Terminál pre aplikáciu Súbory</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Vstavek terminala za sistemski upravljalnik datotek</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Прикључак терминала за Датотеке</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr@latin">Priključak terminala za Datoteke</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Terminalinsticksmodul för Filer</name>
  <name xml:lang="th">ปลั๊กอินเทอร์มินัลสำหรับ “แฟ้ม”</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Dosyalar için Uçbirim eklentisi</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Додаток для Файлів</name>
  <name xml:lang="vi">Phần bổ sung Thiết bị cuối cho “Tập tin”</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_CN">用于文件管理器的终端插件</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_TW">給《檔案》使用的終端機外掛程式</name>
  <summary>Open a terminal from Files</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">افتح طرفيّة من مدير الملفات</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="be">Адкрыць тэрмінал з праграмы Файлы</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Отваряне на терминал от „Файлове“</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Obre un terminal per als fitxers</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca@valencia">Obri un terminal per als fitxers</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Otevírá terminál z aplikace Soubory</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Åbn en terminal fra Filer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Ein Terminal aus der Dateiverwaltung heraus öffnen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Άνοιγμα τερματικού από τα Αρχεία</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en_GB">Open a terminal from Files</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Abrir una terminal desde Archivos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Ireki terminal bat Fitxategietatik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fa">باز کردن یک پایانه در برنامه «پرونده‌ها»</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Avaa pääte tiedostoselaimesta</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Ouvrir un terminal à partir de Fichiers</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fur">Vierç un terminâl da File</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gd">Fosgail tèirmineal o Fhaidhlichean</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Abrir unha terminal desde Ficheiros</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">Open a terminal from Files</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hr">Otvori terminal iz Datoteka</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Terminál megnyitása a Fájlokban</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Buka sebuah terminal dari Berkas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="is">Opna skjáhermi úr skráastjóra</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Apre un terminale da File</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">ファイルアプリケーションから端末を開く</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="kk">Файлдар қолданбасынан терминалды ашу</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">파일 보기에서 터미널을 엽니다</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Atverti terminalą iš Failų</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">Atvērt termināli no “Datnēm”</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ml">ഫയലുകളില്‍ നിന്ന് ഒരു ടെര്‍മിനല്‍ തുറക്കുക</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nb">Åpne en terminal fra Filer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een terminal openen vanuit Bestanden</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pa">ਫਾਇਲਾਂ ਤੋਂ ਟਰਮੀਨਲ ਨੂੰ ਖੋਲ੍ਹੋ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Otwieranie terminala w Menedżerze plików</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Abrir um terminal a partir de Ficheiros</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Abrir um terminal a partir de Arquivos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Deschide un terminal din Fișiere</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Открывает терминал из Nautilus</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Otvorí terminál z aplikácie Súbory</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Odpri okno terminala iz sistemskega upravljalnika</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Отвара терминал из Датотека</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr@latin">Otvara terminal iz Datoteka</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Öppna en terminal från Filer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="th">เปิดเทอร์มินัลจาก “แฟ้ม”</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Dosyalar uygulaması içinden bir Uçbirim açın</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Відкрити термінал з Файлів</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="vi">Mở Thiết bị cuối từ “Tập tin”</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">从文件管理器打开终端</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">從《檔案》開啟終端機</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Open Terminal is a plugin for the Files application that adds a menu item to the context menu to open a terminal in the currently browsed directory.</p>
    <p xml:lang="be">Плугін тэрмінала для праграмы Файлы дадае пункт у кантэкставае меню, які адкрывае тэрмінал у бягучым каталогу.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Това е приставка за програмата „Файлове“, която добавя команда за отваряне на терминала в текущата папка.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Open Terminal és un connector per l'aplicació de fitxers que afegeix un element de menú al menú contextual per obrir un terminal al directori actual de navegació.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca@valencia">Open Terminal és un connector per l'aplicació de fitxers que afig un element de menú al menú contextual per obrir un terminal al directori actual de navegació.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Otevřít terminál je zásuvný modul pro aplikaci Soubory, který přidává do kontextové nabídky položku pro otevření terminálu v právě procházené složce.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Åbn terminal er et plugin til Filer-programmet, som tilføjer et menupunkt til genvejsmenuen til at åbne en terminal i den aktuelle mappe.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">»Terminal öffnen« ist eine Erweiterung für die Dateien-Anwendung, die einen Menüeintrag in das Kontextmenü einfügt, der ein Terminal im aktuell besuchten Ordner öffnet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το «Άνοιγμα τερματικού» είναι μια επέκταση για τα Αρχεία που προσθέτει ένα αντικείμενο στο μενού περιεχομένων, όπου ανοίγει ένα τερματικό στην τρέχουσα θέση του καταλόγου.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">Open Terminal is a plugin for the Files application that adds a menu item to the context menu to open a terminal in the currently browsed directory.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Abrir terminal es un complemento para la aplicación Archivos que añade un elemento de menú al menú contextual para abrir una terminal en la carpeta actual.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">'Ireki terminala' Fitxategiak aplikazioarentzako osagarri bat da. Testuinguruko menuari elementu bat gehitzen dio terminal bat irekitzeko (uneko direktorioan kokatuta).</p>
    <p xml:lang="fa">«باز کردن در پایانه» یک افزونه برای برنامه «پرونده‌ها» است که یک مورد به منو کلیک راست آن اضافه می‌کند، تا از آن طریق بتوان یک پنجرهٔ پایانه در شاخه فعلی باز کند.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">"Avaa pääte" on liitännäinen tiedostoselaimeen, joka lisää valikkotoiminnon kontekstivalikkoon selattavan kansion kohdalle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Ouvrir un terminal est un greffon pour l’application Fichiers qui ajoute une entrée de menu dans le menu contextuel pour ouvrir un terminal dans le dossier en cours d’affichage.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fur">Vierç terminâl al è un plugin par l'aplicazion File che al zonte un element tal menù di contest, par vierzi un terminâl te cartele atualmentri sfueade.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gd">’S e plugan a th’ ann am “Fosgail tèirmineal” airson aplacaid nam faidhlichean a chuireas nì ris a’ chlàr-taice cho-theacsail gus tèirmineal fhosgladh sa phasgan a thagh thu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Abrir un Terminal é un engadido para o aplicativo Ficheiros que engade un elemento no menú contextual para abrir un terminal no cartafol que se está explorando actualmente.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">Open Terminal is a plugin for the Files application that adds a menu item to the context menu to open a terminal in the currently browsed directory.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">Otvori terminal je priključak za Datoteke aplikaciju koji dodaje stavku u sadržajni izbornik za otvaranje terminala u trenutno pregledanom direktoriju.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A terminál megnyitása egy bővítmény a Fájlok alkalmazáshoz, amely egy menüelemet ad a helyi menühöz, ahonnan terminálablak nyitható az éppen nyitott mappában.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Open Terminal adalah suatu pengaya bagi aplikasi Berkas yang menambah suatu butir menu ke menu konteks untuk membuka sebuah terminal dalam direktori yang saat ini sedang diramban.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Apri terminale è un plugin per l'applicazione File che aggiunge una voce al menù contestuale per aprire un terminale nell'attuale directory in esplorazione.</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">Терминалды Файлдар қолданбасының плагині ретінде ашу, ол ағымдағы бумада терминалды ашу мүмкіндігін беретін контекст мәзірінің опциясын қосады.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">터미널 열기는 파일 보기 프로그램의 현재 보고 있는 디렉터리에서 터미널을 여는 메뉴 항목을 컨텍스트 메뉴에 추가합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Atverti terminalą yra Failų programai skirtas įskiepis, kuris prideda kontekstinio meniu elementą, atveriantį terminalą esamu metu naršomame kataloge.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">“Atvērt termināli” ir spraudnis lietotnei “Datnes”, kas pievieno izvēlnes vienumu konteksta izvēlnei, kas atver termināli pārlūkotajā direktorijā.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Åpne terminal er et tillegg for Filer programmet som legger til en menyoppføring i kontekstmenyen for å åpne en terminal i aktiv katalog.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Terminal Openen is een plug-in voor de Bestanden-toepassing die een menu-item aan het context-menu toevoegt om een terminal te openen in de huidige map.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Wtyczka dla Menedżera plików dodająca element do menu kontekstowego otwierający terminal w obecnie przeglądanym katalogu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Abrir Terminal é um plugin para a aplicação Ficheiros que adiciona no menu de contexto abrir terminal na pasta atual.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Open Terminal é um plug-in para o aplicativo Arquivos que adiciona um item de menu ao menu de contexto para abrir um terminal no diretório navegado no momento.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Deschide terminal este un modul pentru aplicația Fișiere, ce adaugă un element de meniu la meniul contextual pentru a deschide un terminal în dosarul curent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Открыть терминал — модуль для приложения Nautilus, который добавляет в строку в контекстном меню для открытия терминала в текущей просматриваемой папке.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Otvoriť terminál je zásuvný modul pre aplikáciu Súbory, ktorý pridáva položku kontextovej ponuky na otvorenie terminálu v aktuálne prehliadanom adresári.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Open Terminal je vstavek za sistemski urejevalnik datotek Datoteke (Files), ki omogoča odpiranje terminala prek vsebinskega menija.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Отвори терминал је додатак за програм Датотеке, који додаје ставку менија за отварање терминала из тренутног директоријума.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">Otvori terminal je dodatak za program Datoteke, koji dodaje stavku menija za otvaranje terminala iz trenutnog direktorijuma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Öppna terminal är en insticksmodul för programmet Filer som lägger till ett menyobjekt i kontextmenyn för att öppna en terminal i den öppnade katalogen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="th">“เปิดเทอร์มินัล” เป็นปลั๊กอินสำหรับโปรแกรม “แฟ้ม” ที่จะเพิ่มรายการในเมนูคลิกขวา เพื่อใช้เปิดเทอร์มินัลในไดเรกทอรีที่กำลังท่องดูในขณะนั้น</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Open Terminal, Dosyalar uygulaması için geçerli olarak gözüken dizinde bir uçbirim açmak için bağlam menüsüne bir menü ögesi ekleyen bir eklentidir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Відкрити термінал — додаток для програми Файли, яка додає пункт в контекстне меню, щоб відкривати термінал у поточному каталозі. </p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">Mở Thiết bị cuối là phần bổ sung dành cho ứng dụng tập tin cái mà sẽ thêm một mục vào trình đơn ngữ cảnh để mở thiết bị cuối ở thư mục hiện đang được duyệt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">“打开终端”是用于文件管理器的插件，这个插件支持通过右键菜单在当前浏览的目录中打开终端模拟器。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">Open Terminal 是《檔案》應用程式的外掛程式，可以在目前瀏覽目錄的脈絡選單中加入開啟終端機的選單項目。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Terminal</url>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <update_contact>https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/Terminal/ReportingBugs</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">gnome-terminal</translation>
</component>