<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.gnome.font-viewer.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>GNOME Fonts</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_TW">GNOME 字型</name>
  <name xml:lang="vi">Xem phông chữ GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">GNOME Yazı Tipleri</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">GNOME Typsnitt</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr@latin">Gnomovi fontovi</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Гномови фонтови</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Pisave GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Písma prostredia GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Шрифты GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Fontes do GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Przeglądarka czcionek GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Gnome Lettertypen</name>
  <name xml:lang="ne">जिनोम फन्ट</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">GNOME skrifter</name>
  <name xml:lang="ml">ഗ്നോം ഫോണ്ടുകൾ</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">GNOME fonti</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">GNOME šriftai</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">그놈 글꼴</name>
  <name xml:lang="kk">GNOME қаріптер</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Caratteri GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="is">GNOME-letur</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">GNOME Fonta</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">GNOME Betűkészletek</name>
  <name xml:lang="hr">GNOME slova</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Tipos de letra de GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="gd">Cruthan-clò GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="fur">Caratars di GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Polices de GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Gnomen Fontit</name>
  <name xml:lang="fa">قلم‌های گنوم</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">GNOMEren Letra-tipoak</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Tipografías de GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_GB">GNOME Fonts</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Εφαρμογή Γραμματοσειρές GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">GNOME Schriften</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">GNOME Skrifttyper</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Prohlížeč fontů GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca@valencia">Tipus de lletra del GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Tipus de lletra del GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Преглед на шрифт</name>
  <name xml:lang="be">Шрыфты GNOME</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">خطوط جنوم</name>
  <summary>View fonts on your system</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">檢視您系統上的字型</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_HK">檢視你系統上的字型</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">查看您系统中的字体</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="vi">Ứng dụng xem phông chữ trên hệ thống của bạn</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uz@cyrillic">Системадаги шрифтларни кўриш</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Переглянути шрифти на вашій системі</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ug">بۇ سىستېمىدىكى خەت نۇسخىلىرىنى كۆرۈش پروگراممىسىدۇر</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Sisteminizdeki yazı tiplerini görüntüleyin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="th">ดูแบบอักษรต่างๆ ในระบบของคุณ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tg">Намоиш додани шрифтҳои системаи шумо</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="te">మీ వ్యవస్థలో ఉన్న ఖతులను చూడండి</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ta">எழுத்துருக்களை கணினியில் பார்க்கவும்</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Visa typsnitt på ditt system</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr@latin">Pregledajte pisma na vašem sistemu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Прегледајте писма на вашем систему</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Pregled pisav v sistemu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Zobrazuje písma vo vašom systéme</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Просмотр шрифтов, доступных в системе</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Vizualizați fonturile instalate pe sistemul dumneavoastră</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Ver fontes no seu sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Visualize as letras no seu sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Wyświetlanie czcionek w systemie</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pa">ਆਪਣੇ ਸਿਸਟਮ ਉੱਤੇ ਫੋਂਟ ਵੇਖੋ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="or">ଆପଣଙ୍କ ତନ୍ତ୍ରରେ ଅକ୍ଷରରୂପଗୁଡ଼ିକୁ ଦେଖନ୍ତୁ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="oc">Aficha las poliças de vòstre sistèma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Lettertypen op uw systeem bekijken</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ne">प्रणालीको फन्ट हेर्नुहोस्</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nb">Vis skrifter på systemet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="mr">प्रणालीवरील फाँट्स्चे दृष्य</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ml">നിങ്ങളുടെ സിസ്റ്റത്തില്‍ അക്ഷരസഞ്ചയങ്ങള്‍ കാണുക</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">Pārlūkojiet un apskatiet savas sistēmas fontus</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Rodyti sistemos šriftus</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ky">Системада орнотулган алиптерди кароо</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">시스템에 설치된 글꼴을 봅니다</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="kn">ನಿಮ್ಮ ವ್ಯವಸ್ಥೆಯಲ್ಲಿನ ಅಕ್ಷರಶೈಲಿಗಳನ್ನು ನೋಡಿ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="kk">Жүйеңіздегі қаріптерді қарау</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">システム上のフォントを閲覧します</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Visualizza i caratteri presenti nel sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="is">Skoða letur á kerfinu þínu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Lihat fonta pada sistem Anda</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Telepített betűkészletek megjelenítése</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hr">Pregledajte slova na vašem sustavu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hi">अपने तंत्र पर फ़ॉन्ट देखें</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">צפייה בגופנים במערכת שלך</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gu">તમારી સિસ્ટમ પર ફોન્ટ જુઓ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Ver os tipos de letra do seu sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gd">Seall na cruthan-clò air an t-siostam agad</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ga">Amharc ar chlónna do chórais</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fur">Viôt i caratars tal to sisteme</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Affiche les polices de votre système</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Katsele koneellasi olevia fontteja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fa">قلم‌های روی سیستم را ببینید</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Ikusi sistemako letra-tipoak</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Kuva selles arvutis olevaid kirjatüüpe</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Ver las tipografías de su sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Rigardi tiparojn en via sistemo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en_GB">View fonts on your system</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Δείτε τις γραμματοσειρές του συστήματος σας</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Schriftarten Ihres Systems betrachten</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Vis skrifttyper på dit system</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Zobrazte si fonty ve svém systému</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca@valencia">Visualitza tots els tipus de lletra del sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Visualitza tots els tipus de lletra del sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bs">Pogledaj fontove na sistemu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="br">Gwelout an nodrezhoù ho reizhiad</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bn_IN">সিস্টেমের মধ্যে উপস্থিত ফন্ট দেখুন</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Преглед на шрифтовете</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="be">Прагляд шрыфтоў у вашай сістэме</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="as">আপোনাৰ চিস্টেমৰ ফন্টসমূহ দৰ্শন কৰক</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">اعرض الخطوط على نظامك</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="an">Veyer as fuents d'o suyo sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="af">Bekyk fonte op die stelsel</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      GNOME Fonts shows you the fonts installed on your computer for your use as
      thumbnails.
      Selecting any thumbnails shows the full view of how the font would look under
      various sizes.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">GNOME 字型使用縮圖顯示在您電腦上安裝的字型。選擇任何縮圖可以顯示出字型在各種尺寸下外觀的完整檢視。</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">Bộ xem phông chữ GNOME hiển thị cho bạn những phông chữ đã được cài đặt trên máy tính của bạn để bạn dùng như là ảnh mẫu. Chọn bất kỳ ảnh mẫu nào để hiển thị xem nó trông như thế nào khi ở các kích cỡ khác nhau.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">GNOME Yazı Tipleri, kullanımınız için bilgisayarınızda yüklü yazı tiplerini küçük resim olarak gösterir. Herhangi bir küçük resmi seçmek, yazı tipinin çeşitli boyutlarda nasıl görüneceğine dair tam bir görünümü gösterir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">GNOME Typsnitt visar dig de för dig tillgängliga installerade typsnitten på din dator som miniatyrbilder. Att välja en miniatyrbild visar en full överblick över hur typsnittet skulle se ut i olika storlekar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">Gnomovi fontovi vam prikazuje fontove instalirane na vašem računaru za vašu upotrebu kao minijature. Biranje neke minijature prikazuje potpun pregled kako bi font trebao da izgledau raznim veličinama.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Гномови фонтови вам приказује фонтове инсталиране на вашем рачунару за вашу употребу као минијатуре. Бирање неке минијатуре приказује потпун преглед како би фонт требао да изгледау разним величинама.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Program Pregledovalnik pisav za GNOME pokaže pisave, ki so nameščene v sistemu, kot sličice. Z izborom posamezne sličice se pokaže poln prikaz pisave pri različnih velikostih.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Písma prostredia GNOME v podobe miniatúr zobrazujú písma nainštalované v počítači, ktoré je možné použiť. Po vybratí niektorej miniatúry sa zobrazí celistvý náhľad vzhľadu písma v rôznych veľkostiach.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Приложение «Шрифты GNOME» показывает установленные на вашем компьютере шрифты в виде миниатюр. Выбор миниатюры открывает подробный режим просмотра шрифта, как будет выглядеть шрифт при различных размерах.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">O Fontes do GNOME mostra a você as fontes instaladas em seu computador para seu uso como miniaturas. Ao selecionar qualquer miniatura é mostrado a você visão completa de como a fonte pareceria sob vários tamanhos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Przeglądarka czcionek GNOME wyświetla obecnie zainstalowane czcionki na komputerze w postaci miniatur. Aby zobaczyć, jak dana czcionka prezentuje się w różnych rozmiarach, wystarczy tylko zaznaczyć jej miniaturę.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Gnome Lettertypen toont u de lettertypen die op uw computer geïnstalleerd zijn als miniaturen. Het selecteren van een miniatuur laat zien hoe het lettertype eruit ziet bij verschillende groottes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ne">जिनोम फन्टहरू तपाइँ थम्बनेलको रूपमा प्रयोगको लागि तपाईंको कम्प्युटरमा स्थापित फन्टहरू देखाउँछ। कुनै पनि थम्बनेल चयन गर्नाले कसरी विभिन्न आकारहरू मा फन्ट हेर्नेछ भन्ने पूर्ण दृश्य देखाउँदछ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">GNOME skrifter viser deg skrifter som er installert på din datamaskin som miniatyrer. Ved å velge en miniatyr får du en full visning av hvordan skriften vil se ut i forskjellige størrelser.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">GNOME fonti rāda datorā instalētos fontus kā sīktēlus. Jebkura sīktēla izvēlēšanās rāda, kā fonts izskatītos dažādos izmēros.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">GNOME šriftai rodo jūsų kompiuteryje įdiegtus šriftus miniatiūrų pavidalu. Pasirinkus bet kurią miniatiūrą parodoma, kaip šriftas atrodytų įvairiais dydžiais.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">그놈 글꼴은 컴퓨터에 설치한 글꼴을 섬네일로 표시합니다. 섬네일을 선택하면 크기에 따라 글꼴이 어떻게 보이는지 표시합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">GNOME қаріптері компьютеріңізде орнатылған қаріптерді кіші үлгілер ретінде ретінде көрсетеді. Үлгіні таңдау кезінде ол қаріптің толық көрінісі және әр түрлі өлшемдердегі түрі көрсетіледі.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Caratteri GNOME mostra tutti i caratteri installati sul proprio computer tramite delle miniature degli stessi: selezionando una miniatura vengono mostrate le varie dimensioni del carattere.</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">GNOME-letur sýnir þér sem smámyndir það letur sem uppsett er á kerfinu þínu. Ef þú velur einhverja smámyndina geturðu séð hvernig letrið lítur út í mismunandi stærðum.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">GNOME Fonta menampilkan fonta yang terpasang dan dapat dipakai pada komputer Anda sebagai gambar mini. Memilih sebarang gambar mini akan menampilkan tilikan penuh tentang bagaimana fonta akan nampak pada berbagai ukuran.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A GNOME Betűkészletek bélyegképként jeleníti meg a számítógépén telepített betűkészleteket. A bélyegképek kiválasztásakor megjelenik egy teljes nézet, hogy az adott betűkészlet hogyan néz ki különböző méretekben.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">GNOME slova prikazuje vam slova instalirana na vaše računalo, prikazana kao minijature. Odabir bilo koje minijature prikazuje cjelovit prikaz kako slova izgledaju u različitim veličinama.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Tipos de letra de GNOME móstralle os tipos de letra instalados no seu computador listos para usar como miniaturas. Seleccionando calquera das miniaturas móstrase unha vista completa de como o tipo de letra debería verse con varios tamaños.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gd">Seallaidh Cruthan-clò GNOME na cruthan-clò a bhios stàlaichte air a’ choimpiutair agad ach an cleachd thu mar dhealbhagan iad. Tagh dealbhag sam bith airson sealladh iomlan air cò ris a bhiodh an cruth-clò coltach ann an caochladh de mheudan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fur">Caratars GNOME al mostre ducj i caratars instalâts sul to computer come miniaturis. Selezionant une miniature al ven mostrât ce mût che si viôt il caratar tes in varis dimensions.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Polices GNOME affiche les polices de caractères installées sur votre ordinateur sous la forme de miniatures. En choisissant l’une de celles-ci, vous obtenez une vue complète de la police à différentes tailles.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Fontit näyttää järjestelmään asennetut fontit esikatselukuvina. Minkä tahansa esikatselukuvan valitseminen näyttää fontin eri kokoluokissa ja esimerkkitekstiä.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fa">نمایشگر قلم گنوم، قلم‌هایی که روی رایانه‌ی شما نصب شده است را به صورت بندانگشتی نشانتان می‌دهد. انتخاب هر بندانگشتی، نمای کامل چک.نگی دیده شدن قلم در اندازه‌های مختلف را نمایش می‌دهد.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">GNOMEren Letra-tipoak ordenagailuan instalatuta dauden letra-tipoak koadro txikietan erakusten ditu. Edozer koadro-txiki hautatuz letra-tipoa hainbat tamainatan nola ikusiko den bistaratzen du.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Tipografías de GNOME muestra las tipografías instaladas en el equipo como miniaturas. Al seleccionar cualquiera de ellas se muestra una vista completa de cómo queda la tipografía con varios tamaños.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">GNOME Fonts shows you the fonts installed on your computer for your use as thumbnails. Selecting any thumbnails shows the full view of how the font would look under various sizes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Η εφαρμογή Γραμματοσειρές GNOME σας δείχνει τις γραμματοσειρές που είναι εγκατεστημένες στον υπολογιστή σας για δική σας χρήση, σε μορφή μικρογραφιών. Επιλέγοντας μια μικρογραφία, θα σας εμφανίσει σε πλήρη προβολή πως θα έδειχνε αυτή η γραμματοσειρά σε διάφορα μεγέθη.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">GNOME Schriften zeigt Ihnen eine Vorschau der Schriftarten, die auf Ihrem Rechner installiert sind. Die Auswahl eines Vorschaubildes zeigt die vollständige Ansicht, wie die Schriftart unter verschiedenen Größen aussieht.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">GNOME Skrifttyper viser dig de skrifttyper, som er installeret på din computer, som miniaturer. Hvis du vælger en miniature, vises en fuld repræsentation af skrifttypen med forskellige tekststørrelser.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Fonty GNOME vám zobrazí v podobě náhledů fonty nainstalovaná ve vašem počítači. Po vybrání náhledu uvidíte, jak font vypadá v různých velikostech.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca@valencia">Els Tipus de lletra del GNOME vos mostra en miniatures els tipus de lletra instal·lats a l'ordinador. En seleccionar una de les miniatures se vos mostrarà la vista completa de com es veurà el tipus de lletra en diferents mides.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Els Tipus de lletra del GNOME us mostra en miniatures els tipus de lletra instal·lats a l'ordinador. En seleccionar una de les miniatures se us mostrarà la vista completa de com es veurà el tipus de lletra en diferents mides.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Шрифтовете на GNOME показват инсталираните шрифтове като мини-изображение. Когато ги изберете, ще видите шрифта представен при различни размери.</p>
    <p xml:lang="be">Шрыфты GNOME паказвае шрыфты, усталяваныя на вашым камп'ютары, у выглядзе мініяцюр. Выбраўшы любую мініяцюру, можна ўбачыць, як адпаведны шрыфт будзе выглядаць у розных памерах.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">يعرض برنامج خطوط جنوم الخطوط المنصبة على حاسوبك على شكل مصغرات. اختيار أي مصغرة ينتقل إلى المنظور الكامل لكيفية ظهور الخط في مختلف الأحجام.</p>
    <p>
      GNOME Fonts also supports installing new font files downloaded in the .ttf
      and other formats.
      Fonts may be installed only for your use or made available to all users on the computer.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">GNOME 字型也支援從下載的 .ttf 與其他格式安裝新字型。可以僅安裝字型供您個人使用，或是給電腦上所有的使用者使用。</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">Bộ xem phông chữ GNOME cũng hỗ trợ cài đặt các tập tin phông chữ được tải về ở định dạng .ttf và khác nữa. Phông chữ có thể được cài đặt dành riêng cho bạn hay cho tất cả các tài khoản khác trên máy tính.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Ayrıca GNOME Yazı Tipleri, .ttf ve diğer biçimlerde indirilen yeni yazı tipi dosyalarının kurulumuna da izin verir. Yazı tipleri yalnızca kendi kullanımınız için kurulabilir ya da bilgisayardaki tüm kullanıcıların kullanımına sunulabilir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">GNOME Typsnitt stöder också installation av nya typsnittsfiler hämtade i formatet .ttf och andra format. Typsnitt kan installeras endast för dig eller göras tillgängliga för alla användare på datorn.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr@latin">Gnomovi fontovi takođe podržava instaliranje datoteka novih fontova preuzetih u „.ttf“ i drugim zapisima. Fontovi mogu biti instalirani samo za vašu upotrebu ili mogu biti dostupni svim korisnicima na računaru.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Гномови фонтови такође подржава инсталирање датотека нових фонтова преузетих у „.ttf“ и другим записима. Фонтови могу бити инсталирани само за вашу употребу или могу бити доступни свим корисницима на рачунару.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Program Pregledovalnik pisav za GNOME podpira nameščanje datotek pisav .ttf in drugih. Pisave je mogoče namestiti le za osebno rabo, ali pa za vse uporabnike naprave.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Písma prostredia GNOME podporujú inštalovanie nových písiem z prevzatých súborov vo formáte .ttf aj v iných formátoch. Písma môžu byť nainštalované iba pre jedného používateľa alebo všetkých používateľov na počítači.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Приложение также поддерживает установку новых шрифтов из файлов формата .ttf и прочих форматов. Шрифты можно установить для текущего пользователя или для всех пользователей компьютера.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">O Fontes do GNOME também provê suporte a instalação de novos arquivos de fontes baixadas em .ttf e em outros formatos. Fontes também podem ser instaladas apenas para seu uso ou estar disponíveis para todos os usuários no computador.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Za pomocą Przeglądarki czcionek GNOME można również instalować nowe czcionki z plików w formacie .ttf i wielu innych. Można je zainstalować do własnego użytku lub udostępnić wszystkim użytkownikom komputera.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Gnome Lettertypen ondersteunt ook het installeren van nieuwe lettertypen, o.a. in de vorm van .ttf-bestanden. Lettertypen kunnen voor eigen gebruik worden geïnstalleerd of beschikbaar worden gemaakt voor alle gebruikers van de computer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ne">जिनोम फन्टहरू .ttf र अन्य ढाँचामा डाउनलोड गरिएका नयाँ फन्ट फाइलहरू स्थापना गर्न पनि समर्थन गर्दछ। फन्टहरू तपाईँको प्रयोगको लागि मात्रै स्थापित वा कम्प्यूटरमा सबै प्रयोगकर्ताहरूको लागि उपलब्ध गराउन सकिन्छ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">GNOME skrifter støtter også å installere nye skriftfiler som er lastet ned i ttf- og andre formater. Skriftene kan installeres for personlig bruk eller gjøres tilgjengelig for alle brukere på datamaskinen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">GNOME fonti arī atbalsta jaunu fontu datņu instalēšanu, kas ir .ttf un citos formātos. Fontus var instalēt tikai savām vajadzībām vai visiem datora lietotājiem.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">GNOME šriftai taip pat palaiko naujus šriftų failus, parsiųstus .ttf ir kitais formatais. Šriftai gali būti įdiegti jūsų naudojimui arba padaryti prieinamais visiems kompiuterio naudotojams.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">.ttf나 기타 형식으로 다운로드한 글꼴 파일을 설치할 수도 있습니다. 자기만 쓸 수 있게 설치할 수도 있고 컴퓨터의 모든 사용자가 사용할 수 있게 설치할 수도 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">GNOME қаріптері сонымен қатар .ttf және басқа пішімдегі жаңа қаріптерді орнатуды қолдайды. Қаріптерді тек өзіңіз немесе компьютердің барлық пайдаланушылары үшін орнатуға болады.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Caratteri GNOME consente di installare nuovi caratteri da file scaricati nel formato .ttf e anche altri formati. I caratteri possono essere installati per uso personale o per tutti gli utenti del computer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">GNOME-letur styður einnig að setja inn nýjar leturskrár sem þú hefur náð í á .ttf og fleiri sniðum. Letrið má setja upp fyrir þig einan eða fyrir alla notendur á tölvunni.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">GNOME Fonta juga mendukung pemasangan fonta baru yang diunduh dalam .ttf dan format lain. Fonta bisa dipasang hanya untuk Anda pakai atau dibuat tersedia bagi semua pengguna pada komputer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A GNOME Betűkészletek támogatja a .ttf és más formátumú letöltött, új betűkészletfájlok telepítését is. A betűkészletek telepíthetők csak személyes felhasználásra, vagy a számítógép minden felhasználója számára is.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hr">GNOME slova isto tako podržava instalaciju datoteka novih slova preuzetih u .ttf i ostalim formatima. Slova možete instalirati samo za vlastitu upotrebu ili ih možete učiniti dostupnim ostalim korisnicima na računalu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Tipos de letra de GNOME tamén admite a instalación de novos ficheiros de tipos de letra en .ttf e outros formatos. Os tipos de letra poden instalarse só para o seu usuario ou facelo para todos os usuarios do computador.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gd">Cuiridh Cruthan-clò GNOME cuideachd taic ri stàladh chruthan-clò ùra a chaidh a luchdadh a-nuas san fhòrmat .ttf agus eile. Faodaidh tu taghadh an tèid cruth-clò a stàladh air do shon-sa a-mhàin no airson a h-uile duine a chleachdas an coimpiutair agad.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fur">Caratars GNOME al permet di instalâ gnûfs caratars dai file discjariâts tal formât .ttf e altris formâts. I caratars a puedin jessi instalâts pal ûs personâl o par ducj i utents dal computer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Polices GNOME prend également en charge l’installation de nouveaux fichiers de police téléchargés (formats ttf et autres). Les polices peuvent être installées pour vous seul ou rendues disponibles à tous les utilisateurs de l’ordinateur.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Gnomen Fonttien avulla on myös mahdollista asentaa esimerkiksi internetistä ladattuja .ttf-muodossa ja muissa muodoissa olevia fonttitiedostoja. Fontit on mahdollista asentaa vain omaan käyttöön tai kaikkien järjestelmää käyttävien saataville.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fa">نمایشگر قلم گنوم هم‌چنین از نصب پرونده‌های قلم‌های جدید بارگیری شده در قالب ttf و دیگر قالب‌ها پشتیبانی می‌کند. قلم‌ها می‌توانند فقط برای استفاده‌ی شما یا قابل دست‌رسی برای همه‌ی کاربران روی رایانه باشند.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">GNOMEren Letra-tipoak letra-tipoen fitxategi berriak (.ttf edo beste formatuan deskargatuta) instala ditzake. Letra-tipoa zure erabilpenerako soilik instala daiteke, edo ordenagailuko beste erabiltzaile guztientzako baita ere.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Tipografías de GNOME también soporta instalar nuevas tipografías descargadas como archivos .ttf u otros formatos. Las tipografías se puede instalar para su uso personal o para que estén disponibles para todos los usuarios del sistema.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">GNOME Fonts also supports installing new font files downloaded in the .ttf and other formats. Fonts may be installed only for your use or made available to all users on the computer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Η εφαρμογή Γραμματοσειρές GNOME υποστηρίζει επίσης την εγκατάσταση αρχείων για νέες γραμματοσειρές που λήφθηκαν σε μορφή .ttf ή σε άλλα πρότυπα. Οι γραμματοσειρές μπορούν να εγκατασταθούν είτε αποκλειστικά για δική σας χρήση, είτε να είναι διαθέσιμες για όλους τους χρήστες στον υπολογιστή σας.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">GNOME Schriften unterstützt auch die Installation neuer Schriftartendateien als .ttf oder auch in anderen Formaten. Schriftarten können zu Ihrer eigenen Verwendung oder für alle Benutzer eines Rechners installiert werden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">GNOME Skrifttyper understøtter også installation af nye skrifttypefiler hentet i .ttf og andre formater. Skrifttyper kan installeres til brug for kun dig selv, eller gøres tilgængelige for alle brugere af computeren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Fonty GNOME umí také nainstalovat nové fonty poskytnuté ve formátu .ttf a dalších formátech. Fonty je možné instalovat jen pro své použití nebo je zpřístupnit všem uživatelům počítače.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca@valencia">Els Tipus de lletra del GNOME també permet la instal·lació de fitxers de tipus de lletra en format .ttf i d'altres. Els tipus de lletra es poden instal·lar només per al vostre ús o fer-los accessibles per a tots els usuaris de l'ordinador. </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Els Tipus de lletra del GNOME també permet la instal·lació de fitxers de tipus de lletra en format .ttf i d'altres. Els tipus de lletra es poden instal·lar només per al vostre ús o fer-los accessibles per a tots els usuaris de l'ordinador. </p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Шрифтовете на GNOME позволяват инсталирането на допълнителни шрифтове в множество формати. Инсталирането може да е за един или за всички потребители.</p>
    <p xml:lang="be">Шрыфты GNOME таксама падтрымлівае ўсталяванне новых файлаў з шрыфтамі ў фармаце .ttf ды іншых. Шрыфты могуць быць усталяваны толькі для вас або для ўсіх карыстальнікаў камп'ютара.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">كما يدعم برنامج خطوط جنوم تنصيب ملفات الخطوط الجديدة بأنساقها المختلفة. يمكن تنصيب الخطوط لاستخدامك الشخصي فقط أو لكل المستخدمين.</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.gnome.org/gnome-3/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugzilla.gnome.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=gnome-font-viewer</url>
  <url type="donation">http://www.gnome.org/friends/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://help.gnome.org/misc/release-notes/3.6/figures/users-font-viewer.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>GNOME</project_group>
  <compulsory_for_desktop>GNOME</compulsory_for_desktop>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>AppMenu</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <translation type="gettext">gnome-font-viewer</translation>
</component>
