<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.kinfocenter</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>Info Center</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Centre d'informació</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Centre d'informació</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Informační centrum</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Infocenter</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Infozentrum</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Info Centre</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Centro de información</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Info-gunea</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Tietokeskus</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Centre d'informations</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Centro de información</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Info Center</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Centro d'informazione</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">정보 센터</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Informacinis centras</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Informatiecentrum</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Informasjonssenter</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Ośrodek danych</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Centro de Informações</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Centro de informações</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Информация о системе</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Informačné centrum</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Informationscentral</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Центр інформації</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxInfo Centerxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">信息中心</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">資訊中心</name>
  <summary>Centralized and convenient overview of system information</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Resum centralitzat i pràctic de la informació del sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Resum centralitzat i pràctic de la informació del sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Zentrale Übersicht über Systeminformationen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Centralised and convenient overview of system information</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Resumen práctico y centralizado de la información del sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Sistema-informazioaren ikuspegi-orokor zentralizatu eta praktikoa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Järjestelmätietojen mukava keskitetty yleisnäkymä</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Aperçu centralisé et pratique des informations système</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Resumo centralizado e cómodo de información do sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Ikhtisar informasi sistem yang terpusat dan serasi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Panoramica centralizzata e comoda delle informazioni di sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">시스템 정보를 한 눈에 보기</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Centralizuota ir patogi sistemos informacijos apžvalga</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Gecentraliseerd en prettig overzicht van systeeminformatie</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Sentralisert og praktisk oversikt over systeminformasjon</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Skupiony w jednym miejscu i wygodny przegląd danych o systemie</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Visão centralizada e conveniente da informação do sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Visão geral centralizada e conveniente das informações do sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Централизованный и удобный просмотр информации о системе</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Centralizovaný a pohodlný prehľad systémových informácií</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Centraliserad och bekväm översikt av systeminformation</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Централізований та зручний огляд усіх даних щодо системи</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxCentralized and convenient overview of system informationxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">中心化和方便的系统信息展示</summary>
  <description>
    <p>The Info Center provides you with a centralized and convenient
     overview of your system and desktop environment.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Centre d'informació proporciona una vista general centralitzada i còmoda del sistema i l'escriptori.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El Centre d'informació proporciona una vista general centralitzada i còmoda del sistema i de l'escriptori.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Das  Infozentrum bietet Ihnen einen zentralisierten und bequemen Überblick über Ihr System und die Arbeitsumgebung.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">The Info Centre provides you with a centralised and convenient overview of your system and desktop environment.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">El centro de información le proporciona un resumen práctico y centralizado del entorno de su sistema y de su escritorio.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Info-guneak zure sistemaren eta mahaigain ingurunearen ikuspegi-orokor zentralizatu eta praktiko bat ematen dizu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Tietokeskus tarjoaa mukavan keskitetyn yleisnäkymä järjestelmään ja työpöytäympäristöön.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Le centre d'informations vous propose un aperçu centralisé et pratique des informations du système et de l'environnement de bureau.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">O centro de información fornécelle un resumo centralizado e cómodo do seu sistema e contorno de escritorio.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Info Center menyediakanmu dengan ikhtisar terpusat dan serasi terhadap sistem dan lingkungan desktop-mu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Il centro d'informazione ti dà una panoramica centralizzata e comoda sul tuo sistema e sull'ambiente desktop.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">정보 센터에서는 시스템과 데스크톱 환경 정보를 모아서 표시합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Informacinis centras pateikia jums centralizuotą ir patogią jūsų sistemos ir darbalaukio aplinkos apžvalgą.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Het informatiecentrum biedt u een gecentraliseerd en handig overzicht van uw systeem en bureaubladomgeving.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Informasjonssenteret gjev sentralisert og praktisk oversikt over systemet og skrivebordsmiljøet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Ośrodek danych zapewnia skupiony w jednym miejscu i wygodny przegląd systemu i środowiska pulpitu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Centro de Informações oferece-lhe uma visão geral centralizada e conveniente sobre o seu sistema e ambiente de trabalho.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O centro de informações fornece a você uma visão geral centralizada e conveniente de seu sistema e ambiente de trabalho.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Программа «Информация о системе» позволяет централизованно посмотреть параметры системы и окружения рабочего стола.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Informačné centrum vám poskytuje centralizovaný a pohodlný prehľad o vašom systéme a prostredí pracovnej plochy.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Informationscentralen ger dig en centraliserad och bekväm översikt av systemet och skrivbordsmiljön.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">«Центр інформації» надає вам змогу переглядати централізовано і зручно параметри вашої системи та стільничного середовища.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThe Info Center provides you with a centralized and convenient overview of your system and desktop environment.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">信息中心为您提供了一个集中和便利的系统和桌面环境概述。</p>
    <p>The information center is made up of multiple modules.  Each module is a
     separate application, but the information center organizes all of these
     programs into a convenient location.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El centre d'informació està format per múltiples mòduls. Cadascun és una aplicació individual, però el centre d'informació els reuneix tots en un lloc comú.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El centre d'informació està format per múltiples mòduls. Cadascú és una aplicació individual, però el centre d'informació els reuneix tots en un lloc comú.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Informační centrum se skládá z celé řady modulů. Každý modul je ve skutečnosti samostatná aplikace, informační centrum ale všechny tyto aplikace sdružuje do jednoho místa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Das Infozentrum besteht aus mehreren Modulen. Jedes Modul ist eine separate Anwendung, aber das Infozentrum ordnet all diese Programme bequem an einem Ort an.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">The information centre is made up of multiple modules. Each module is a separate application, but the information center organizes all of these programs into a convenient location.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">El centro de información está compuesto por múltiples módulos. Cada módulo es una aplicación separada, aunque el centro de información organiza todos estos programas en un lugar adecuado.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Informazio gunea modulu anitzez osatua dago. Modulu bakoitza aplikazio bereizi bat da, baino informazio guneak programa guzti hauek kokaleku praktiko batean kokatzen ditu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Tietokeskus koostuu moduuleista, joista kukin on erillinen sovellus. Tietokeskus järjestää nämä ohjelmat yhteen paikaan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Le centre d'informations comporte plusieurs modules. Chaque module est une application séparée, mais le centre d'informations permet de centraliser tous ces programme au sein d'un emplacement pratique.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">O centro de información está composto por varios módulos. Cada módulo é unha aplicación de seu, pero o centro de información organiza todos os programas nun lugar cómodo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Pusat informasi terdiri dari banyak modul. Setiap modul adalah sebuah aplikasi yang terpisah, tetapi pusat informasi yang mengorganisasi semua program tersebut ke dalam lokasi yang serasi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Il centro d'informazione è composto da diversi moduli; ognuno è un'applicazione a sé, ma il centro d'informazione li riunisce tutti in un posto comodo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">정보 센터는 여러 모듈로 구성되어 있습니다. 개별 모듈은 개별 프로그램이지만 정보 센터에서 한 자리에서 편하게 볼 수 있도록 모아 줍니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Informacinį centrą sudaro daug modulių. Kiekvienas modulis yra atskira programa, tačiau informacinis centras sutelkia visas šias programas į patogią vietą.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Het informatiecentrum bestaat uit verschillende modules. Elke module is een apart programma, maar het informatiecentrum organiseert al deze programma's in een handige locatie.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Informasjonssenteret består av fleire modular. Kvar modul er eit eige program, men informasjonssenteret samlar alle desse programma for enkel tilgang.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Ośrodek danych składa się z wielu części. Każda część jest osobnym programem, lecz ośrodek danych zbiera je wszystkie w jednym miejscu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O centro de informação é composto por vários módulos; cada módulo é uma aplicação separada, porém, o centro de controlo organiza todos estes programas de uma forma conveniente.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O centro de informações é formado por vários módulos, sendo que cada um deles é um aplicativo separado. Porém, ele organiza todos estes programas, em uma localização conveniente.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Она имеет модульную структуру. Каждый модуль является отдельным приложением, а приложение KInfoCenter объединяет их в одном месте.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Informačné centrum pozostáva z viacerých modulov. Každý modul je samostatnou aplikáciou, ale informačné centrum organizuje všetky tieto programy na vhodnom mieste.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Informationscentralen består av flera moduler. Varje modul är ett eget program, men informationscentralen organiserar alla dessa program på ett bekvämt ställe.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Центр інформації складається з декількох модулів. Кожен модуль є окремою програмою, але центр інформації об’єднує всі ці програми у вигляді однієї зручної оболонки.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThe information center is made up of multiple modules. Each module is a separate application, but the information center organizes all of these programs into a convenient location.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">信息中心由多个模块组成。每个模块都是一个单独的应用程序，但信息中心将所有这些程序组织在一处，形成一个方便的工具。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kinfocenter</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kinfocenter</url>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kinfocenter</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kinfocenter/kinfocenter.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <provides>
    <binary>kinfocenter</binary>
  </provides>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <releases>
    <release version="5.17.4" date="2019-12-03"/>
    <release version="5.17.3" date="2019-11-12"/>
    <release version="5.17.2" date="2019-10-29"/>
    <release version="5.17.1" date="2019-10-22"/>
  </releases>
</component>
