<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<application>
  <id type="desktop">system-config-printer.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Print Settings</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">إعدادات الطباعة</name>
  <name xml:lang="as">প্ৰিন্ট সংহতিসমূহ</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Принтерни настройки</name>
  <name xml:lang="bn_IN">প্রিন্ট সংক্রান্ত বৈশিষ্ট্য</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Ajusts d'impressió</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Nastavení tisku</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Udskriftsindstillinger</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Druckeinstellungen</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Ρυθμίσεις εκτύπωσης</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_GB">Print Settings</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Configuración de impresión</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Trükkimise seaded</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Tulostusasetukset</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Configuration de l'impression</name>
  <name xml:lang="gu">પ્રિન્ટ સુયોજનો</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">छपाई सेटिंग</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Nyomtatási beállítások</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Pengaturan Cetak</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Impostazioni di stampa</name>
  <name xml:lang="ja">印刷設定</name>
  <name xml:lang="kn">ಮುದ್ರಣದ ಸಿದ್ಧತೆಗಳು</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">인쇄 설정</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Spausdinimo nustatymai</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">Drukāšanas iestatījumi</name>
  <name xml:lang="ml">പ്രിന്റ് സജ്ജീകരണങ്ങള്‍</name>
  <name xml:lang="mr">छपाई सेटिंग्स्</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">Innstillinger for utskrift</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Afdrukinstellingen</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Utskriftoppsett</name>
  <name xml:lang="or">ମୂଦ୍ରଣୀ ସଂରଚନା</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਪਰਿੰਟ ਸੈਟਿੰਗ</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Ustawienia drukowania</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Configurações da Impressora</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Configurações da impressora</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Настройки принтера</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Nastavenia tlače</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Nastavitve tiskanja</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Подешавања штампе</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Skrivarinställningar</name>
  <name xml:lang="ta">அச்சு அமைவுகள்</name>
  <name xml:lang="te">ముద్రణ అమరికలు</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Yazıcı Ayarları</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Параметри друку</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_CN">打印设置</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_TW">列印設定值</name>
  <summary>Configure printer queues</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Configura les cues de la impressora</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Konfigurace tiskové fronty</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Konfigurer printerkøer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Konfigurieren</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Configuración de impresoras</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Tulostusjonojen asetukset</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Configurer les files d'attente d'imprimante</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Nyomtatási sorok beállítása</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Konfigurasikan antrian pencetak</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Configureer printerwachtrijen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Konfigurer skrivarkøar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Konfiguracja kolejek drukowania</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Configurar filas de impressora</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Nastavuje fronty tlačiarní</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Konfigurera skrivarköer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Yazıcı kuyruklarını yapılandır</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Налаштувати черги принтера</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">配置</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">設定</summary>

  <description>
    <p>With system-config-printer you can add, edit and delete printer queues. It allows you to choose the connection method and the printer driver.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Amb system-config-printer podeu afegir, editar i eliminar cues d'impressió. Us permet triar el mètode de connexió al controlador de la impressora.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Se system-config-printer lze přidat, upravit a odstranit tiskové fronty. Umožní vám vybrat si způsob připojení a ovladač tiskárny.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Med system-config-printer kan du tilføje, redigere og slette printerkøer. Den giver dig mulighed for at vælge forbindelsesmetoden og printerdriveren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Mit system-config-printer können Sie Drucker-Warteschlangen hinzufügen, bearbeiten und löschen. Verbindungsmethoden und Druckertreiber können damit festgelegt werden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Με το system-config-printer μπορείτε να προσθέσετε, να επεξεργαστείτε και να διαγράψετε ουρές εκτύπωσης. Σας επιτρέπει να επιλέξετε την μέθοδο σύνδεσης και τον οδηγό εκτυπωτή.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Con system-config-printer se puede agregar, editar y eliminar colas de impresoras. Esto le permite elegir el método de conexión y el controlador de la impresora.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">System-config-printerillä voi lisätä, muokata ja poistaa tulostusjonoja. Sillä voi valita yhteystavan ja tulostinajurin.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Avec system-config-printer vous pouvez ajouter, modifier et supprimer des files d'attente d'imprimante. Cela vous permet de choisir la méthode de connexion et le pilote de l'imprimante.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A system-config-printer alkalmazással hozzáadhat, szerkeszthet és törölhet nyomtatási sorokat. Lehetővé teszi a kapcsolódási módszer és a nyomtató-meghajtó kiválasztását.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Dengan system-config-printer Anda dapat menambah, menyunting, dan menghapus antrian pencetak. Ini mengizinkan Anda memilih metoda koneksi dan penggerak pencetak.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Met system-config-printer kun je wachtrijen toevoegen, bewerken en verwijderen. Het laat je een verbindingsmethode en printerstuurprogramma kiezen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Med system-config-printer kan du leggje til, endre og slette skrivarkø. Du kan og velgje type oppkopling og skrivardrivar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Za pomocą programu system-config-printer można dodawać, modyfikować i usuwać kolejki drukarek. Umożliwia on wybieranie metody połączenia i sterownika drukarki.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Com o system-config-printer pode adicionar, alterar e apagar impressoras. Permite que escolha o método de ligação e o driver da impressora.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Com o system-config-printer você pode adicionar, editar e deletar filas de impressão. Ele permite que você escolha o método de conexão e o driver da impressora. </p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">С system-config-printer вы можете добавлять, изменять и удалять очереди принтера. Утилита позволяет вам выбрать метод подключения и драйвер для принтера.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">S programom system-config-printer môžete pridávať, upravovať a odstraňovať tlačové fronty. Umožňuje vám zvoliť spôsob pripojenia a ovládač tlačiarne.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Са system-config-printer можете додати, изменити и уклонити редове за чекање штампача. Такође вам дозвољава да бирате начин повезивања и управљачки програм штампача.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Med system-config-printer kan du lägga till, redigera och ta bort skrivarköer.  Det låter dig välja anslutningsmetod och skrivardrivrutin.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">За допомогою system-config-printer ви можете додавати, змінювати та вилучати записи черги завдань принтера. Програма надає вам змогу вибрати спосіб з’єднання комп’ютера з принтером та драйвер принтера.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">您可以用system-config-printer来添加、管理以及删除打印机队列。它可以用来选择连接方式和打印机驱动。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">有了 system-config-printer，您便能加入、編輯、和刪除印表機佇列，並讓您選擇連線方法與印表機驅動程式。</p>

    <p>For each queue, you can adjust the default page size and other driver options, as well as seeing ink/toner levels and status messages.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Per a cada cua, podeu ajustar la mida de la pàgina per defecte i altres opcions del controlador, així com visualitzar els nivells de tintat/tòner i els missatges d'estat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Pro každou tiskovou frontu lze nastavit výchozí velikost stránky a další možnosti ovladače, stejně jako vidět množství inkoustu / toneru a zprávy o stavu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Du kan justere standard-sidestørrelse og andre driver-indstillinger for hver kø, såvel som at se blæk-/toner-niveauer og statusbeskeder.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Für jede Warteschlange kann die Vorgabe-Seitengröße und weitere Druckoptionen angepasst werden, sowie Füllstände und Statusmeldungen eingesehen werden. </p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Για κάθε ουρά, μπορείτε να προσαρμόσετε το προκαθορισμένο μέγεθος σελίδας και άλλες επιλογές του οδηγού, όπως επίσης και να βλέπετε τα επίπεδα μελανιού/τόνερ και τα κατάστασης μηνύματα.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Para cada cola, usted puede ajustar el tamaño de página por defecto y otras opciones del controlador, así como ver los niveles de tinta/toner y el estado de los mensajes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Voit asettaa kunkin jonon oletusarvoisen paperikoon ja muut tulostusasetukset, ja näet muste- ja väriainemäärät ja tilaviestit.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Pour chaque file d'attente, vous pouvez ajuster la taille de la page par défaut et d'autres options de pilote, ainsi que consulter les niveaux d'encre et les messages de statut.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Minden sornál megadhatja az alapértelmezett lapméretet és más meghajtó-beállításokat, valamint megtekintheti a tinta/toner szintjét és az állapotüzeneteket.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Untuk setiap antrian, Anda dapat menyetel ukuran halaman baku dan opsi penggerak lain, maupun melihat ingkat tinta/toner dan pesan status.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Voor elke wachtrij kun je de standaard paginagrootte en andere stuurprogrammaopties aanpassen, naast het bekijken van inkt-/tonerniveaus en statusboodschappen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">For kvar kø kan du justere standardstorleik på sida og andre drivarval, samt sjå blekk-/tonarnivå og statusbeskjeder.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Dla każdej kolejki można ustawiać oddzielny domyślny rozmiar strony i inne opcje sterownika, a także wyświetlać poziom tuszu/toneru i komunikaty stanu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Para cada fila de espera, pode ajustar o tamanho da página por omissão e outras opções do driver, assim como ver os níveis da tinta / do toner e mensagens de estado.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Para cada fila, você pode ajustar o tamanho de página padrão e outras opções de drivers, assim como checar o nível de tinta/toner e mensagens de status. </p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Для каждой очереди вы можете настроить размер страницы по умолчанию и другие параметры драйвера, такие как отображение уровня чернил\тонера и сообщения о состоянии.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Pre každú frontu môžete upraviť predvolenú veľkosť stránky a iné voľby ovládača, ako zobrazenie úrovní a stavových správ atramentu alebo toneru.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">За сваки ред, можете подесити подразумевану величину странице и остале опције управљачког програма, као и надзор нивоа мастила/тонера и статусне поруке.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">För varje kö kan du justera standard sidstorlek och andra skrivarinställningar, samt se bläck-/tonernivåer och statusmeddelanden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Для кожної з черг завдань ви можете вказати типовий розмір аркуша та інші параметри драйвера. Також програма надає змогу переглядати дані щодо рівня чорнила або тонера у картриджі та повідомлення щодо стану.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">对于每个队列，您可以调整默认页面尺寸和其他驱动选项，以及查看墨水/墨粉余量和状态信息。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_TW">每一個佇列您都能調整預設紙張大小、其他驅動程式選項、以及查看墨水/碳粉使用程度與狀態訊息。</p>
  </description>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot width="624" type="default" height="351">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/zdohnal/system-config-printer/master/data/screenshot-mainwindow.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="752" height="423">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/zdohnal/system-config-printer/master/data/screenshot-properties.png</screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/zdohnal/system-config-printer/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/zdohnal/system-config-printer/issues</url>

  <provides>
    <binary>system-config-printer</binary>
    <dbus type="system">org.fedoraproject.Config.Printing</dbus>
  </provides>

  <updatecontact>zdohnal@redhat.com</updatecontact>
</application>